Hmm
Seeing as the far is before the first word was spoken
And dark as the space where the silence is broken
You hold the pair at the sword and the song
You speak from the edges where truth has belonged
great art form was born from your name you are the word in the throat before language
you are the music beneath every madness
Goddess of the spoken and the unspoken
Matanji, Matanji
Every vow I make is your token
You are the song that was always inside me
Green fire, dark grace, come and find me
Shaman
You rise from the river Bane
Fierce and unbounded, where the clean and the sacred were never quite founded.
The offerings you love are the ones left behind, the discarded, the broken, the searching mind.
You teach us the altar is not always marble, that truth lives in fragments.
and smoke and in sorrow you are the rebel that holiness needed you are the prayer that refused to be seated
shout my love, shout my love, God I saw the spoken in the end the spoken my tangy, my tangy
every vow I make is your token you are the song
Let every word carry your green benediction
Let every silence be sacred and taught
Oh, my tongue is...
It's a cozy cave. It's a cozy little cave.
You hear me okay? Let me just test my mic.
Check, mic check.
I think it's working.
What's up? Goddy, Goddy, Goddy.
Let me throw something to you.
Hold on.
Everyone having a good day?
I hope so.
Okay, just a moment.
Yeah, maybe I'll change the background.
It's a little bit too much graffiti.
Got a time?
Okay, hold on.
Never say I didn't keep my promises.
Hey, let me change the background.
I think that is how's everybody doing. Let me see. Let me shout at everybody in the chat.
Thing that is gaudy. Thank you Chanel. Chanel, bad bitch.
Um, no, I don't think I don't think so. I don't think we're part of that at that part of this the cycle again
That go yet. Hey turn. What's up? Thanks for being your turn
Let's see less smelly cat is here. What's up guys? I
Look okay, I don't know. I have no idea who that was midnight. You can't stand it
Maybe if you came with a better attitude and didn't come in vomiting
And I'm just like trying to start the show and just take down the vibe of everybody
Maybe you wouldn't get timed out for two minutes or something. I don't know
Hmm
So then to think about
I tricks I tricks
No, let's not let's not do that
I think midnight when midnight has a better attitude and is a little bit, I mean, I understand trolls and stuff, but it's like, you know, I don't like appreciate necessarily.
Okay, thank you so much. Let me, let me handle the, let me handle the runches here. I only have a certain limited amount to get out. Okay.
I like to at least come in with like hey what's up psyche instead of like a vomiting emoji face
I'm just like playing like a two-minute song to start the show
Hey tower you good evening
Hi, oh, this is tricks. How is everyone doing good to see everybody? Okay
I don't care if you don't you can just say you know you don't have to be here
You don't have to like you know be mean to me about it and stuff
Kind of like kind of like is that a kind of concert for any or the concert and it's like not just like it's like
Yes, it's heavily assisted with AI. I mean I can't play the instruments myself and everything but that was like
That was a dedication to my goddess and stuff. So appreciate you not throwing up
But anyway, let me throw out the link
Say hi
I mean, that is beautiful. I love her cat Williams look a transsexual Jesus Christ
Who's the clean face? Yeah, handsome young man. Oh, not clean face, but yeah, I don't know. I
Don't know you look okay
Dear John dear John by the time you read this note, I'll be gone and you remember that
Yeah, anyone remember that uh that song
Good to see ya
I'm still drinking the McDonald's coffee.
See McDonald's doesn't do too bad for the look.
Looking dapper.
I don't know, just took a little shower.
Put my hair back a little bit.
Put on a nice white shirt.
Vacuumed my house, cleaned up a little bit.
Just thought I'd come in with a little bit.
I mean, it doesn't have to change the way she is.
Like if I time it somebody out, they can't like, you know, it's not the end of the world. I've been actually hidden from chats
That actually didn't really do anything. I mean, I'm not actually like a even a mean troll, you know
Like that white shirt. Thank you so much
Thoughts up did or anything. Okay. Let me let me see. What kind of background do I want? Let me see. How about like a cool
Let me see. Oh
How about some beautiful this looks good, so you try this one
Feeling a little bit like Roman tonight
Well, this is dedicated to actually
Midnight because you know what they call a bad bitch cake mix apologizes. Okay. It's okay. I'll
When I go to my
Stream yard or integrate my studio. I'll I'll look at Kate my cake mix
I think he makes it we did have a rogue mod guys
And so I'm sorry if like, you know, if I find your if you find yourself hitting and stuff, you know, let someone know
Because you know, I have like hundreds of people on that list and I had a rogue mod and stuff or maybe a couple of road mods
Thank you for the two dollars. I appreciate that very much and I will go look ASAP for you
Okay, I'll look during the show and a little a little break cake mix. Okay. What's the comeback?
I can look at it in a second. Let me just put this back earned up and I'll go
That wasn't very polite. I'll look for a look in a second
Sometimes but sometimes he's not like, you know, I did have somebody named
Had a mod and they all of a sudden the mod disappeared, but in their place. It's that sweet pee was here
You know that and I found a lot of my very good friends hidden
Anybody with that a wrench, but I mean because I did on mod like almost everybody before and so there's some people
I'm fortunate that I'm protected for a second. So I will go check, but let me just put this up real quick
Have a list of us have a beautiful run. Oh, yeah, so this is dedicated to midnight because you know what they call a
Roman shower
Have you ever heard of that term a Roman shower?
It's basically when someone vomits on you during sex.
She left YouTube?
Well, that's why it says Sweepy was here, I guess.
She left, but she left her mark.
She left her mark in my chat.
Yeah, it was a few days ago.
I think it was when she left.
I told her,
You know peace. I would like, you know, I always told her she could use my clips
I asked her if she cannot encourage
You know, I've been making me like
Bald which is now, you know, but I'm not bald. I mean, I'm pulling my hair back. This is part of the girls
Is that bald? I don't know but I was like don't alter my like actual actual image makes it look like
But uh, I know
Argue us the whole day. Yeah. Yeah
I had a dream about sweepy last night and I dream that she was like obsessed with me and there's like this album
And I had my baby pictures in it with all this like burnt like all this Burma
I was like is this because she was trying to kill my inner child or something
Could be you know for example, you know Tommy James came on my show last night
And I was sick, you know, I try to be gracious to guests when they're when they're here
You know that I let up and I was like I respect him as a content creator
I played some of his content and we all had a laugh when he was like, you know acting the fool and the
Tempur-pedic mattress store and you know asking for poop fish and saying that the fish counter at the supermarket smelled like his girlfriend or something
but
You know, he was like came on he's like, oh, you know, he's just friendly and he's like I have no problem
And I was like, you know, I was like, I think I mentioned and be this chat today. I said hey, you know
I taught me James on my show and he was perfectly cordial and I was cool with them. He's cool with me
Then he comes on her.
Oh, Psyche, I was, I'm not cool with him.
I just came on to see Q, Q45.
I hate Psyche.
He's the worst.
I mean, it was like, whoa,
you weren't like that at all on my show,
but okay, and I confronted him on it.
And, you know, there's a lot of hypocrisy going on.
There's a lot of, like for example,
my friend, DJ Electra,
who I met and introduced to a lot of people.
Betis and I'm in contact with currently talking privately and stuff, you know, none of probably do business about what but
Betis said leave DJ Electra the fuck alone
And I'd let her know that and she's like what why the fuck would she say that I
Don't know
I don't know, I don't know why she say that.
Also, oh, you're stalking, you know,
stay away from Elisa and I'm talking to Elisa tonight
on perfectly good terms.
I don't understand what this thing is about.
Look at all these women, he's stalking.
You're like, oh, why are you bothering her?
I haven't literally been in her chat
because I didn't want to bother her
because I get a bunch of trolls following me
and harassing me in the chat
and I just didn't want to bring down her chat.
So I kind of stopped commenting in her chat and stuff.
But it's like really crazy how it's just like,
people just lie.
We didn't roam.
Do as the Romans do, right?
You know in the Roman bath they had a Roman bath house and they used to actually just like I'll be like taking a dump
And like around it and they would share the same sponge to wipe
That's pretty horrid that's pretty horrid
No Alexander McQueen he I mean he he he did get back his like his standard mod officially today and
I look more Greek than Roman, maybe. I've been to Greece actually, but I think America is in a way
almost a new Rome. Actually, I think probably the Roman Empire is officially ruled from probably
Greenland, which is icy. Greenland is icy. Iceland is green. I don't know. It's very confusing.
Yeah, but if you look at all our government buildings and the architecture and the laws and all this kind of stuff
We are very heavily influenced by Rome, you know, and so I think that's kind of interesting
Let me just pull this a little bit. I don't want to unplug the thing. I'd be careful a little okay
I don't want to spray someone this is unstoppable, you know, cuz I'm unstoppable guys. I'm unstoppable
So this is a perfect spray to
Fresh in the air a little bit. Let's clear the air
Yeah, but it was particularly really rude and I was like one thing I did say that I kind of like do believe and I don't want to
Dwell on any of this, but I said hey wouldn't be nice to play even past
You know we take this YouTube shit so seriously and how about and bet you know, but all these bad things are happening. How about like
Beyond that we could be like
You know, maybe going a clink-link and like, you know kind of just laughing and saying, you know, it's a show
It's silly things. It's like this is just like kind of a make-believe universe. We're in in a certain way, right?
all based on just
Screens and and people behind cameras and I mean all this kind of stuff people and characters people
but it's like when it when things go offline it's kind of
Pray page looks Roman much. It looks like a black foot to me a little bit a black foot
But um
Yeah, but I wish that message would have been kind of more well received
But no, it's like I'm just a piece of shit and I'm just you know the worst person in the world and
disgusting and horrible and nasty and
It's just horrible doxer and you know
When all these things are happening to me and it's like
It's like nothing right
but um
You know, I just wish people
Could take things a little less seriously sometimes, you know, I do
Troll sometimes, you know back at people
I'm the worst person in the world midnight. Oh, I'm not okay. Thank God. I didn't see and I see that's the problem
Too is like sometimes I'm just read stuff and it's like I already assume and it's like, you know when I assume
I make an ass out of me and you and I'm sorry if I
Incorrectly judge. Okay. Let me see. Well cake mix. I'll see if I can find the cake mix person real quick. Hold on
Because I did get a nice super chat and so I think that does get priority for like checking out the
checking out my block list and
Seeing if I can clear things up and I'll give them another chance. I mean, you know, if someone comes and
You know, let's me know about hey, maybe and it's like I won't even check like what I can I can actually check their history and stuff
It's see like what they're saying, but
Yeah, I had kind of a interesting night last night. So it's my name is cake mix. Okay. Let me see if I got me
Just I have to scan kind of fast. Just give me a second. I have to scan. I'm just scanning
scan scan scan
for cake mix
Is there a cake mix on the list?
Let me see Luke. Oh some of these names
Oh my god some of these names and people that are like oh just um if you were to see this list of names I
Mean I've read it a few times, but some of these names are absolutely
Revolting and shocking and it's like and Docs Docs thing. Oh my gosh
Climb that okay one second
Cake mix. Oh, I found cake mix. Okay. Your wish is my command. Your wish has been granted cake mix
You get another chance step up
So it's a beautiful night in Rome, you know, I'm on this bit. Oh my god, my armors disappeared
What's that? Oh my gosh, this is the callus I have from
It's not dirty or anything. It's actually just a callus from
Okay, no, no long long dong silver that will not be happening tonight. Okay, you're lucky enough to be in the chat
Your name is terrible too long dong silver. That sounds like that sounds like a
Trollish kind of name, but you know trolls are welcoming as long as they behave themselves
I do have you know cattle prods and stuff
I'm getting sort of wrenches. I gave them give the mods cattle prods and
So, if you feel like a sharp electrical zzzz, you know, on your back and stuff and your
butt, Gotti, don't put it up, don't put it up it, you know, just light, do it light on
the arm or something, because midnight did a vomiting face in Rome when you throw up
on someone that's called a Roman shower.
Is Halo? Halo was hidden. I unhid Halo. Yeah, I unhid Halo. Um, that was the rogue mod, I think
You know, there was maybe a few of them. I did have to unmod some people unfortunately
I'm feeling Romans and I'm just feeling like fucking going to the Colosseum and watching like some gladiators
Oh, hello gladiator and gladiator movies are so hot
Sorry, sorry, sorry
Sometimes they get a little excited. Do you know those things? Oh, oh, oh my god
Midnight, no, no, no, no, no that sounds like some kind of mini Manson
It sounds like that sounds like the next mini Manson picture I'm gonna get and I don't want to see it
I don't want to see it
No, I don't think Alex C. Taylor, but I am I'll
You know there's a lot of there's like a lot of like I have friends that were like hidden and stuff
I like that have nothing to do with where it really much like they got this lady Capricorn
Soul tribe. That's a great friend of mine. The great supporter just like this awesome lady
And she's on the bland list and hey those of them bail us. I was like who hit and Alex
I looked at and Alice didn't hide anybody Alex timed out some people most people were freaking take time up for 10 seconds
Some people the other night
that were threatening our lives.
We were actually being said I'd be swatted and murdered
by the next morning and we were docked on IP2
and blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
All this crap.
So it's like, we were under siege
and it's like a lot of people, you know,
and some people just for their protection out.
Like, you know, I didn't want them to get, you know,
hurt in the cat and stuff.
And so they were timed out for maybe an hour or something
while I wrapped up the show and stuff.
But let me put up the link again.
Yeah, good morning, Tim Kisco. Let's see what else is here midnight again is here. Hey midnight. How are you?
It's Samantha Avery
You know thing that is we did a funny thing yesterday, you know
I thought the insulting I'm at the transcripting things I do and like my new website and I get all this
You know people that actually check it out like most people are like, oh my god
He's gonna steal my identity or something like I'm some kind of like
horrible, you know, thief or, I mean, I'm just like setting this up to, I guess they're
particularly of Alexander's story. I'm setting this all up to actually black males, the audience
and the streamers and stuff. It's like, that is not true. I mean, it's like.
That is actually the furthest thing from my mind.
I was like, you know, I don't know how long
this channel will be here.
I want to test them into it.
I want all the transcripts.
I want to analyze transcripts.
I want to, so last night we analyzed thing that is.
And interestingly, you know, it gets mixed up sometimes.
It thought things that isn't Mason were the same person.
And so there was a little conflicting information.
It was a little bit interesting.
Think that is is not Mason. I've seen them both on camera. So I know for sure. He's not Mason unless there's a really really good
Filter and ventriloquism involved and stuff, but it said like one really good thing it said
Thing that is is kind of like the philosopher of the chat in that in all the chaos and all the negativity
He's he stays
Calm and neutral and grounded and that's kind of like a miracle in itself and it's interesting
I mean it was just like it put it kind of in a cool way. I don't know
I got chills thing that is I think may have got chills. I think he was impressed with the technology. It's like I mean
Literally, it's like people expect me to like hand code everything to hand
I think they want me to write at the transcripts out with like a quill and a
Feather and then to like I mean it literally that way it would take me
the rest of my life and then everyone would be already passed away and then no one would even care.
So I have to like you know have things that help me do things that I don't even know how long I'll
be here with all the threats I'm getting right. I don't know how long I'll all remain on this earth.
So I wanted to test submit to my show and a way to search every episode and you know and it's like
now there's technology that can assist me like no one had a problem the calculator came out.
That's blasphemy. He should be using a ledger even though my father did to to the end. He never used a computer
He always would use this old-fashioned ledger and would like we would do math that way and stuff
And you know, he was but he was very brilliant man patient man. He came from a different time, right?
He did have a calculator and stuff and hey Rudy did have a calculator and stuff, but
me to say
you know
There's you can do it both ways, but there's like kind of old-fashioned methods and it's like methods people are comfortable with
I'm comfortable with using technology and using the latest technology and
Seeing what I can do with it and doing things people haven't thought of and I mean there that's possible now and it's so cool
It's really cool, you know
And so it's like the people that are just denigrating me and they say oh
Look at how he's just lazy and blah blah
I'm not lazy. I'm just motivated to get
everything out in the best way and also there's these
miracle
There's miracles that can be accomplished that maybe I mean the human beings are intelligent
But it's like kids are there that many human calculators really that can just like what's eighty five thousand six hundred and seventy five divided by
Sixty-four. We're now no, no, no, no, no, no. I want it right now. How many people can do that?
Or you can go 78,664 divided by 60.
Oh, and there's the answer.
You might get my analogies or metaphors, maybe not.
But I figured out basically it's just some people
that you'll just never please.
And no matter what you say,
they'll say, I just take this one streamer
and he was, you know, he had a nine to five
but then he would be streaming.
And he had a pretty much a troll audience, and they would say...
Well, you're not oh shit, they would say you're not dedicated to streaming quit your job and be a full-time streamer
Blah-blah, and he eventually did think he got trolled into quitting his job
And then he knew what they said. Oh you dirty bum
You're just streaming get a job get a job
That's like kind of what I'm being told now get a job and I actually have a job too
Which is the ironic part and I keep explaining explaining explaining I say things a million time
It'll still be the scenario. It's frustrating sometime
But I do want to announce, you know, that I have been accepted into like an actual internet gang and it's like, you know,
I'll be getting a duck tattoo. I am a quacker. I guess I'm in the quacker gang now.
You know, so if you're gonna be quacking and stuff, it might be at a fellow duck gang member.
Hey, what's up Ziggy, and I don't know why you were timed out today. It didn't sound like anything that...
No, it's not the bean gang not at all. No, it's it's the quacker gang
I'm in the quacker gang. So I got I go quack quack quack
Never heard of it. Well good
Let's you know about it the batter
Anyway, anyway, I'm just I'm just kidding. I'm just oh my gosh, I'm getting it called from Texas
Well, I'm sorry. I'm on the air right now. I can't take a phone call. You'll have to leave a message
Hopefully it's not too rude.
Hey Lola, I want to come up here and hang out with me.
Come here Lola.
Hi, come up here.
Come up Lola.
Hey, hey babe.
I miss Lola.
This is a beautiful cat.
This cat is, you know, she is spayed.
Like I've said again, everyone's like, get your cats fixed.
You filthy human being.
You filthy excuse of a cat on her animal abuser.
Your cats hate you
You kill your cat to eat your cat and
So the first thing but if they say you get your cats your cats spayed an eater, I'll say
well actually
Out of my four cats, I've had four cats for
Man probably about almost a year now
You know
And people keep saying, well, what happened to the other five cats?
Well, I did have a litter of kittens.
And what would happen if I had nine cats?
Would I not be getting animal control called on me?
This person has nine cats?
Oh my god.
I mean, it's like so ridiculous, right?
Yeah, the kittens went to another home, you know?
Hello.
Kisses hi sweetheart. Yeah some other homes and stuff you never hear see that word is way over used
You'd rather show a chopstick into your eyes. You're what what I'm sorry
I'm gonna join the Aldi army. No, no, no, but Aldi was really cool last night because he's like, you know what?
Fuck some of these people like
This site fucking sale should do you and then like they only expect you to defend yourself and they're all ganging up on you
But now I do have the Quackers. I have some I have a few fellow ducks
To uh, you know, I guess peck out the eyes of our enemies with our beat or there are their duck bills
And yeah, hi Lola, but yeah tricks. I mean there are
Stay in neuter clinics and when I find one that is like, you know nearby and I'm
able to you know get everything together, you know
Maybe that will happen soon, but Trixie is not really a wanderer. He likes to stay close. He's right here
I mean he's here all the time
Do I have yeah, I'm in the Quackers I'm in the Quacker gang
There we go. Where's Trixie?
oh there you are hi babe yeah and it's like and some people would say cutting off the balls of
a cat is abuse I mean so that that's something you neutered your cat how dare you kick you tied
up his balls that's terrible sorry I lost my voice a little bit when I tried to do the higher pitched
You know can I join your server sure I can Ziggy if you can you can you don't have to come on the panel
But if you want to drop that link backstage
Just you're coming up backstage. Hey, K. Oh, how are you? You want to drop that link backstage? You know, that's cool
Hi
Hi everybody, how's everyone doing?
I'd be happy to join you. You're not good. Well, I don't think have you been have you been initiated?
You know the initiation for the for the quackers gang is quite violent
Yeah, you could you hear it like you don't know when it will happen
but before you know it you'll hear like quack quack and then you'll hear like
Some feathers ruffling and then when you turn around you're just surrounded by these ducks
And you think they're about to tell an alive you and stuff
That's what I thought
And they beat me up pretty bad.
I still have the pec marks and stuff.
But afterward, when I was just like laying on the ground
and it kind of composed me like,
oh my God, please don't kill me.
And they're like,
you just passed your initiation.
And then we ate a bunch of breadcrumbs and had wine.
And it was like pretty much the best night of my life.
know but next so next I have to get a duck and so thank God I got all that
concrete because I was able to actually make a duck pond and so I have a nice
area for them okay thank you Ziggy I'll get it right now hold on and I'll let
you on key one second
um shit hold on
Hmm
Hold on Ziggy I'm gonna fringe you on discord and then if you can invite like accept my friendship and then invite me that way
Because I don't I'm not able to set up the discord in my browser
It's just like so complicated logging in they have all these like codes and it's kind of confusing even for me
And I I know how to use computers and stuff
So if you can help if you can just accept my friendship and then you can invite me and you don't have to stay friends with me
But I would like you know be cool if you could because then we could like you know
Have have a have a bro to bro conversation once in a while. Okay, so let me see
Discord
And I got your screen name.
Okay, let me see, add friends.
Just sorry Q, I'll be right there.
I'll be right there.
I'll write that homie in a second.
Okay, friends, add friends.
Let me put this name in.
I do have the StreamYard or the Discord software.
Okay, I sent you a friend request.
If you can answer that friend request
and I'll let Q write up.
Q, can you not like not even like a fake porn bomb because that does that I don't like that kind of stuff
Like because that can like trigger algorithms or like people reporting and it's just like a pain in the butt to like
Have to like delete and start over and stuff if you can just respect me with that and
Just go a little bit easy on the n-word and no threatening people. Please. Okay, hope you can agree to that rule and let's
Welcome Q to the show
I said the n-word before
I know I know I'm trying to I'm trying to turn over a new leap. It's a fun word to say sometimes
But when I said it it's now turned into a scandal
I mean there's people that just say all day all night and every other word
Did he just do it guys, okay, you showed his pussy, that's fine. Oh
That's
I'm sorry, that's my ginger. That's ginger. Maybe ginger. Hi, ginger
You know how you know if you mix around the word
That's why I love him so much. I'm gonna name my manager. I'm gonna name my cat my next manager, okay?
Yeah, you get it
He's a big boy. We're dark. Oh look it on his oh look
Yeah, he trusts you because you're petting his belly and cats really will not let you touch their belly unless they really trust and love you
You know hey, I rescued this little n-word. Yeah
And I really, like I said last night, I was like,
you know what, I see good, I see good in you.
I know that I don't want to hurt your rotation
or embarrass your unity, but I see good in you.
And I think some good things have happened to you
because there is that good in you.
And I mean, I see some people that maybe are,
in the words of Amanda, maybe lost souls,
not lost causes necessarily,
because I think anybody can like,
Change for the better, but I see you as like, you know, just having basically a good heart
Maybe a little rough around the edges. Maybe a little bit salty, you know, I wouldn't want to piss you off
Seriously, I think you might you might you know, I might get maced. I'm just kidding. Okay. Okay
Midnight that's midnight for you to come on to this channel and talk about cutting cat time off is crazy
This whole channel is like built off of cats
Right. This channel is a cat loving channel.
This is one of the places where you're supposed to come and show your cat.
Right. Everyone's welcome to show their pussy on this show.
Yeah. Speaking of pussies, where's the female cat that I own?
Have you, worse, have you, has she been around?
Have you seen her today?
What's happened?
Oh, I see her all the time.
She's, she's definitely in this room.
I just don't know where she's at.
She's probably under the bed.
He's hiding.
She's, or is she taking a little, a little cat nap?
Her and her brother don't really go far from each other.
They're kind of like, you know,
they're kind of like bonded together.
Hi, yin and yang.
Hey, we have another guest coming up.
Can we welcome live from the beautiful oceans.
of Canada. Welcome to the show. Oh, is she at the door? Oh, oh, no. Oh, sorry. I'm sorry.
It's all good fun. Okay. It's all good fun. Oh, great. The devil, the devil is manipulating
me today. Oh, is that right? I am not the devil Q neither. How are you doing? Good.
Look at her with her cat. Look at her cat. Oh, is that part B? Yeah
Same pattern as ginger but different colors and you know, it's funny Q. She actually when the Sun hits her grapher
She's like an undertone of like ginger like red henna
The Nord too, the Nord's a black cat, but when she lays in the sun, you see this dark red almost fur, like she's like, really, she's a dark red.
Yeah, same as me.
The chat saying hey to pay.
Turn your echo cancellation on, woman.
Hey, I'm sorry guys, just give me a sec.
You're absolutely fine, you're absolutely fine.
Yeah, how's everyone doing? Yeah, I wouldn't say hi to Paige. Do you want to join the panel?
I guess I can try to pin the link tonight, and you know, we're gonna have I want a good vibe show tonight
You know, it's like
I'm gonna come up to Chris Lanny you're welcome up and sit to say hi and to hang out she's always been
She's just a nice on the show, and I appreciate
That and I got a lot. Oh, we have another guest coming on. Let's welcome to the show
Live from New York and I don't
Live from New York we have
Yeah. That's who? Porky pig. Oh,
it's porky pig. I didn't know
Oh, that's horrifying.
That is absolutely horrifying.
I mean, if I was, if I was, if I was buying.
See, I'll change it for you.
I'll change it for you.
OK, it's scaring me too much.
I've got you, psyche.
I've got you.
OK, perfect.
Oh, I like that one.
I like that one.
OK, that's better.
That, that, of course, is a big, scary feeling.
And the one in the show is empty.
No, you thought, you thought it was flying.
Yeah, you thought it was flying.
Copy this.
For New York City.
Are you from New York? You're from New York City, right? Yeah, it's not like one of those gay guys from New York City a lot of
Well every other guy from New York City that I meet on here, they're always gay, I don't know
I was just I thought it was I thought it was a thing there
No, I'm just kidding, no, um, yeah, like I said, I'm, I'm going to stream crack your
stream, crack your stream, yeah, stream, crack, quacker.
Yeah.
Hey, midnight.
We're not bringing that up.
I only hit on page when I'm drunk.
I'm not drunk.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, we're.
Oh, that's me.
Oh, what a thing.
Page alone.
Okay.
Leave your page alone.
Hey.
She doesn't need your defending boy. I'm gonna be a white knight right now. See my white. Yeah. Yeah, leave page alone
Oh, I'm gonna say no, I'm gonna say she said she's not interested in like eat eating
So yeah, yeah, yeah, I never said anything about that
If he's I was just responding to what somebody said in the chat, that's all
Yeah, yeah, definitely
Just might not have been here for it. That's all
Yeah, I'm we I'm waiting for I'm crack crack to come up
Another quacker coming
I'm waiting for Alex I'm waiting for Alex to come up too. Oh come on. That's the whole the whole gang will be here
I love it. I love it
I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I
Yeah, but, um, yeah, we're all
right there. Oh,
yeah.
Okay, but how orange can you
you. How orange can you go?
Oh, I know you like that orange and you find out. Hey, look at this. Oh, there's, there's ginger. There's one right here.
Tricks is somewhere around here. So, you're a pretty orange face ginger. You're, you're gorgeous.
Oh, you're pretty. Look. Oh my god. Oh, the north is knocked the pillow on the floor. Oh my gosh.
North. Show your orange face. Oh my gosh. There you go. The north is knocked over the pillow on the floor and jumped off.
she was parachuting oh wait I hear I hear somebody clawing at the door are you ready for this
and it's oh you can't really see her because she's too damn black
yo bro you look dirty that's the who looks dirty
That's cute. He's that's a child. Yeah, cuz these fucking are you talking about all the pieces of this cardboard bag
That are all over the floor cuz these little fuckers ripped open a cardboard bag and fucking the board all over the place
I understand like Lenore will actually like wrestle with a roll of paper towels and like just shred it
yeah that's a really clean like animals with themselves but they like to make a mess they
tear shit up dude they tear they get bored and tear shit up and it's always these fucking brown
paper bags that i get from the dispensary uh when i buy weed they fucking tear those things up
You know, it's crazy is like, I don't know if weed has like that whack-ass
Just in certain oils or certain other herbs if you will I guess cats like my cast go crazy
You live in New York City. There's probably that fucking lace-ass fucking
And the cat's, because the cat's in anxiety.
Oh, I know who's that.
That's that fat boy who pulled him on me.
He's not fat, Q.
He's not fat.
I'm not fat at all.
Oh, I thought he was that fat boy, Zigg.
Oh, no.
You sound like Zigg.
Yeah, I sound like Zigg.
You sound retarded.
You sound like a bitch.
You sound like one of those fucking gay boys from New York City.
Oh yeah, Papa.
Yeah, we cooking Papa, stand on business, Papa, stand on business, Papa.
Guys, good vibes only in that piece.
You know, I've had enough heart for it all.
Yo, you funny, yo.
Calling all your grown men pop off my heart.
Yo, yo, you funny, bro.
I stand on business in the heart.
They're bonding over you.
You're fucking crazy.
That's fine, that's fine.
They're bonding over you right now.
I met enough of you fucking New York fucking n-words on here.
Yeah, yeah, you ugly.
Yeah
Puts it on my gladiator, bitch
Hey, I'm not sick.
Stig looks like fucking Squidward's house, okay?
That is not me.
No, he's just fucking with you. He does live in the Bronx though, but he won't
Know I know I know where he lives. I see him both of the liquor shop
He said he lives near the the Joker stares where the Joker movies stairs, you know to me in the Bronx
He said he lives
All the way from where he lives or where he's from but my friends
untrackable
What a checkable
What's up, man. What's up,
man. What's up, man. What's up,
man. What's up, man. What's
Oh my god, she's at the window, right? She's at the window, right?
The Norris
I think that's the one that's outside. I
Love building today. I see the choreo is on a show. Oh, yeah, she's at the window
It was on a show and she said
Yo, yo, you from the project you project boy
Well, um, Victoria said, oh my God say he turned around and he bent over to show me his back side and
His ball sack it was disgusting. Oh my gosh. I mean it's like salmon the first time's free
But you know, it's first time is free, but I don't have to find you
All over my dick all the time, every day, all day.
Well, what you like hanging over here?
All over my dick, all day, every day.
What we don't go live, nigga?
What you like hanging over here?
You're here, Sam.
You want to watch my stream?
You want to watch me go live, baby boy?
Go watch Go Live, nigga.
You want to watch me go live?
That's cute.
What happened?
Nothing I was I know I was just I was just rolling down the he just made a argue with
No, no, no, I'm chilling with our page. How you doing? God bless America. I'm here chilling baby. What are you getting angry?
door-to-door Oh
You're trying to dox me. What you mean door-to-door? What do you mean? He's always trying to dox my job
That's your job door-to-door
I didn't know that's a door-to-door salesman. What's wrong with that? I make hella money doing that. I make
I know you're a doctor and you were just talking about dangerous kids the other day too, so you you break all your own rules
Yeah, oh look at me
Look you think niggas gonna run with an error
I don't want to look at you because you look like your mother, like Shrek.
Yo, why you slip in the tent door-to-door nigga pussy?
Okay, let's watch our language.
Your mother and your sister look exactly alike and it's very hard to.
Door-to-door, I never do the door-to-door.
Look at them, they're disgusting.
You sell diamonds? What'd you sell? Dimes? What'd you sell? Dimes or nickels?
Jesus Christ.
Door to door, what'd you do?
Smoke weed?
What'd you say weed?
What'd you say, papa?
We do sit on discord all day and cry like a woman.
How I'm doxin' saying door to door.
All you do is sit on discord all day and cry like a woman.
You're the reason why I asked Mr. L.E.S. here.
You're the reason why I asked Mr. L.E.S. here if he was one of those New York faggots,
because you're the prime example of one of those New York faggots that I was talking about.
Oh, shit.
What the fuck?
You crying, though, about your job?
Literally, Les, this is why I asked you this, because of him.
This is why you hot! This is why you hot!
I'm going to door to door.
You're a gay boy. All you do is sit on discord all day and gossip like a fucking woman.
That's your whole life. That's your whole life.
Enjoy. Enjoy papa.
Enjoy papa.
I'm gay.
You hotboxed your fucking, you hotboxed the cat that you were watching, didn't you?
Didn't you hotbox that cat that you were watching?
I'm hot boxin' my cat.
You really give a fuck about cats,
niggas, your cat havin' been into the vet a million years.
Why you hot boxin' titties?
Stop hot boxin' the cats, bro.
Niggas, don't quit.
Niggas, you're nervous, bro.
Chill out, bro.
I'll see you on the other side
door to door though it will be door to door I'll see that bitch on the other side and I'm gonna stick my dick in there okay okay okay no we don't talk like that here
crash out door to door
last year last year last year when I was working here you get a
door to door I'm chilling baby I'm chilling I don't need a I'm chilling door to door nigga
knock knock it's me Q I got what you need
I don't know what's going on with this guy tonight
sick you got a door-to-door job too I didn't know you do the door-to-door I
just I thought that was a joke I didn't know it was real
I didn't know it was a job I thought it was a joke God bless America he get mad
why he so mad this is a job right
Shout to the commission man. You get very far commission
Okay, Elias is back. Let's look at me. That's cooking this up. Oh my god. He cooking this up. He like
Yo, simple you fuck boy
Say I mean
Same thing to y'all need to be giving us off off for no reason
Ladies get trolled and oh my god comes you how to drop his own people with child abuse
That's a crazy I made clumsy drop his own paperwork. It was a great panel
Hey, but you know, you know, you know, can you remember like Tommy James last night how he came on like very friendly and like cordial and reasonable
Anthony's like, oh, I hate that you just came on there to see skew skew
one-footy-third, right?
I'm not talking to you. I'm talking to you. I'm talking to you. I'm talking to you. I'm talking to you. I'm talking to you. I'm talking to you. I'm talking to you. I'm talking to you. I'm talking to you. I'm talking to you. I'm talking to you. I'm talking to you. I'm talking to you. I'm talking to you. I'm talking to you. I'm talking to you. I'm talking to you. I'm talking to you. I'm talking to you. I'm talking to you. I'm talking to you. I'm talking to you. I'm talking to you. I'm talking to you. I'm talking to you. I'm talking to you. I'm talking to you. I'm talking to you. I'm talking to you. I'm talking to you. I'm talking to you. I'm talking to you. I'm talking to you. I'm talking to you. I'm talking to you. I'm talking to you.
the grandpas of the community even though he's probably a year older than me. Oh great, it's good times.
Yeah, good times buddy.
That's a prairie page. That's not a prairie page. She doesn't look that old. Oh my god,
pack you up. I'm cooking a door. I'm cooking a door to door, man. Let's do this door to door, man.
Can we sell what you do at do what you do at door to door you wear a suit
Why do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you do you
You can go ahead and throw that shit out the window.
I will say the N word.
Hey listen, I hung out in Detroit.
They used to call me a nigger.
Oh my god, that should look dirty.
I
Just saw that she is faking me nobody chased her away. She's just a stuck-up bitch
I never said I don't like her.
My fat boy.
Okay guys.
That's a pain.
Edward, I'm going to go slip these on, okay?
And I'm going to dance.
Look he out of here. Look exactly get the fuck out of bounds nigga
Okay, yo, what's looking crazy kick that nigga out you bitch has no run queue to my docks nigga
Nobody gives a fuck about your fucking job nigga bum ass nigga
Oh, that's me. I have to be I have to be I have to be fair. And so, okay. Oh, that's a good time bugged out. Yo, actually, I can't get it off because he started saying
But I had to be even to kick him out because he's said it just 10 times too and it's like you know
I have to apply the rules fairly here. I'm trying to have a good night here. And it's like what happened
It's like why can't they behave their offending page?
You guys guys just take a breather and just think about you know, this is like I'm wearing a nice shirt tonight
I'm I'm well dressed. I don't like this like filthy language
I know I asked you to be like, you know, be a little bit nicer and like fuck. I mean it's like
Oh God, I mean, it's like why you want to just like case it I don't know
Sorry if I'm slow with the fucking trigger finger and stuff. It's like it's hard. It's not easy like applying all these
Okay, I like that. Okay. So here we go
I apologize page
My brain fucking it literally crashes out when everybody's yelling like that. I can't handle it
Okay, over stem to the maximum also like signal. Fuck you quick show on your dick online. You fucking bitch. Don't talk about me
Exactly
Q if I let you back you yeah, that was your like one warning is like next time
Just be able to do nothing.
You didn't do nothing.
Well, I'm just being.
Acceptable. OK.
So let's all calm down.
You didn't pick me.
OK.
He left himself.
I left because there was somebody being a fucking
Chimp Monkey Ape on the panel and I just don't need
to talk to Chimp Monkey Apes.
OK.
You from New York?
You from New York too?
No, I'm from Pittsburgh.
Oh.
All you from PA
I live in Cali though now. Oh, that's cool. That would be cool
And guys, I'm not going to put on the speedo even though the end rule was broken, but next time it's said, I'm going to go put it on.
You're going to go beat me for a punishment?
I'm going to put on the speedo as a punishment and dance for everybody.
I found it. It's just freshly watched. There's no stains or anything on it. It's perfect.
There better not be. You shouldn't even have mentioned that.
Well...
You know, they look clean as a whistle, I'll just say.
It is a, okay.
Wait, wait, I just want you guys to realize
how the panel is now, right?
How we're chilling, we're talking,
and then when certain other people join,
you know, things change, right?
Just, I just want you to notice that.
You know, just remember that.
Well, that's how it is.
That's how it is.
Draw myself.
Energy interference, it's just sometimes a cloud.
Yeah, but nobody's selling anything,
and not everybody wants to sit around
and constantly sit in a fucking drama pool.
Your bro, we gonna sell you next.
I'll just leave I'll sell you into sex trafficking
Yeah, that's my stuff. That's my stuff bro. That's my yeah, it'll be fucking red light yellow light green light and that
Yeah, he's a you know, he's a very insufferable person and a lot of people don't fucking like him just being honest
We're talking about the the fucking faggot from New York. That was just up here. Oh
I didn't know that that word was off limits. You say it all the time
Thank you so much. I appreciate it. I appreciate it. Okay. Thank you so much
Let's all have a fun night. I think we should I think we should all fucking I think we should all dog pile on prairie page
I'm just kidding. I'm just I'm gonna light an incense. Okay, I'm gonna light up this fucking Josephina pack
I like that. I like that idea.
Incense and then a Josephina pack. We have weed and we have, like...
Yeah! Yeah! Shout out to that Josephina pack.
Where's my... Do you have a lighter somewhere?
Shit. My lighter is kind of not working really well.
Pardon me for my ignorance, but uh, what is a Josephina pack?
Uh, you know, it's a very good herb.
Oh, it's, it's, it's kind of dark. It's pretty fat too.
Yeah, it's a really good weed strain yeah, so next time you're with your friends and you get you hit some really good we'd be like man
That's that Josephina right there
There we go
Might be a bit old school. I know weed which is a good thing
And I know good weed which is a better thing
Talk about marijuana or talk about he's smoking incense idiot
No, we're talking about smoking Josephina. We're doing both. We're doing both. There's there's weed in the air
There's incense smoking in the air
Everything's Josephine is in the air. Yeah, it's all good
Smoke I'm gonna go out from the cottage
Yeah, you don't need to know how to hit a golf ball woman.
Oh my gosh, oh my gosh.
I don't know how to hit a golf ball.
No you don't.
Fuck you. Yeah I do actually.
Why are you being mean to Paige tonight? Good thing I thought you had a crush.
Well, that's how he is
You know when he when he has a crush on a woman he starts to bully them and stalk them and harass them and
Well, you do have a charge for stalking and harassing so
How about this
Does that make me a horrible person Q?
Yeah, it makes do a terrible person garbage
You know what good times you got a lot of hate in your heart I
Actually don't actually love life. You got a lot of hate in your heart good times
I want
Prairie peace teach me how to play golf
Yeah, well the other night I wanted to show her feet we can't all give what we want
What you asked her sure feet are you what I
Know the other beard guys just as confused. You must be hearing things good times. I don't look a fuck you're on
No, I'm talking about the guy above me in the middle, he is confused, you just don't know.
It's confusing to me is that I've been some places and for some reason I have been confused
with you.
I bet you I know some of them places you've been to, I bet you they're circular.
What is the connection between me and this gentleman? I
Don't know you both look like fucking gay wannabe pirates
That's maybe that's
If you guys were to start a band together
I'll start a band with all of you and it'll be the case if you and if you and untrackable you should start a band
You should you could call it tears for bearded queers
What did you just say?
Because now I think you're way cooler than you
It's not a competition it's not a competition no it is no way well for you guys maybe but
I ain't here to be better than anybody and never fight over me so funny what's so funny
I don't know what's funny.
Hey, good time.
So how was your time on the, how was your day today?
Tell me about your day.
It was amazing.
I got $50 from my father.
I told him I'd pay him back tomorrow.
Hey.
I
Trolled the hell out of him and my parents and I asked him if I could borrow some money
I said you got $20. He said no, I don't got $20. I said you get $10. He said no, I don't get $10
I said you got $5. He said no, I don't got $5. He said I got $50
Are you gonna pay my ass back? And I said yes, I'll pay your ass back tomorrow. That sounds cool, you know.
Well, Key left because his father died from a heroin overdose.
He already said it himself. I didn't know.
Put salt in it. Do you want to put salt in a wound, especially that kind?
That's not salt in a wound.
Larry talked about my grandmother being tortured before.
Okay, I mean, I know it's terrible, but someone was saying stuff about you today two good times and you didn't like it, you know, and just like, you know, have some empathy, you know?
I have no empathy for nobody that has empathy for me.
Well, you know.
I think like there's some good people on the panel right now that are empathetic like I think like
Intractable me and Paige are our empath
Yeah, so it's obvious yes, and you know so it's like you know you're around you're around people that are our hearts hurt when we hear that kind of thing and
so
I'm not, I'm not a fence rider, so somebody's talk shit to me, fucking I'll remember forever.
You're not even on the phone right now, it looks like you put that up.
Very appreciate how I married you and moved to Canada.
You won't like Canada, or me probably, if you got it to know.
Why, why would I like Canada? I basically almost live in it, I live in fucking Michigan.
It's just a joke you might you might love Canada. I don't know you might love it
Yeah, I might obviously I would be able to carry handguns
Honestly, where I live personally Alberta isn't much different from Montana
Alcohol is very expensive in Canada. It is fucking outrageous. It'd be expensive and trackable your cracks
I don't want to live in Canada anymore
I just talked to a Canadian, like...
You know before I came up here
And he said a six-pack cost him 17 dollars
Yeah, I paid 12 I paid 12 dollars for a pack and I
Retarded I paid
$22 for a 24 pack so it's like the more you
I'm gonna get a six pack of George Killians, then it'll cost me like eight bucks or something.
So let me put this example, I guess. So a 24 pack of like say Budweiser here where I live in Alberta
is fucking like well over 50 bucks, 55 bucks.
No, fuck that fuck that
And that's what I that's what I was saying
Homeboy was drinking a six pack of of bush light and it cost him 17 dollars
Yeah, same thing. It's the same same price
But I like to like the space and it is like 22 bucks for 15 of them
Yeah, I don't drink special beer, but
Your your country's monsters is filled with monsters, so
In order for me to live there with you, I'm gonna have to be the guy that does the golf course, grooming, like, um...
Bill Murray out a catty shot, right? Then I'll kill all the goddamn fucking
Am I giving you anxiety by saying that I mean
I can take care of the golf course
Well, if they're hiring, I'll put a good reference for you.
Okay.
Okay, okay.
You can be like, you can work at the end of the session as well.
Hey, listen everybody like honestly, there's when it comes to a groundskeeper at the golf course either like we are subject
I have to do it or fucking cuz no one shows up for their shift
So I'm out there doing it. I love cutting grass. There's something so serene about it. It's like swimming. Like there's just a peaceful
It's not serene
You're committing murder you're burning God
Not not really
I'm giving a haircut. I've given God a haircut. Okay. I'm giving it a trim
We'll off the end
Okay, okay. Yeah
Yeah, I love cutting grass and I love playing golf
Fuck yeah high five
That's my shit. I love it. I'm just trying to hit on my future wife
That was so loud. I'm sorry
I'm good to go brother
What why you have her we make a key I make key chains out of these
What are those
They're both casings like shells. I make fucking key chains out of you. You want to see gum bullets?
I can show you them right now
Yeah, I shoot guns. Yeah. Well, how do you think I got these?
Obviously, well, I know I know
Kenanians are not allowed to possess
fucking
Firearms
Why yeah, I am yeah, we are have no you're not. No, you're not. I know the laws in Canada
All right, whatever helps you sleep at night good times, but I have we are
You're not allowed to own
Handguns you're not allowed to handgun
I don't want to fuck your stream up or else. I show you something
handguns absolutely you need a special what while she's showing bullets on her stream you dumbass
it's an empty keychain shell like it's not even it's a craft it's so it what type of shell is it
it's like a cat show let's see if you know it's a it's a what no i think what kind of show is it
it's a shell i'm sorry
Listen, yes when it comes to handguns. Absolutely. You have to have a special like you have to have a special
Yeah, you have to special what?
Yeah, special what?
Special what?
You need for anything. What is this? I'm testing your knowledge. What is this? I can't fucking see it
That's 22 shells. Is it not?
It's a not it's a nine millimeter you fucking idiot
it looks tiny it looks skinny obviously I didn't know like I mean okay one
second let me prove to you what I mean okay just a sec you want you want to see
my 38 no please don't show guys on my show well she's baiting you and get me
doing this you fucking moron control yourself I will never control myself
Don't bring out of the way all the guns I'll buy your legal
If you bring your gun, I'll bring out. I I I pass
FBI background checks. This feels my biggest power
Where's my loader at?
That's right here
You know controlling yourself is part of being part of a community. Yeah, you know what controlling yourself is saying suck my dick
That's a dangerous thing to say on a gay person's joke
Sorry, I'm low on my nine millimeter. Okay. You're out of here. You're out of here. I don't want to see you load again on my show
Oh my gosh.
Oh my God.
I just have it.
SIG is trying to come up again and again and again.
OK.
You're rude.
I'm going to give you one more chance at SIG.
If you do anything, the speed is coming out, OK?
And I'm going to dedicate a dance to you.
OK.
You're on the air, SIG.
Don't look at me. Yes. Yeah, you're on the air
I heard you the first time Howard
Hey now hey now
Rest in peace you guys you guys heard that the what's the guy's name the midget black guy
From the wack, I heard he passed some buck beel juice.
Passed away, like recently or what?
I heard, I'm serious, yeah, I heard he passed some beel juice.
Let me look it up, hold on.
That's crazy news.
Rest in peace to that dude.
Yeah, he always would say, it would say, how do you spell your name?
And he's a good sport. He's a good sport.
He said, how do you spell red?
And he'd say L-S-T-R because his name is Lester.
And that's like the only thing he knew how to spell,
but he couldn't even spell his first name right.
But it's OK.
Let me see.
Beatles News.
Oh, from the Howard Stern Show.
Yeah, it says, oh, no, it says, it looks like he's dead.
Let me see.
Look at the news. That's what I heard. I'm serious. That's what I heard. I saw something
What was it in April?
I heard this a while ago
Seven years old
He's 70 what seven years old and look at that smile
57 and God bless him
Well, I'm glad to hear that he's still kicking in I'm not joking you see me laughing. I'm not joking
That's what I heard. I heard that this guy passed
So yeah, everyone used to do
Yo, can you mute your mic if you're not talking really bad
Appreciate it love. Thank you
What does that
of
the
It wasn't George Floyd like you think it was clumsy. It's actually it's actually water
This is actually water. I fake all of my shots. This is actually water. I don't drink alcohol
Yeah, I don't I don't believe you
Because who chases water
And maybe I don't like the taste of water
Maybe water is fucking boring. Is water have a taste?
Water is much tasteless. It's like, you know, isn't it?
That's what you ever go to you ever go to like, I mean, maybe you're in San Francisco
Wherever the fuck you're at psyche, but like you ever go to like
Small towns or water tastes like fucking pond water
You know a beyond water from the glaciers that has like a nice like
almost like a silky taste to it like if you ever taste it has like a look a little like a
Avian Avion. Yeah, they'd be on from that French Alps. No, dude. Do you mean you mean Fiji?
Are you talking about Fiji? Fiji is the one that they put silica. Fiji water is from like a filtered water.
Isn't it a Fiji filtered tap water? Oh, that's just the saunee or something.
the sonny is the the sonny is literally it's crazy it's owned by the coca-cola
company yeah and what they do is that they resell you bottled tap water yeah
it's fucking tap water yeah sonny it's literally what it is and cap water does
have a taste it tastes like metal from like the pipes you know right depends on
That's how bottled water works is the
bottling plants because
You know, you talk about Pepsi you talk about Coke you talk about anybody that
Bottles beverages, right?
Everything starts with water right because so what they do is they
They create these processing plants
That clean water
So they subsidize
For tax relief, you know, don't call me blood. I'm a Crip don't call me blood
Gangs and that's we're in the quacker game. I didn't call you anything
But what they do interrupt you I was just referring to comments
Yeah. Yeah. Okay. You you talk to comments.
This is awkward. I'm sorry. Now I'm just kidding. This is awkward. And I'm uncomfortable. There's a
great key in it. There's a great key in here. I'm comfortable and I like it. One guy keeps saying
awkward for like everything and everyone's like stop saying awkward, stop saying awkward.
And then he like explodes and then he leaves and the guy's like awkward.
I love except I'm not the one that's leaving
Well post a link for that old lady that wants to join come on letter on what's your name?
I mean, I think I'm not on my my whole month page. Oh
Come on with a G. Hey, yeah, what's the letter? No, they're pages with a G
Yeah, I don't know how the fuck you spell it. Okay, here we go
There we go. There's a link again. I'm gonna pin the link actually. I'm just gonna be a second. I'll pin the link so I don't have
It's a great idea. Yeah, I'm gonna pin the link
And let's go
I'm about to do it. There we go. It is now pin
Cheers child. We're taking fucking water shots. This is water
I do not advocate for the consumption of alcohol.
This is alcohol.
I mean, not this.
Alcohol is poisonous.
I do not advocate.
Well, you know, and you know what they call water.
You know what they call drinking water.
You know what they call water in Russia?
Vodka.
I think that's I heard that Russia is an insanely difficult language Russia. Russian isn't
I know that coke dealer cuz I have my best friend is they have like
Alphabet or something like that. I know the alphabet has like backwards ours and stuff. I mean it gets confusing
But yeah, I mean it's hard. It's probably but you know, it's even the hardest language
I took Japanese classes when I was like in suit. They had a Japanese class on a Saturday
and it's like that shit is like it's like you're like fucking drawing like
like fucking like 10 lines for like one letter into like the special shape I was like this is
too confusing I can't even figure out how to how to draw it less but it's just pronounced it in
a read I mean it's like the shout out to the Japanese that's and Chinese is just as hard you
know it's like um but you know it's just yes sign language is so much easier because you don't have
It's like charades. Yeah, it is similar to straights. You know what this means?
Remember I remember learning American sign language like in elementary school. They taught us like the basics
And and they just put they just gave us earplugs. I remember Howard light earplugs
And
Honestly, I couldn't remember
I love all you guys. What does this mean? I don't know. What is this being right here?
Yeah, I mean there's a movie called the day without Mexicans and there were no you know that movie that movie is great
Only Mexicans know that movie shout out to you that movie is hilarious. Yeah
Only beiners know that movie to you guys all right you guys are cultured
I did my look it wasn't the best movie ever, but it was fucking funny. All right
It's funny premise like there's no premise is pretty funny. Yeah, the lawns are all overgrown. No houses are built
Like there's none of no dishes are washed. I mean, it's great. There's no Mexican food, which is like the best food
I love Mexican food. It's awesome. I mean it basically consists of flour tortillas corn tortillas beans and
rice and and cheese right but it's like they can make so many things and hot sauce too
but you know i am you know chile in the country of chile hot food is not very popular but in
mexico it's very popular kind of interesting well i'll tell you that uh that that day without
Because poor is poor no matter what you are
So when they say oh
Who who's gonna wash my laundry who's gonna take care of my kids like
Why don't you take care of your motherfucking kids? Okay, you're about to be kicked off the show
I apologize. I apologize the problem with what you're saying is that it makes a lot of sense at face value
At face value what you're saying makes perfect sense
Well, when you look at reality, it doesn't really add up
Yeah, do you know like who works at the slaughterhouses?
By the way is like usually illegal immigrants and because nobody really American would once to once to work at a slaughterhouse
Like most know what it is what it is these illegal workers they're propping up the economy
These businesses would not be as profitable as they would be if they had to hire americans
For a minimum wage exactly they wouldn't be making as much money they wouldn't be
Contributing to the s&p 500 as much
Literally that is the backbone
That is the backbone all these companies would collapse their shares would collapse if they had to pay Americans a living wage
This is the system that you guys wanted well
That's also the system that benefits you right system benefits you right and that's what the country is kind of built
Remember the country is almost built on slavery because it's like that was like
Very like free labor and that's like, you know, but that's how the country was able to prosper and some and you know grow at first
you know, which is like the hardest thing to do for a country and
You know, so but it's unfortunate, you know, it's like of course the horrible horrible thing, right, but
You know, like it's just interesting to think where we would be without some of these dark dark times in history, you know
Well, or where would we do that without you know, Tyre you kind of what outsourcing even outsourcing
You know, there's you know, I guess you know, Nike which is like sells the sneakers for like a hundred fifty dollars a pair
They actually like build their sneakers and sweatshops with under horrible conditions and stuff like that, right?
Ever see Michael. They have child slavery in their factories. I know it's terrible
And you have why ends paying $300 retail
And then and then those same why ends will complain about the police injustice
See number it's a good movie. I haven't heard of that means without a name
You know Charles Manson, on those verses we get it says no name, no name Manson or it says no name, maybe Jones or something like that, but actually he had no name, like his parents didn't even give him a name, did you ever hear about that?
So maybe there's reasons people are the way they are, like maybe they had fucked up lives, childhood trauma, all kinds of things that we don't think about when we like to judge people so harshly for why they do bad things.
Everybody has a reason for why they are the way they are.
Right, but I'm saying the part that differentiates us from the animals
The part that differentiates us from the animals that we can is that we can be conscious
Yes, and choose to behave differently
Otherwise, you're just a fucking animal. That's the smartest thing that I have heard sick say I think I think the smartest
I say smart every other fucking thing I say that comes out
Yeah, I also like sale out of dumb shit, right
Okay, so you guys say reasons I say excuses does that make sense
No, because well, I say like, you know we can choose
the higher path, we can choose to improve ourselves.
We can choose to break cycles, ancestral cycles.
Sometimes there's ancestral cycles
that keep repeating over and over
because there's no consciousness put into it.
But human beings, that's we do above the animals,
we can make choices and we can make better choices.
And sometimes it takes a long time,
but it's like still, as long as we're,
Bearing up instead of bearing down. I think that's the important thing
That's why I believe no one's really beyond redemption if they are actually
Come to a point where they're like I want to change for the better. I want to make a better decision
I want to do better. I want to break these cycles. Okay?
That's what I was taught eliminate excuses
Right, I mean we just maybe said it a different way. I wasn't arguing with you
I was just like, you know, we have very different vernacular a little bit or you know, there's differences in our
Everyone's different. Everyone's we're as human beings. We're pretty much different, but we're also the same in some ways, right?
It's all very different, but it's also very much the same right there you go. There you go. That's my point, right?
So, oh, we have another guess. Okay. Good times. Are you you're not gonna bring out gun or anything?
Please okay
Where's that old white lady? I haven't seen page. Maybe you scared
What's up?
No, you're part of kitty good. Well good. I don't want to be part of that game
You know, I'd rather you know, you know, you know what I realize you know what I realize you motherfucker people like beta
People like beta they want a guy. That's docile
They want a guy. That's docile like like good times
They want a guy. That's docile like thing that is
That's what they want
I'm not and then they're like wondering why they aren't married
It's so bizarre. They literally it's they look for a guy. That's a docile and then crush him
That's what they want
That's bizarre. What wouldn't you say crush what was supposed to be?
I'm I'm gonna try to cook some food or something. I didn't think I have a jar of cottage cheese over there.
Okay, you're all wet. It was raining outside.
Is that the control aspect of things?
Like everybody wants to be in control, but nobody's willing to be a team? Like equals and whatnot?
There's no such thing as a team
There there's only dominance and submission. Are you fucking retarded?
Well, sometimes
Sometimes you just need to play your position
We can all be quarter play your position small
Play your position small soldier, that's what he told you pussy
Hey
It doesn't have to be that way. No, it's that that's that's how it works with a lot of
things
I'll be right back guys. I'll be right back. Okay guys gonna trust you be right back guys pull my dick out right now
No, and if you talk like that again, you're not you can't well. I'm gonna stand up fuck this
Good times
Okay, I was joking. Okay. Okay. Okay. I just want to make sure
I'll be right back guys untrackable. Can you cue babysit for me? I'm gonna watch a movie fuck this
I'm gonna watch Michael Douglas falling down screw this shit
Enjoy your evening
That's the gayest fucking movie you could possibly watch
What do you think
Give us a breakdown.
Is that Georgie hitting you hard?
That's the fentanyl.
See that
The real deal right there phantos
Hello, hostile high boring. How are you? I'm doing good. How are you? I'm sorry. Good. I
I recognize you've been on the show, right? I have a it's a long time. I want to say months
Maybe six months seven months. Were you like talking a lot about like religion and stuff?
Probably occultism magic. Yeah, the little theology philosophy stuff like that
This is one of the theme. Okay. Well, you're wrong with you're on with untrackable. You're on with dig and talk you should go ahead
No, I don't have any shit to talk. I came in. You're gay Howard Stern. I
Came in late and they were about to he was on with eugenio derbes
Well, it's good to see you
It's tough around here right now.
What's wrong?
What's tough?
You know, attitudes, personalities.
I'll be right back.
Signal game, thanks, thanks, thanks, please.
This is the signal game.
Cells.
This is the sig cells.
the city of all the sick cells
, I'm trying to take the sick pill and got it on the
sick cells deployed worldwide don't share
so what's on your mind has that
a lot man I uh... I like to think about reality
deep truths
existence
capital capital E capital R
capital T
the truth, right? That's what I'm concerned with.
Well, when it comes to the truth, what's your most recent witness?
Yeah, so most recent, well, I've been said in my ways for some time, so I probably can't recall the most recent.
I'd probably say
That and this is a philosophical this guy this goes into the realm of philosophy that there is no such thing as creation
Things like that
That there's only existence there's no such thing as non-existence
Okay, okay, you resonate with that or is that a little too far-fetched well what you kind of sound retarded right now
What brought you to that thought? What did you see? What did you hear? What did you
Feel yeah, I think it's I think it's intuitional right? It's something that you don't think about
You know normally because it's a very deep
Concept it's it's underneath our daily lives the the typical habits that we have as human beings
So when it's brought to your attention, I think it clicks
When you start to think about the word nothing and what nothing means
You realize that that that can't be a thing. There's no such thing as nothing, right?
Okay
So that's probably the most recent thing that I've stumbled across and that was I don't know probably a couple years ago
So
You know
Did somebody call you nothing, or did you feel like nothing?
And you'd be like, how, hey, how could I be nothing?
Like, even if I failed, I'm still not nothing.
I get to try again.
I'm still here, right?
Oh, that's a good way to look at it.
That wasn't my instance.
But yeah, it's another analogy that you can use.
And I like that one.
Yeah.
Mine was just reading, trying to find out
what religion means, what theology means,
I ended up coming across it. Yeah, through reading.
I apologize, but I appreciate reading and hearing others' accounts of things,
but witness is like, you went through it.
That that too, right? It's not just reading. It's reading weight against the experience, right?
And we have experiences and sometimes we don't know what's going on
Until it's brought to our attention and it clicks, you know, sometimes it takes hearing somebody mentioned something
An interpretation of a former experience usually the things we have
Realizations about are in retrospect. It's things that happened in the past that we didn't understand. So the experience is there
It's just it took a little it's in combination with reading
It's like a symbiotic process
Yeah, I agree because
it's a comparison of
What you actually witnessed yeah
Versus the many different explanations that don't hurry page of fans in my chat
I
That can explain
Oof drinking that clear cheers to you
Take a shot take a shot
Take a shot
Oh
Like I mean sorry say are you drinking ever clear?
I'll look like vodka vodka. Okay. No, ma'am. No, ma'am. This is water
No, sir, those are lies. I've never seen somebody look that way after drinking water
No, have you ever drank?
In high school as cultured girls would pitch on like a fucking a Mickey even I've ever clear and like six of us would drink that and
We would be blackout drunk. Oh, yeah. Yeah, that and
Yeah, I'm sorry. No, it's okay. I was just saying it's like drinking paint like it's like drinking paint thinner gasoline logically
It's not good for you. It's bad. Yeah, it's actually it's actually very effective at cleaning things. No, I know it is
Extracting it's like it's just it's extremely abrasive like and I have drank it. Yes
Yeah, it's crazy, but I've also used it for cleaning for cleaning resin off of things
like literally it's like a
Extremely, I mean it's almost 100% it's really strong. Yeah, it's really fucking like it's insane to drink it
I'm using it to clean shit and like get the chemicals out of like
Shit like literally like it's
It's crazy
Purpose was not for consumption. It was actually for that for cleansing of certain things like bacterial wounds
Like it's an it's an out high content alcohol. So it definitely has properties of cleansing for sure
If you're drinking in a large volume, it's definitely not great for you at all
Like you're gonna get alcohol poisoning, right? But not at all. Yeah, it's original purpose
And I found this out through practicing alchemy was used as a stringent. So like you can draw
that you can draw spirits out of. What do you mean alchemy?
Alchemy like, you know, like the science of like balancing like fucking chemical balance or fucking alchemy is anything of balance that you're taking one thing to another and you're you're
Yeah, the transmutation alchemy. I thought alchemy was turning garbage into gold.
That can be that can be alchemy if you try to be big transmuting something and use alchemy as well. You can do that.
Yeah, yeah, it's like the transmutation of stuff. Yeah, no matter what that
processes. It could be fermentation, distillation,
circulation. Yeah, but that's the one of the main parts is that that extraction that you're talking about and Everclear is recommended for sure.
But the Cardi 151 was another fan favorite, right? When I was in, you know, right out of high school got fake ID's in the bar.
Yes, that 151 is very very strong and blackout inducing for sure.
I'm actually allergic to Bacardi white rum like any kind of white rum. I don't know why I can drink spiced rum
I can drink amber rum dark rum, but I can't drink a certain vodka
I think it's what it's made from like what the for what the what they used to ferment your in so potato vodka or corn
Yeah, it's corn
Oh, sorry. I thought we were talking about Everclear. I don't know what they do Bacardi out of well
Just bought I mean anything so it depends for me like my allergies to certain alcohols depend on what they're made from
Yep. Yeah
Everclear, I think it's corn. It is. Yeah, same with
Tequila's not that's a good like a fucking cactus flower guava
Yeah
So that what should be it, then I think it's a keyless good
Yeah, that's some good stuff. Yeah, I don't need a chaser for that. I don't it's got to be silver though
the gold and
Rosado
I'll pass on those you give me a good silver man. There's nothing like that
Yeah, no chaser is crazy. I can't do that. I don't need chaser for things certain things. No chaser
Lime, no, nothing nothing just nothing for shots. I just know
Salt and lime is a delicacy
Yeah, maybe I need to experience it with like I guess high quality
Tequila maybe in the in the environment authentic environment if that makes sense like if I go to Mexico, maybe it'd be different
I've never I just go to like, you know blue collar bars here. So it's like just do the shot. There's like that's it
I just do it
Yeah, I don't I don't do I have to it's anymore
But if like somebody says a shot shots all around
No, I say put it in a low ball with an ice cube and then I'll stir it for about 10 minutes
and then I'll sip it
Well, that's a
newspaper and you go
All the time sit by your fire. Like that's the gentleman's
No, listen when you said ice cube it reminded me of something have any of you here had absinthe before yeah
I have properly actually when you light it on fire the sugar cube and drop it into the thing
Yeah, and you drop the water into the drops the loosing. Yeah
Yeah, that's a that's a method, but you got to lose shit. You got to do the drops first. Yeah
Yeah, I think hallucinate which kind of was like well because you see it on movies
It's not the same kind of thing and actually it's derived from warm wood which actually was a hallucinogen just because of the
Anyways, it's for any star the any star is better than the wormwood. There's different things you can use for it
But yeah, yeah knee star man. That's some good
Shit and you get this giant
There's this wine bar here locally that we have and they drop a giant ice cube in a cup
So that will lose shit. It doesn't disturb the absence. It hits the block. It hits that block of ice
That's why we have it shaped for even other fancy drinks like old fashions and such, right? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
That drip though, it's it's really cool when you watch it if you guys never have seen this
Look it up later when you got whenever you have time
You watch the absinthe is clear at first. It's like a clear green
And then once you lose it enough, uh lose it. Sorry
You'll add a drop. It's still clear. You add another drop still clear after about five six seven drops
It turns into a cloud. It looks like milk
So like this like a milky green. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
What is that my idea behind it is I'm trying to have a good time
Not get fucked up and getting trouble. You know I'm saying yeah
But there's also like there's drinking and there's like there's a certain class about it
You know what I mean?
It's kind of like a vibe if you will if that makes more sense than that like you go into something if I'm gonna go
Have an old-fashioned. I'm in a certain setting. I'm with certain people
You know, I mean, it's like it's a place of time for certain things like at home
I drink beer or I make
say if i have like a mixed drink night for just for fun like paralyzer thursday or something stupid
like that right but for the most part just beer but going out like i mean just the environment
will kind of bring out what i'm willing to drink as well because i know what i'd like when i drink that too
So it's maybe a vibe like mushrooms. It's like mushrooms mushrooms mushrooms is a vibe
It's an energetic high, right? So like you're very energy sensitive
You're very very vulnerable and open and so for that
It's like you have to have like the right people and the right environment and like you kind of have to plan for that
But the spontaneous times are fun, too. Don't get me wrong, but normally it's like why don't want bad vibes
I don't want bad things. I don't want bad people there because it'll fuck with my vibe
It'll fuck with my high. That's just something I learned, you know
And also, mushroom tea doesn't fuck with me in a negative sense, like eating them does.
So maybe if that's something that you have a problem with, you should try.
That's not good advice. What the fuck am I doing?
Blacker Rage said, it doesn't matter what you do to the absent or how expensive it is, it still tastes like a wormwood's licorice asshole.
It does, it totally does.
No, it tastes so good.
It's so good.
But to each their own, not everybody likes the taste of black licorice, but some people, that's their favorite candy, right?
Yeah, yeah, it does kind of taste like black licorice.
That's that any star taste.
Yeah, it's like fuzzy or prickly.
Yeah, it's like eating a pineapple with that. It's kind of same
Yeah, silly feeling or like no like okay. This is not the same taste, but the same sensation like horseradish
Yes, yeah like horseradish how it like stings your tongue or something
Mm-hmm. It's actually like even like wasabi or like even yeah
Yes, we're talking about alcohol the um, what do you call it rice wine like?
Socky it is it like a head drunk more than it is like a body like other the rest of your body almost feels unaffected
And it's not like it's all about the mind with that one in the head. It feels heavy. You know, it's different for everything
Yeah
Another comment Felipe says all alcohol tastes like shit. I have to disagree. I have to disagree like it's an acquired taste
I understand that but like a good bourbon or a good page
What?
What
Fig what do you want for me?
How many black guys have you fucked based?
How many black guys have you slept with sick?
A thousand good round of applause round of applause
He's fucked 5000 black guys his level is 5000
So he's got a drink so it's hard liquor to forget about the terrible memories
He's been reamed bad
You have to ask weird shit when people are having a good conversation you just have to do it. That's what my chat is asking
Well, you know the sleeping with black guys things thing. It's not the problem is how much you paid them
That's good. That's good. It is what it is child
So yeah, Prairie you sound like she actually wanted a high answer
They actually wanted you to say a high number gross
Did you just say you wanted a high end a high answer they wanted a high number
Yeah, they were they're actually hoping for a high number
It's not creepy at all. It's not weird at all. Right? Oh
I swear to God that was that was creepy for sure, but uh
The bong rip it already looks cloudy, did you rip it and hold it are you holding the carb?
think sig is unhinged right now yeah it's all that um it's all that water
he's been drinking yeah the water in the in the the herb
I don't blame the herb blame the water and whatever sugar drink he's chasing
fentanyl
The he's he's he's got that high fructose corn syrup
Yeah, taking bong rims of Fint will do it for sure
Yeah, good luck with that shit
But yeah back to the witness thing right so for me
It was the realization
This is how the witness of it
occurred right so
Coming across the specific
Philosopher was Parmenides is how I came across this but when I sit there and thought about it
You you either have you have two options, right you have something and you have nothing
There's not a middle ground here. This is like a true fork in the road problem
There's nothing and there's something okay
You and I are here. There are a bunch of forms or a bunch of categories. We know that there is something
Right, so how does this nothing thing come into play?
Parminity says if there is something
You cannot get something from nothing
That's profound think about that well for instance
You you know, you you have let's just say first comes to witness something you experienced it
And then and then comes the question
What was that
You know and then you start to enter water and then you start to sink seek
other's witnesses to answer the question of what was that and who
You know put in work to try to answer that question
Yeah, it's like true science it first requires an observation of some natural phenomena. No, I get that right
But what I'm saying is is sometimes we observe things we witness things and
We're not
Truly seeing it right. It's it's so deep
It's right before our eyes is like the National Geographic. Oh, this is for sure for sure
minus the animal
Minus the animal sex stuff. What microphone do you have?
What microphone do I have?
What microphone do you know? Oh, why would you ask that question?
manufacturer model
I'm an I'm AI. This is I'm actually I'm generated what my mic from you have
why are you asking what microphone do I have that's weird do you like it model
manufacturer no I'm asking a question okay I'm gonna tell you whether I think
it's good or bad it's just a question yeah yeah yeah so it says signal
Ball but this is the serial number b o n g r i p f e n t
Vod a a that's the best joke. That's the best
They got the sure sm7b. Yeah, man. It's the it's the share sm7. It's the it's the road
Pardcaster pro. It's not that one. It's the share sm7. It's the
Audio Technica
AT 2020 no bro, it's a bluebird. Yeah, I mean, yeah
There we go. You we could go completely to the floor and say it's a blue yeti
Ray
Sounds good could also say it's cans attached together with strings
It is it honestly is like I'm sitting here as I speak I have to pluck on this string
To transmit the vibrations of my voice through it like I'm doing this manually with my finger. It's fucking wild
You should see my setup
Yeah, it's crazy
100% AI
What interface do you use?
It's a MIDI controller
Yeah, I got a MIDI controller and I'm literally pressing on a keyboard and I have words programed
What's the interface from your microphone to how?
Right now when I press the A, you know, I'm in and I press A
When you press the AI button?
I press, I press, I go AD
EC and those are programmed words, right? I have all these words that I'm saying right now that programmed on a keyboard
I'm just playing keys right now
It's it's wild my setup is wild. It's far-fetched. What's what's your audio interface from your mic XLR?
Right, this is yeah, so it's not an XLR. It's a quarter. It's out to yeah, or didn't to what?
Yeah, like I said, it's a MIDI controller. I'm using an oxygen 49
I'm using a keyboard right now
I wouldn't be laughing. I look like Mozart right now
I was just saying this completely bold-faced the user right the user of this is not even speaking
He's playing keys right now, and he looks like
Johann Sebastian Bach
It's crazy
What do you mean one single star?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, it's good he broke character. You got him
And we got him. Yeah, the keys only have 40 is only 48 keys on this motherfucker. It's crazy, dude
You should see how
I'm sweating right now very brave posted thumbs up
You know, thank you. Why don't you let her on? I think that's a I think that's a middle finger because you did something weird
Is that a no finger?
Why didn't you ask me how many my guy little finger? Why didn't you ask how many?
That's a thumbs up. That's actually a thumbs up
It's not I think you're dizzy. It's a thumbs up
Okay, real question looking right at it a real question
It's thumbs up. Why didn't you ask me how many black guys I had sex with? Why don't I get the same proof?
Cuz I already know the answer
What's the answer bub? Oh?
We know that is a middle finger
Why is she mad? Why is she mad? What the fuck?
You're really a zero. Why is she mad? What the fuck?
You're mad, bro. I'm not mad
Well, you're easy to shout out to her your chat is you can see that my eyes are smiling
Bro, you don't even look second anymore. You look yeah, I was gonna say he went from Mexican to Mongolian in a heartbeat
That was crazy
multiracial
I can't, he went from like a mariachi to throat singing, that was wild, um, so yeah, back to
us.
Sorry.
Go ahead.
No, no, no, no.
I was about to say something very rude, so you go ahead.
No, say it, say it.
I was going to say that's the chink in his armor.
Oh the chink in the armor. That's good. That's good. It's not my it came from a sitcom, but
So it says that I'm a chain
Prairie says I just wanted back. Did she get kicked off the panel?
That's what I'm saying
Well psyches probably that's what I'm saying how did she get on when psyche was off shout out to prairie pager, right?
Listen, I don't care how many black guys you've had sex with. All right, it's okay. I think you're cool
All right, it doesn't matter. I don't care how many black guys you've been with. All right
You're cool, right?
Chill out
Don't let these guys fucking make you spaz out
psyche is fucking asleep probably
Shout out to you next time I see you
Hey, let's take a shot take a shot. Yeah, well, probably not be here because psyche meth out
He took too many facts on the pills
What why'd you get this? Why'd you get the small bottle? Is that the economy?
Somebody got me this somebody got me this and they said get a 750 and I did so the 750
I didn't run prairie page off. She's literally waiting backstage and she says she's not mad
Yeah, that's she wants to join on
You're sounding weird right now
No
It's the AI thing. It's the if I could use a different filter voice filter. I would
Yeah, I just my the my programmer in the large language model I use I we haven't got one yet. So
No, we'll work on it. We'll figure it out
So as my mic crispy is that why you're asking
May give you it. I may give you the model if you if you use it, but it's crispy
Clumsy, I did not run her off. She's literally typing in the private chat backstage waiting to join
And she says she's not but mad
She's not mad, dude
What was your origin?
Psyche passed out Psyche passed out or whatever the fuck. He's not letting her back down
For whatever reason he's not letting her back on go on
Go on
You telling me to go? Yeah, dude. You were fucking talking. Did you were saying something?
Well, I asked you a question. It was weight. I'm waiting on you. I forgot. What was your question? Excuse me. Yeah
Yeah, so is the
Mike crispy is that why you're asking for the model or what's going on?
I'm just asking because it is more
Crispy is more crispy than the usual
I'm not asking because it is particularly exceptional
Better
Than the average. That's my question
Yeah, yeah, yeah, the setup is actually so basic that if I admitted it it you'd probably laugh at me
I mean
You can make things more complicated than they have to be it doesn't necessarily mean you get a better end result
Yeah, no, there's a
This is simply a plug-in bro. This is a USB port mic
That's it. The thing is usually people go through XLR and interfaces all that for more granular control and
Just to dial everything down, but you can still like
Kind of dial it down with all that you can get a USB whatever
It is possible
Yeah
Yeah, I think just like as a like a nerd. I think it's cool like the XLR stuff and whatever
Analog stuff. I think that's cool
for sure it is it is my dad was a
He mixed music as a side gig
he was a musician and I
Grew up learning about that stuff, but
Yeah, I actually do have some stuff here. I have equipment here
I'm just not using it. This is literally plug-and-play you plug it into your computer your laptop whatever you have
It's just a USP port to a mic. No interface. Everything is automated. It's it's built into the mic
Yeah, I know that's not the answer you wanted, but uh is for as fake and gay that as that is
I mean I wanted an answer. Yeah
I'm not saying like oh, I wanted you to have a fucking whatever the fuck I
Don't know the most expensive fucking thing. Yeah
But yeah, okay, that's cool
That makes sense in some instances
Or you can believe the cool story that I made up and like the AI thing that that's cool, too
I think it's either or it could be many things
It's like a flip of a coin also be that it's literally an entire AI thing and there was no microphone used
At all. It's just been AI dad extrapolated
Used to generate this voice. Yes. Yep
Right, you could also be using a whatever fucking $25,000 set up
It's $25,000 it's $25,000 worth of crispy is that what you're saying? Yeah
Yeah, baby, I'll take it. I'll take you're very economic
You sound like it
No, but you make best with what you have and you have this very very crisp as
Crisp really as you can get
Really for a feasible amount. I mean you can throw millions and millions more and it's like
That's not you know that you get past diminishing returns. Yeah, no, there's soundproof glass in here
I got a it's literally it's it's eight by eleven this room that I'm in I'm eggshell
Yeah, no, it's it's it's official man. It's like a whole podcast set up
I just don't like to do the podcast thing right? That's why I get on panels and I just don't show myself
Yes
Some say it's a waste of money, you know, I just was like fuck it. I just want to be an audio guy
the
Uh
There's a guy in the chat that said a hostile hypermorian are you an alchemist?
Yeah, I did alchemy for a long time. I'm I'm still do ceremonial magic. It's just highly
Satanist
No, I'm not a Satanist, but if you want to get up on the panel, I mean you want to talk about some stuff
That that's all I'll say I mean
If you have any questions put them in chat and then
Or if you just want to state something you don't even have to have a question
But yeah, I've been a ceremonial magician for almost two decades. I've been a part of
several different orders
Free masonry theosophy anthroposophy the golden dawn what about the what about the order of the black Hebrew?
Israelites
Yeah, no, yeah
Yaakub man praise be his name. Well, yeah, yeah for sure
we lose in my man here
No, no, no, I'm here. Oh
psyche's back. I think
He commented he said who big head scientist
Hey, man, don't talk about my my my god like that man my creator
No, I think we're watching my man pass out right now
He said Jacob saw we
Yeah, so that's weird because yeah, he's here. I
Guess Paige just
Our prairie tellies whatever her name was
It's why it's wild to me. I'm sorry to say this it's wild to me when you can't bring your food to your face
Like you have to go down on your food. I have no sound for a second. It's gonna just give me a minute
But that's annoying
I'm going down on now. I got a short neck
To tell you hey be quiet for a second listen listen. Yes, ma'am
Can you hear the coyotes? I
Can't I wish I did
Anyway, I'll take you out there in a minute, but they're loud
Actually, let's just go. We're going to go for a little walk. Let's go.
Did any of you all see the, uh, like the blood moon?
Yeah, I charged my crystals in it.
I saw it, uh, was like two days ago.
It was full. I was on my way to work.
I get in the car and the first thing I frequency.
This is this big red moon
It doesn't mean much to me it's what it's beautiful, you know what I mean
So it's a celestial thing and I
Believe in I believe in its existence and
It was fun. It was very fun to drive to work looking at a red moon. I'm like, oh, today's
going to be a good day. It wasn't a bad day. It was just a day like any other.
Yeah, I'd be cool with flip-flap flip-flap jump jumped on this panel
Yeah
Did psyche say he was awake or is
He jumped in the chat. He was he was typing in the chat
Okay
Yeah, maybe maybe maybe he grabbed a taco as well. Yeah taco sounds so good right now man damn
Hey, he saw he saw a signal
Flash and food and he was like, you know taco is easy
Like we were talking about
You know where they come from or whatever it's like, hey, you can put whatever you want in the taco
All you need is something to put into the taco
You you got tangerines put it in the taco
Clementines uh, you got you got some sour cream you could you know
Damn
Our cream is fire. Oh, hey, you could put lasagna. Hey, you got leftover lasagna put it in a taco
And held food has changed the world
Who needs a rocket ship? We got handheld food. Why would we go anywhere? You know what I'm saying?
But I'm uh, I'm wrapping it down for myself.
I'm not sure if I have before met you. I stopped but
It's a black guy
What's it matter? What's what's it really matter? We met each other and it's none of your fucking business. You tell me
Yeah, so yeah good talk
Love each and every one of you
Even those that have been kicked off or dropped off or
No matter how it may be
It is what it is. It's another day in paradise
It is what you make of it and I will see you
I got kicked off by a bunch of black guys like untrackable
Yeah
Just the baddest black when are you gonna paint your fucking ceiling?
Soon I promise
I'm lying
but soon you have a problem with my garage
no man i've seen these drywall marks like for how long
have you walked us the wrong side do you show people where you live
They all know they'll know
Yeah, how about you walk outside?
What's up? I'll walk I'll walk outside outside. They all know they all know exactly where
Yeah, you know exactly where
yep
They know all my shit's up to go to what's up
Your shit's not even covered right there run your fucking left side
Your right side you have an entire conduit that's uncovered
What are you talking about? That's my garage door open or you dip shit
That's the track. You have an entire fucking conduit in the motherfucking garage
And I have an entire black guy in my garage and you don't see him
So what the fuck is he talking about?
if I have to come over there and be the black guy in your garage I
Already have a black guy in my garage
Prove it prove it right now. So we're going black guy for black guy. Yeah, of course. Oh, yeah
You don't really look like a black guy kind of look like a white guy
Well, you called me a black guy
Gorilla, so now I get the pass
Not now we get the pass, right? Because you called me a black guy
I didn't give you a pass
You sorry ass fucking pass as son of a bitch
I didn't give you a pass to my garage
Come on, man. Come on. I really have to do it to you. Okay. Can you not find peace?
You're not just any ordinary black guy. Oh
I'm the white black guy. That's enough
all
It's all bad man. It's not it's not looking good. Where are all my fentanyl smokers out?
Take care of each other. That's all I got to say. Oh, yeah
Make sure you watch your shit my nigga. Oh
No, not my nigga. I send you and your family blessings
Take care of yourself
The occult is as fake as Sig's garage
Yeah already is
Come up here and explain that to me. Please enlighten me
They want you to take a shot they want that bad believe it or not believe it or not
Katrina, that's not how occultism works.
You've read too many New Age books.
Yo, Prairie, can you read my cards, please?
Oh, hi. He finally let me up. What's up?
Do you keep getting do you keep getting put in time out? What's going on here?
No, no, it's because I have like really bad internet
I was in my bedroom and then I went out to show you guys the coyotes howling and they have a tin roof
So it just kind of interferes. I don't know how to explain it
Yeah, are you on your Wi-Fi? I am now
Okay, that should help hopefully
Yes, give me a reading, please. I hope that you can give me a reading before your internet craps out
Okay, I don't know if I want to take 20 shots
Don't take 20 of them just a moment. I'm gonna grab something like here the I hear the discord notifications
Yeah, psyche man. I hope you figure that out. Um, I hope it ain't too too crazy or whatever
Cheers guys
My niggas and Chad cheers to you. Yeah, I want to see that I wanted to talk to you where it's at right now
It's almost at the bottom of the knot knotting out
It's almost at the bottom of the sticker. I need to see you get to the bottom of the stickers with this one
Let's go
How do you feel signal do you feel yeah get it in yeah
Do I feel one feel good I
Think the problem with alcoholics
And people that push it too far is that you feel good at some point and then you think
Oh, but I can feel better. It was like a dopamine and then you keep going
It's a dopamine your body actually only reacts to the first drink you have you're not gonna find it again through it, you know
Not necessarily because sometimes you do
Yeah, well, that's fair, but then you just get to the point where your shit face it out
You're out of your own mind, so you're really not feeling much better at some point. You're just completely fucked. Yeah
Are you gonna read my cards or what I wish I just said, um, cuz I was gonna say are you ready?
Are you laughing what's my what am I gonna do?
You have a tarot deck. Is that what's going on?
I'm asking her thank you very fucking much
She's asking what's going on though cuz he's also up here, so that's fair for him to ask
So I'm actually gonna channel, but I do have decks here. Yeah
Like an oracle deck or something can you like a bunch like a wall of them like I have tarot oracle, but I'm an oracle I'm
Card, I guess if you will and we would wait. Yeah, no, I understand
No, I said let's no I said let's get it going like let's start it. I'm not I'm not that way so don't I'm not trying to
Yeah, we know you're not that guy we know that you're not that guy pal letter keep going
Okay, Sig, I see and like I'm just gonna hold I don't know why but shuffling helps me tap in in my weird way. I'm gonna
Okay, so
Sig I feel like you're going through like this
Unusual for you transition. It's like you're doing new shit with I think
Not only just like your channel because that's starting to show through where are you reading your cards or is this your personal opinion?
No, this is my channeling. I'm doing what I feel first and I'll do the cards. That's how I do it
No, but I thought you were reading the cards though
Well, if you want me to read the cards then I can just be a fucking reader
But if you want me to actually
Do what I do I can't I thought that's the entire point of this shit that you're I thought I don't let her
I mean, bro, you got a letter that the entire point of this was that you're reading the cards and
that the cards are just like
This
Knowledge no the cards are clarity for the shit. I spit before let's say before I pull cards for visual
Yo page. No, I understand your man that has ever said that directly as you have ever
As I've ever heard before
Have you ever been page? Have you ever been in your city? No
There's so many like literally you walk down the block and they're hustling people for readings
Hustling them you gypsy. It's like beta
Literally look like beta no offense to be to and
They're hustling you for a reading. It's they're like, oh, oh, you're this. Oh, you're that. Oh, let me like talk to you
Oh, let me tell you your future
And that's like not even like a joke. It's a real thing
Nobody has ever described it as directly as you
Okay, well never heard it. I have to be real with you because in this like I guess whatever fucking abilities or shit
The crazy shit I do. I mean, I just don't want to lie to you. So I can't
So you're like giving people like an assessment you're like looking at the person and what they're saying and all these things
Bro, she already said it's channeling bro. Just let her cook
I'm not asking you for an answer. I've know you're not but I'm just saying thank you very fucking much
Like the vodka is clear, right? So like just let her cook. It's so much more. I think that you're fucking retarded
Okay, can you guys not I'm just trying to explain myself so sick the question that you asked so I am just like
Okay beans you gotta move babe
Surfing on cards. Yeah, I hear
Okay, you guys got to relax.
So I'm reading your energy.
All I'm doing is reading from your energy.
I'm channeling from that, tapping into you in a sense.
And I'm not going to explain the depth of what my,
because every gift they're more advanced or not.
Like it's a whole spectrum and it's its own.
But the cards I pull after to clarify what I'm saying
for visual proof for those who might be skeptic,
but it's me giving you the reading from me
from connecting to your energy.
That's why I do it in that like for order or whatever.
You want to call it.
I can't hear you. You're muted
It's because I'm muted. Oh, no, I have fucking eyeball sick. I
Believe that
So can I have permission or do I have permission to access your energy to give you this reading?
Or would you just want me to pull a card and read it for you? No, here's the thing
Like you're gonna say like you can't say like do I have permission to access your energy?
Well, I can't you can't say this and then say okay, so I'm I'm I know because you seem like a real concept
This entire concept is not real. Okay, but can you do it? No, I know
Can I tap into your energy signal what you're doing is profiling
What you're doing is profiling
If I don't ask you it's in base page
you're up and there's nothing wrong with that but I'm just like to suggest that it's some sort of
supernatural sort of thing when it's actually just
profiling yeah so signal can oh my god this is a problem with sick is like first of all he's like
doesn't respect and he doesn't believe in so he's gonna be blocked off and the problem with psyche
Okay. I'm sorry. I'm also I'm a boring. I think would you be more open ever reading from page? Yes?
That's what I've been trying to ask. I'm so sorry. Hey guys, I'll leave you guys alone. But yeah, I think it's a better chemistry
I'm sorry about you know, I can't stop leaving
Stop I just have an emergency right now. I promise I'll be back in five minutes. Okay. I'm gonna let you guys handle this
I'm trying to keep a watch on it. Okay
Thank you. Yeah, no, so as a as a practitioner myself like I said for over
Coming up close to two decades. I
Understand your methodology and I am open to it and you have permission
So I think I would work better for you to do this right now
He just wants to make keys. He's very, yeah, he likes to prove a point and that's very sick. If you're listening, obviously you are.
I'm just going to say I respect you and that's the most reason I ask you permission because it's very invasive and I know you're apprehensive and it's kind of like you fucking with me or you're not because if you want to do that, then I'm not going to do it, right?
So it is a respect for me and for you, whatever. And teach that is here that is not into this kind of shit. Sorry, just give me a minute, okay? Please respectfully.
Yeah, okay, and blind reading is are my favorite the less. I know about you like that's the that's the best outcome
Did you just finish a huge you just completed something?
I don't know if it was like something to do with schooling or like an advancement and upgrade of so words
I I think you're also very athletic
It might be something to do with that
But I also feel like it's connected to some sort of
Advancement in some a study as well. So like whatever it may be to your career. I don't think it's to your career
I think it is more like a personal thing like a you know what I mean. I feel like also
There has been some hindrance within like the heart chakra.
I feel like it's a little heavy,
so I'm not sure if you just kind of went through.
This is weird, so don't get me face.
Connected to what I just brought up,
like that extracurricular or hobby or activity or advancement.
There was something that was holding you back that had something to do with maybe.
I don't know like a friendship or just a connection in general. What is that because I I don't know
Just don't don't tell me but I'm gonna ask you questions, but I'll tell you when to tell me um
I think you're also upgrading your life.
Like it's just an ascension time for you.
So you've let this like,
but it's different than just an ascension.
There's like these stepping stones.
It's like a door was always there at the end of the stairs
and then finally it opened.
You're like, well, what the fuck?
I got to do this now.
So you jumped, it's like the full card.
You jumped and you didn't know where you was gonna go,
but you knew no matter what,
it was gonna make it better for you.
So whatever shift that you've just went through,
you let go of some things, you lost some things with that but you gained a lot more and that was
like a hard decision I think for you but also you thought about it for a long time so you were like
I just wouldn't need the hard part was making the decision it wasn't the decision itself.
I also know you're very intelligent I picked that up immediately but that's also not fair to say
just from conversing with you as well but your energy is like it's like old soul intelligence
absolute knowledge, because you saw the knowledge. You actually did the work and everything that you go through.
Some things I think you've had to go through twice though, because it's like you're like, I kind of liked how that felt even though it hurt.
So you did it again to like make sure that that's how you felt about to get hurt. You know, you have to kind of...
You've gained some maturity in that though, and I feel like you were just faced with a decision that came with that very like almost
I want to call it high school-esque mentality where you're like
Not you putting yourself in that position, but other energies or influences or other kind of like I guess
Ultimatums if you will
I really think that
You're you're definitely a go get like you when you do something you do it with your
Absoluteness like that's what I mean that word absoluteness keeps coming when it's annoying me actually because it's just constant
So absoluteness is like who your your demeanor is. It's like I get shit done
I know the facts and I move forward even though things hurt. I understand there's greater gain from risk
I mean
You're you're moving forward with whatever it is you're doing, but there's still to me this
Decision that I can't quite tap into but you're guarded so you are protecting it might be a better word for it
anyways, um, that's my
Interd, hi, I'm Paige nice to meet you
Yeah, yeah, yeah, but it's a pleasure. Yeah, okay
Hey, I feel like you got one for me or are you down for or you're still doing him?
I'm sorry. Oh, I just gave him my channel reading first. I didn't
Like I got what I just said do it. No, no, don't leave you should be an interactive
I'm gonna do the nose it
These ones I'm gonna pull one of these for you. I think
You know a lot about your dark side and your light side.
I feel like you have a lot of play in that, like me, where it's like that's to you is
wholeness one misbalance within yourself and it helps you teach and navigate and understand
other people too.
So when it comes to that, it's like you're very connected to like even the paranormal
like I am.
so it's something that like you know you're like I don't want this to maybe be a hobby one day it
could be something more that's a side it's a little side bubble that I just okay so anyways um
I don't know which deck to use for you because I think that you like this like I know that you do
because it obviously people should this is the truest form of
Channeling if you will I mean and I divinate with lots of different tools, but if you don't need them
I mean that's a true beauty in this shit, and if you're not a believer, sorry, but maybe this might help I guess I'm gonna
Tell me pick one to three one two or three
two
Okay
Sounds good
So we're gonna go through religion and go with these ones, and then I'm gonna do this since after so in order form these
Our firm dream for two as you know, she like went crazy kind of and stopped they don't make her stuff anymore
So it's interesting. I'm only pointing this point out is because if there's something about you that correlates with that where it's like
You stand true to the things like you there's a solidarity about your nature
Like you just you know what you know, and you fucking know like people try to persuade you or like whatever
But I think that's a great quality like you're not easily had if that makes sense my
throat chakra interesting
Have you been not speaking up lately like is there something is that you haven't been able to communicate?
With certain people to clear things up before you move forward with your ascension
Interesting, okay
Yeah, we've got teaching and learning we just talk about beautiful so we've
teaching and learning it's like keep an open mind which you always have but
you're teaching others to do this so this card is not so much directed at like
advice for you it's clarifying that
You're understood and like you're in the right direction with your lessons that you've learned and that it's not unrecognized
I suppose so keeping an open mind and learning new ideas and then teaching these to others
That's how you've learned. That's how you've gained this
Respect I guess in whatever regard it is like there's something that you do
I feel like you do teach you do have a healthy lifestyle like I said, I think you're
your fit, you very much body, mind, and soul balanced.
You know, eating healthy, working out,
kind of just taking care of yourself.
Even if it's not eating healthy, it's like,
or working out, whatever you do for yourself is like.
It's balance like it works for you. It nourishes you your soul all aspects of the of myself, right?
We have courage. Um, you know, maybe that's that thing if you're not speaking up about something or it's not a place for you
You think that you have a place to say something?
It's definitely time to do so and have courage as well, but I think you already know that like this is child's play to you
I'm aware. Don't worry. So take back your power
Um, I think that goes back to what I started with when it comes to maybe that like, I guess connection that you had that was involved in
Your studies or your work or you know, like something you're passionate about there was just a hindrance with that
But taking back your power ending that shit like you already know these things
You know what you have to do being self-aware and stuck is the hardest fucking place to be like I if you ask me personally, but
Um, I think you already know that lots of people in here are very smart. Yeah, Claire sentience. There you go
Of course, I know your gift did pick that up right away
You're noticing you're returning physical and emotional feelings
So I feel like you were shut down for a while because of said incident
Only you'll know. I don't know specifics. I can get into that if you want, but I
Don't know maybe maybe I'm having a hard time with that one every so far things are
Resonating I'll say that much
Okay so your gifts from God which you're also very aware and if not always very much more
prominent in the last few years because of experiences that you've gone through that have
kind of pushed you forward or opened your mind more than it was before.
I mean, I could toughen your childhood if you want me to do that, but I don't think that that you would like that here
So we're not I'm gonna pull one card or two cards from here. I think I'm gonna say that there
I'm not imposing any restrictions or limitations. Okay. Okay
There is some things that you need to clear up like within
You're inner child like it's still a trigger. I'm not sure what it is yet. I will get there
I think it's something to do with conditioning
I think it's something to do that you learned by watching your parents or your example of
Of what that is supposed to be, you know, maybe if it wasn't mom and dad, you know, but not in papa or whatever
There's something that I think affects your
Okay, you feel indifferent from how you feel and think from your experiences and your conditioning to how it like you play a
Role in in a relationship or how you play role in any kind of kind of connection or how they play role to you
It's like an expectation things but not in like a like a conceded way. It's in a
I know what I don't want because I watched it or you know, and that that's what I'm hearing, but I could be wrong
I feel like there might be more to it, but I'm not gonna expose everything
That's just like the basis of of what I feel personally not even from the cards because it did not come out
We have the Queen of Pentacles, so you're definitely climbing towards some success for that stability
and you know that there's fruit at the top of that tree, you know where the best fruit is.
It's almost like the hummingbird card in the animal oracle, it reminds me of that.
It's like knowing where the source is, the going back to the elixir, you know where to drink to
nourish myself, like I said before. So I mean, interesting, but hard work is nothing for you
either, like the pentacles are a slow build, right? But she knows what to do, she has the patience,
come to fruition so you're a very patient person I do see that or else you wouldn't have learned
all of these lessons especially in like the fucking is like crammed into a shorter period of time
each time you know like long periods of time in between a short time of cramming in ascensions
that's a weird way to put it okay um I want one more card please and thank you and then I'll let
Maybe two I do see okay, so we do have oh
So the the acupennacle so it was in the reverse so there's something that
Didn't come to fruition like I when I see these together. It's like okay, so but it was a minimal offer anyway
So there was something that wasn't gonna benefit you either way even though you did have the
The drive everything that it was needed to put into it
But the investment because of the size or the quality or quantity of the offer or whatever
Wasn't it wasn't matching your your vibe your frequency your fucking your
advanced where you are in your life right now. It didn't fit you. It was like an old,
trying to put on an old shoe. Do you know what I mean? And also going back to like that, it says
like something about your experiences. They keep bringing that up. So I don't know if you were a
little bit of a rebellious teenager. I know you went through, like I know you've experienced
stuff enough to understand it or else you wouldn't teach it. So that's where I'm kind of going back
Teenager in you there's something about that where it's like, I don't know if it's like
Certain energies for sure a huge play in that but even environments like you're very sensitive to your environment
You're very sensitive to people's emotions being very empathic like you are it's like oh see my lights just flickered
Did you see that?
clarity. Love it. So I mean, hindsight, you know who you are. So that's not what this reading is about.
It's about where you're going and if you are making the right decisions, I think.
And I know that you know where the fruit is, but it's almost like
using a different ladder or like finding a different tool to do so. So you're kind of in
another experience like you love to you're always on the go like you're a
mover you know what I mean I don't see there's no stagnancy really in any of
this and your energy is in it's always is pushing mine forward like I just want
to leap out of my chair kind of okay so it's not giving me another card I'm gonna
look on the bottom and the hermit so lately you've been maybe out of your
norm or out of your like it's not out of character for yourself to others in
Kinds like when they're looking and seeing what you're doing you're but you they don't know what you're doing behind the scenes
Like you're going in there's introspection and you're being quiet and not so
Socially out there, but you have a plan and I know that you do and I know you're working really hard at it
and you're gonna have a great outcome, but
There is getting in the way of yourself that keeps becoming an issue
I feel like that's your biggest problem is just you are you get in the way of self
But you're working on it. I want to know I want to know if this makes sense because I mean like I
Do really enjoy reading your energy. Thank you for letting me do that. If you'd like to speak now go right ahead
Yeah, yeah, that was a yeah, that was a good reading
So like I said, I'm very familiar with this work and
sitting there and trying to, you know, open myself up and resonate with what you're saying, you did a great job. Um, yeah, you made me reflect on things that weren't necessarily in my sight. If that makes sense, like not something under my radar, but is it's something that's going on in my life that I wasn't necessarily aware of.
The work the hidden work
Protecting that work. That's all accurate
And that's like yeah, it's not like anything to do with my job or my family per se, but it's an esoteric
Coal endeavor. It's a philosophical. It's a metaphysical endeavor a magical endeavor and it's been it's been a thing
For most of my life, but as of recently
You are you are correct. It's culminated into something more important
I
Guess she dropped off. Yeah, the the reading was good for sure
There were some things that were a little and not many just a couple points that were
Her face value they didn't seem accurate
But I can I can bend them enough to make them make sense. So
She's actually, yeah, she's actually good at her work.
I'm surprised.
Not many people are, you know, genuine when they do this.
So yeah, that's interesting.
So I'm looking at the chat here.
I'm the type of person on a panel that does that.
I kind of, I will look at the chat from time and time again.
During her reading I didn't but as I'm looking over bonebuilder says you said too much now. She lost interest
No, she's it's her connection. I think
He also the person also said he needs a woman the end. I'm married. I have three children
I don't think I need another woman
So yeah page was cooking for sure
Hey psyche
Yeah, yeah, yeah, not in that sense though. No, they're more
Ceremonial, I guess was how I put it not not riffing off to fly like that. I'm not like a medium or anything
Mine is more for
Formulaic or whatever more of a science than an art
Okay
Well, I think Paige might be coming back up. I think that is your connection. So
I'm in a shirt tonight. I look okay. I look okay. I take a shower. It's bath actually and I clean up my house a lot and
You know trying to make some positive changes for myself and it's been a little bit wild here lately and stuff
little bit
you know
Little bit difficult at times, but I think that uh sometimes the the outer can reflect the inner and
Um, that's interesting how so you baby, it sounds like you're very
You know, I heard I heard you're a bit about like all your
all your
your studies and your you know
Associations and things like that and that's very interesting. Like I'm more of
personally
Solid solitary practitioner. I'm like, you know, I kind of
More as you kind of
Being under under oaths and things like that, but everybody's different. Some people are more
Extroverted and like the like liking groups and working groups. Oh, here's page is back. Okay. Here you go
I'll I'll I'll mute it mute up and let you guys spin
Okay
I'm so sorry, and I don't know what happened, but it just dropped
So that also might mean that maybe I was supposed to give I don't know this little connection. I'm sorry. I didn't run from you.
It's doing it again.
Oh my God, maybe I'll just like switch.
I will move my shit around. Let's see if I can fix it.
Oh, yeah, looking at the chat flip flat. So in the golden dawn, I made it to five six before I realized that it really wasn't for me, which was a deptus minor.
So, yeah, second, second order.
Let's just say this, the goal, my goal is different from theirs.
My goal is really niche.
And I've come to find that in a different.
Practice which it would be defined as solitary like psyche was mentioning. I've always been a solitary practitioner
behind the scenes right when I go home, and I'm not a not a you know going to Lodge or
Joining a circle or or an anthroposophical movement
per se like
I'm doing work behind the scenes
So so solitary has always been important to me. I think without it. You're not really a magician
You have to have that
But yeah, it's healthy to get out there like I wouldn't be so reserved
I have confidence and have
Courage right like you are the
Indole be all to your path
As long as you understand that no order or oath or obligation should come between that
Right those should be superficial
at best
Right, but they take the oaths very seriously and it's like right like those are in there
Some of them are extremely serious like extremely like you know the threat of being unripped out and trampled by you know dogs
I mean, it's like there's some some hardcore oath
You know along the way. I think that I like to be able to just
not be afraid to actually because I'm a big blower mouth and I can say the wrong thing and so
Plus, you know pretty introverted, but yeah, you're guys. I think you're exactly right about
Ultimately like the spiritual path for me and maybe it's a different for other people, but the spiritual path for me is about
Self-improvement, you know, and they ultimately and yes. Yeah, and that is it. That's the true magic. It's internal
It's not an external thing it can you can express your
Internal journey right like the the progress you've made internally you can express that externally it can manifest externally
But yeah, those obligations that you're mentioning right like in these days. They don't even call them oaths anymore most member
You are
just like like like Alistair Crowley you know he was like the OTO or that was the
Golden Dawn and the OTO but he came he was initiated in Freemasonry in Mexico
he had like you know he had these you know there's a picture of him was just
covered in metals and decorations and it kind of almost looks ridiculous because
there's just so many and it's like it reminds me of the Wizard of Oz where he
you know, they're looking for their heart and their brain and their courage and things and he
gives them medals and degrees and things like this, but it's like those are just window dressing.
Those aren't the real things. It's like it's actually like the internal spiritual, like your
internal, like the alchemy of approving yourself, right? I mean, that's what I, I kind of look at it.
But yeah, no, it's a good way to look at it. Yeah.
the theosophists with like Manin Blavatsky Society
What was the name?
L. Frank Baum and the Wizard of Oz author. Oh, I'm unfamiliar, but probably
Light and frankly I see that he was a theosophist. Oh pages back. Here we go. I mean, I'll meet up
And to be forward, I was never a member of the OTO or the AA
Or I'm not a thalamite, so I've never really been into Crowley's work, but uh pretty much everything else under the sun
While as a Crucianism, I'm a member of the fraternities rather than Crucianism of the lineage of Pascal Beverly Randolph
Martinism
Some of Scottish right Mason York right Mason
I've just I don't know. I've chased the thread as far as I can. I
Didn't mean to leave. I'm sorry. I'm the fucking worst in the world
And it was on my favorite part when I got to hear what you thought
Yeah, yeah, if
Yeah, if so, I'm trying to remember where I left off
So basically I was just saying that your reading was good most people don't
They're not authentic, you know with their work
You seem to be authentic
It's it's genuine. It came off most of it came off as accurate
Listening to the word and opening myself up to them
I was able to align a lot of my experience with the reading.
There were a couple things like I was mentioning when you fell off.
There were maybe just like two points that were kind of further out.
But thinking about them long enough, I was able to bend it enough to actually make sense of them.
Like the whole parents thing.
There was some reaching for me to do there, but...
It kind of made sense in context of the work the work that I'm protecting the work that I'm advancing in turn
So yeah, it was overall a really good reading. I'm surprised the job
Thank you. I mean when it's not on here. They're a little different a little bit more
People are vulnerable like you're accessing information that is
Shit that like you said you had to search for but I see it so to a certain extent though
Because you can take certain like vague fucking knowledge or just say something and someone can relate to it
And I actually one thing I really hate is that YouTube or like most places have used this as a monetary trend for gain
Like you know what I mean? It's not
it's not that they're they're genuine it's like anyone can pick up a tarot deck and read fucking
what it means like anyone can be a reader no offense to anybody who is love i'm happy for you
in your journey and you know but there's an in there's i know things since i was in diapers i've
just been a fucking weirdo like i know i knew i was different for it like my whole life you know
Hypersensitivity or fucking abilities. I don't know what it is, but I can do a lot of different stuff and
it's hard to
Do when you have collective energy like this
It's a lot of people to connect to but it's also like I mean you are free people out either and it's vulnerable for the person
You're giving a reading to so to be respectful to them
It's like that's a that's a one-on-one thing for like a decent like you know sit-down reading
But thank you very much for like, you know being as
general, I guess, kind of without freaking people out and shit, you know, that's what I can do and offer.
Hence the, I try to tap into you, my personal self with my energy connecting to yours first, and therefore then the cards are visual proof.
And normally I always do clarify what I've said, the shit I spit I say.
I want to say something though to address it because it seems, okay, you trying to stretch
yourself to connect to it, digging deep is different, and I think that's what you mean,
which is fine.
But like trying to find something to connect, to resonate to a reading, it doesn't, if
it doesn't resonate, it doesn't resonate, you know, sometimes we're off, but what I
meant by those things is like, it's like, okay, there's stuff that I feel like
If it was off also, it could be something that you need to work on the future like some things
I've said they come to fruition later
The people will call me and be like holy fuck you weren't wrong. I didn't understand it at the time
And it's like okay
So some things and when I get this information you guys it comes to me in pictures videos sent smell
loved ones talking to me in spirit like there's so much going on and I have to just kind of make sense of it
to spit it to you so that you can understand it because it makes no fucking sense to me,
not the stuff, you know what I mean? And it comes to me so strangely. So that's also learning
to use your gifts or your intuition, whatever the fuck you want to call it, weirdness.
And then, you know, you're going to see where it resonates in your life. I'm just giving you the
information that's coming to me in the best way I can with how it's coming to me. Does that make
any sense? It does make sense. And maybe I am misunderstood or I didn't explain myself good
No, you weren't wrong. You weren't wrong. Yeah, no, you weren't wrong about anything. A lot of it is
in alignment and accurate actually
Like I said, there was only like two points out of all that five to ten minutes of reading, which was a lot of words, right?
There's only like two points
that seemed off it to begin with but when I sat there and let it sink in I was doing my work on
my side right being quiet and listening and letting it absorb it right I was absorbing it and yeah
it made sense I'm like okay yeah well that was something that was not on my radar I just I wasn't
paying attention to it but now that and that's why I like readings because it will open you up to
thinking about exactly yeah that's why it's one of the main reasons I do tarot is for that reason
because sometimes we're too busy in life to notice the things that are more subtle.
So yeah, you guys are a good picture. Oh, thank you. Do you like doing reading for yourself?
I don't like doing it for myself. I mean, I will and I do, but I prefer...
like you were talking someone was talking earlier on here when I first jumped up and they were saying
it just hits different when you hear it from someone else like my spirit guys are telling me
all the time they're always like this in a corner shaking their head at me it's like you know that
why why did someone else have to tell you and it's like because it just hits different it just
resin it just doesn't place where you want to forward movement might come from it rather than
Well, not my work particularly, but yes, you're right most of the time. It's very biased, but yeah, it does hit different from somebody else
Yeah, that that group work element that especially the one-on-one the group work element
I think when you have a big group that you kind of can become convoluted and tainted. There's a lot of energy there
You're picking up on a lot of different shit, right?
So as your good reader, if you can weave through that and keep your tunnel focused on the person you're reading with that many different energy
interferences
Yeah, yeah, that's the good ones, right? Yeah
There's people who have that ability for sure and you know it by the reaction of the individual that you're reading
Those they'll they'll tell you they they'll know that you and they'll they'll make it known that you what you're talking about
Yeah, you do a good job. How long have you been doing it?
Fox like maybe eight years old. I got my I mean I've been doing it since before that
But I didn't know what I was doing when I was doing it when I was younger. Does that make sense? Yes
Yeah, so I mean like I mean like I said since I was in diapers
I knew I was different because of just the way the energy came off of other kids to me and I could see their energy
I could I knew stuff that I shouldn't know and then I was like I had nobody to ask or guide me and it was fucking weird
Like this stuff kind of just became
More of like mainstream something that was socially kind of acceptable because like I would have been burned or lobotomized
If it was like back in the day, let's be real, okay?
Yeah, run it in an asylum because there was something wrong with me
Which is sad because it happened to a lot of gifted people
But I'm just saying like I get that this might seem kooky, but when you know you fucking know, right?
Like it's just something you just know you feel it is who you are
Yeah, that's true. And yeah, when you said being general, right? I
Don't mean to be it's it's exactly what you said in your reading. It's I'm purposely protecting it, right?
It's something that I do not want to disclose and the courage thing kind of makes sense because
With tight-knit circles or closed groups, I do fear speaking too much about it, but I do have the sensation that I need to with certain people and maybe I need to loosen up a bit to disclose some of this information or this wisdom.
I feel like it is more of just like it comes with an insecurity of trust of such or said,
you know, ability.
Like it's like, I don't, you don't want to over, like overstep you there.
Like it's a weird place to be when you have messages to deliver, but also don't trust
trust.
You know what I mean?
It's like, it's like, I don't not trust my gifts.
I don't trust other people with certain information.
You know your I know you're empathic like a super empath
And so the ability to just use your discernment with that we're just getting a read from people first before you expose yourself
Or expose anything that might hurt you in the long run or I've said, you know, like kind of thing
It definitely is hard, but also it makes it easier if
your your your intuition you guys you all have it the intuition is literally instilled in us our
most primal fucking natural state of a human being and it's connected to you are knowing and it
helped us survive you know like you had to know to be scared of something to fucking run from it
to survive from it right we were not always on the top like we were not always top dog so there's
certain things that we you know we use that to your advantage in life like you can come to somebody
but knowing you're using your own intuition and your own got feeling you're knowing in your own like hey
I see that shadow move like you when it comes to the paranormal or like you're no
spirits whatever you want to call it like all of that stuff and also being closed off like
this is another topic which is good to open with what we just talked about and you're reading and
thank you for letting me use it as an example but teaching and learning to come up so this is kind
Like don't block yourself off to the point where you forget that you
Can do such things does that make sense like use your intuition? It's in you. It's instilled in you
You know shit. You just need clarity you need to hear it different or from someone else
I don't know. Maybe that's just me and I talked to you. Yeah
No that the last thing you just said is what it takes right because the intuition is sharp
Yeah, the discernment is sharp. Yeah
Yeah
It's this hearing it from somebody else, right? It's this echo chamber where I'm so reserved
To disclose right like it's more so that my cosmology is like a dualistic cosmology
I
Adhere to this idea that there is a spiritual war and that there is a true thing as an enemy
So with that sense right with that sense in me
the enemy is always lurking right but sometimes there there's the loyal there's the companion
there's the comrade that needs their teaching or whatever and i think that's the problem i'm
having right now is i'm i'm kind of uh bow guarding the wisdom i'm kind of holding the
the fuck was it for a pentacles and he's just like this is mine like yeah and you know exactly
you're withholding the the knowledge and the wisdom that you have to share
one thing i'll say i think i think maybe our biggest enemy is our own selves you know
I won't even expand on that.
It's like, but we are our biggest sabotagers.
We're probably already on ourselves
that our enemies are, right?
We are our biggest enemy.
You know, you can look in the mirror
and see your, which is sad
because we're a lot more amazing
than we give ourselves credit for.
Also, we create what we speak, manifest our thoughts
and project and attract what we feel.
So keep that in mind as well, as always.
And we also attract circumstances in our life
that can bring us the greatest lessons
and our biggest difficulties,
actually we've learned the most from it.
So our enemies are actually our teachers
in certain ways, right?
Our biggest enemies are actually,
they get us to grow and they get us to.
to do better for ourselves and so we keep your friends closer, your enemies closer for that ascension purpose. You're totally right.
Keep yourself the closest, you know.
Right, exactly.
Exactly, and there are like, you know, we're talking about things like, you know,
governments and stuff, and you know, people taking over and stuff. I tell you guys, there are these outer enemies, but it's basically,
they're also
it's easy to villainize, villainize greed,
race.
Yeah, I just think it's
So we're kind of you're kind of struggling a little bit, sorry
Sorry, you know, it's my bad. I was just agreeing with you. I was agreeing with you. Thank you
Yeah, I mean it's and it's also like, you know
our world is a reflection of our of our inner world in a lot of ways
And so that
Oh, go ahead.
Go ahead.
When we change ourselves, the world changes.
If we can change ourselves, all of a sudden, the different circumstances will come in.
That's all I wanted to say.
No, it's totally right.
It's a great topic.
I love this topic.
It's a good topic, and it definitely correlates with all of the rest of the theme of what
you kind of put up tonight.
our own world. We do have so much more power than we even think, right? And also our source,
like, it doesn't matter what religion you are, you guys, like, religion is based off the same
idea of a higher power creator, right? It's just different. People pass it down to create, to suit
them in whatever endeavor they were in, and it's just now, it is what is just written, okay? And
it's beautiful if you believe in what you believe in. I take that and I emulsify it into my beliefs
I'm not don't belong to anything I just belong to my own beliefs and I don't I know if you
don't agree with that that's okay and I'm sorry if I offend you but I'm just saying I believe
in all of what you you know do and for who you are and what it makes you feel and I respect it
so it's just all the idea of the same thing it's just kind of bullet point and fine print indifferent
categories in a weird way.
But either way, I love this topic tonight.
Psych, good job.
Thank you.
I mean, it's like, and it's really,
it is refreshing to like.
You know, it's funny like I like kind of like clean myself up a little bit
put on my shirt and like
I think it's a vibe. You're fueling yourself. I need to tell.
And it kind of attracts like a nicer
Nicer circumsents. And it's like and I'm responsible as a host to like, you know
I mean I was I did kind of mess up because I was not here or super busy
Super busy like concerning guests are a little bit
I'd call you, I'd call, I'd feel bad but if I woke I called you and I wasn't just like
No, you didn't. I wasn't asleep or anything
I was I just couldn't have the volume on at the same time I was doing something else and um and I was and I
Got it kind of wrapped up and stuff
But um, and I think that the people like sing like he's always been the same
It's like he'll challenge you. Oh, you're shuffling the cards wrong or this?
I think you're reading like I've known him for almost two. I've known him most of you for like at least two years now
You know, and I honestly
He's always just, I know who he is. It's okay. He is sick. He has no excuse to him for acting the way he does.
It's not, I'm not allowing him to sing. I know who he is. I know what to expect.
So he doesn't really bother me or disappoint me because that's just fucking, I know what I'm getting, you know?
But I was excited to give him a reading because it's, I mean, I mean, it's needed.
But I did question it because I knew that he was fucking with me a little bit.
It was just about that, you know, he didn't want to actually hear what I had to say
So it would have been a waste of my fucking air kind of and you know, whatever
The lights just flickered again. Yeah, there you go
For those of you
I'm not trying to cut you off or anything, but I think there's a like a echo coming through your
Your side page after you
If you just press mute or whatever I can hear psyche better. I'm having trouble hearing him
I'll get closer to my microphone. You mean better now. I'm sorry
My let me see if my mic is okay. I think he's having problems hearing me. I'm not sure but
Yeah, well, you know, you can always if you're interested, you know, go back
Yeah, but I was kind of expounding on like kind of the point about enemies and you can hear me. Okay hostile
Yeah, no, I've got you up to this point. I just want to bring it up for the future. Yeah. Yeah, and
And and also, you know, thank you page like page has always been yeah
It's like as for like cards cards are a tool. It's like cards are like for me when I read it
I am we all have a different
different style of reading and things like that
But and for me like, you know
It's the basically I have a lot of thoughts coming in
I have some of times a lot of voices are coming in and it's kind of makes it easier to focus on
a storyline or and also at cards
I'm like very versed in symbology and so
Different symbols on different decks and different things. They just pop out at me and so I will go with these and I was like
I'm not sure of the significance of some people sometimes, but I'll you know, so, you know and as for
You know as for you know, there are people that are just
monetarily concerned. I mean, it's like I really don't
Push reading on people. Like, you know, I kind of started as a terror channel then I
Since there were so many trolls and so much negativity and you're not really sure who to trust about it
You know part of part of like kind of like, you know
Finding out people are serious or interested is I don't think there's anything wrong with
Charging a reasonable fee especially for like long long detailed readings
You know, I do with tons of readings for free most of them like 90 like 95% of the readings
I I do for free, you know, but I do think there's an energy exchange
I do think sometimes when people pay for something they a little maybe appreciate it more sometimes
Of course, I've been very criticized. It is a troll community. Yeah, also a get
You know, it's not easy being a gay, you know, spiritual person and it's like, I'll get criticized no matter what I do, it's like people will just always, you know, try to be contrarian and things like that and we have difficult personalities.
But the thing is it's like everybody has these powers. It's not like anything. I'm special or anything. It's just who like some people decide to
Develop them or get more into them. I've also been I think I got my I don't think I got my first terror decade eight years old
It was called the terror of the cat people my second deck was called the mythic tarot. I was always at this
Shop called the second guy when I was young I had taken my lunch money or whatever save it up and go
I think I have my first book I got with
My first book is called the way it was like by Valerie worth or something on Valerie worth the what is that rhoda?
It was hurt. I mean the lady's name was Valerie though
And it was like it was like the richest book of spells and incantations and that was this and I about the satanic Bible
It like a very young age the lady was like, what are you reading this for like?
You know, I was just always, I was different like that too, you know, and it's like, um, and then I went from almost getting kind of into this darker, satanic view of the world, this more negative view of the world, this like, oh, there's the animals, and then there's the gods kind of kind of thing, and oh, it's okay, the people, like most people are just these hurt animals, like, not hurt animals, but H-E-R-D, like, you know,
people are kind of like put down to livestock or dehumanized almost and the older I got I think
around 27 years old that's called usually the word no it is called the Saturn return you know
every 27 years Saturn is where it was when you were born usually have this big karmic
Upheaval and that's what happened to me and it's like everything went crazy and I and I but it led to mice a real spiritual awakening and
since then I pretty much devoted myself to the study of things and so
You know, it's not it's really nobody's business about
What people's gifts are or people's job to judge people's gifts that are I think are given by the divine by the highest by and
so
I try not to be judgmental. I try to be forgiving. I try to be loving. I respect people of all religions
I think there are good and bad
Behavior behavioral people and on all things. I also believe that you know, ultimately people can
Decide to change for the better and things like that
Yeah, and page says our soul plants the seeds. It's up to us to nurse flowers
Or the wheat um or your or pole the weed. Yeah, or the weeds. I used to love this
But I prefer to nourish the flowers and the weeds and context of our duality the light in the dark within
Yeah, and that's such a thing. It's like, you know, we're born or we're conceived in darkness
Look, the womb is a dark place and we're nourished in this dark place and when we sleep we're in the dark
And so the dark's not necessarily evil. The light's not necessarily good
like just look at Lucifer this angel of light, right?
And so and there's a little bit of pride maybe there were
He doesn't just want to be like God or he wants to he wanted to be God, right?
But you can you can read in Ezekiel and things are
Um, and I think it's also in Corinthians that the the
I say and I say yeah, but yeah
I say the devil was ones that God's covering cherub his most favorite a favorite angel the leader of the heavenly choir
But then he wanted to be God instead of be like God and so God's like, okay
Well, if you want to see how easy it is, you know, why don't you rule your own worlds and basically?
There's a there's a line of thought that
he is the ruler of this world, that he was given this world, that made me to test people.
And, you know, we're going through this alchemy, we can decide to go further into hell and
ignorance, despair, we can think everything's meaningless, or we can, we can decide to change,
to grow, to improve, to do better, to help, to love, to be...
Compassionate I mean these are not things that we're born. We're not born. So compassionate. We're born
Selfish basically because we need to be we need to cry and get you know a bottle and stuff and get our needs met
But it's like as we mature we can decide to go down darker paths
We can decide to like manipulate people for our own gain. We can decide to be cruel. We can decide to be
Merciless we can I mean or we can decide to be
Compassionate kind and see others as what what is the saying in the cash or namaste?
I said the divine and myself sees the divine in you even I
Didn't think that some people get pulled in by the darkness and it's like it can be difficult to pull them out
But I think that there may be a still a
glimmer to a tiny little glimmer even if there's a just a hardly anything there anymore of this powerful light that is more powerful than
anything and
That can if we call on it and we develop a relationship with that we can
Pull ourselves out of almost anything, but that's up to us. That's not necessarily up to any other people
It's like that's our responsibility to nurse that little seed right this page might say that's a seed
I hope I put it in an interesting way or this is just my that's how I think and everybody's individual
but I always say everyone's
Everyone's different, but in the way everyone's also the same the same because we're all I believe we're all human and
Some people can get very animalistic and
Right, but at the end of the day, I'm very wary to dehumanize or to become so prideful that I call myself a God above others or I'm better than others.
I think we have different experiences, different things happen. I don't know. I'm sorry if I'm talking to you, but you can respond or you can give your view of that or let me know.
No, I enjoy your explanation. It's a pretty...
Um, and I don't mean this in a negative way a common explanation for it
And I think it's a correct assessment the right like people who actually understand it. This is the response
And it's not like the twisted dark left-hand path response. This is like the
level-headed, what typical, you know, magic would label as high or right hand
path magic. You could say centered, right? I'm not labeling you, but most, the
average, right, the majority of these type of practitioners would have that same
assessment. Yeah, I mean, you're going to Crowley and he's called the
He also had a very holy, I think he got overtaken by his demons.
I think that he did a lot wrong.
And I think, you know, it's like basically like sex magic.
I mean, yeah, you can like, you know, make love and create a baby.
And that's, that's a magical act, right?
Or you can like eat abortions basically and ask for material gain or things like that.
Some of these societies are on the
I'm sorry to say have lost their way and
I mean the the ends justify the means kind of attitude
Mmm, that means you can do a lot of evil to
For whatever you think is the right thing and stuff. I mean it's like and it's a lot about and some of this I think is about
externalizing these enemies and seeing all these that this is my enemy this
person is bad there's good and bad people right there's good and it's like I
can see that there's good and bad in all people because that's part of being
human and it's like
We can nourish the good or what it's like the two wolves in the Indians tail
It's like there's two wolves and one one one so like love one says about which one are you gonna feed and it's like
You know, maybe like give love and compassion to both wolves and try to
share
With both of them instead of trying to like starve one to death
and make the other one big and fat and gluttonous.
See, I don't know, there's different ways.
So I don't think it's as common as you might think.
I think that it's pretty much common
to be very materialistic in this world.
It's common to be very selfish and to encourage it.
And it's like, you know, the psychopaths
and the anti-heroes are celebrated these days.
And it's fun to have these groups
Say this is the enemy and then I say and we're powerful because we're a group and this person is like this little weak little
Look and look at Jesus. He Jesus had 12 disciples, right? And it's like, you know, he didn't need
Thousands of doubt he wasn't looking for thousand thousand people or millions of people even though
His teachings have affected millions of people right he had his his group and he was even betrayed by his group
People and that he that he loved and trusted betrayed him and sold actually one of them
Sold him out for 30 pieces of silver
Judas and then you know Judas felt so guilty afterward. He hung himself. I mean that is in the bible
um, and so
You know, I'd suggest like, uh
You know, there's cultural, there's people that are born into things and taught things and basically ingrained into things and it's like, so it's hard to get past it's programming basically at the end of the day, right.
And it's like when you're programmed and you're like this and it's like this and then if you're programming as a child when the brain is developing and all these connections are being made.
It can be more difficult to pull yourself out of some of the negativity
But is it impossible? No, because I think that with God and with love, especially I think love
Love really I think God is love personally, but I think with love all things are possible. And I think if the world was more
Evil than it was
good
We would have not we've already destroyed it already, but we are in the process of
destroying it too, right?
Then again, we have to realize the material world is just illusory, temporary, a billion
lives of a billion or eight billion lives, you know, of a hundred years is like a blink
of the eye to the divine or to God, in my view, you know, I'm sorry, you can respond
to her.
Go ahead.
No.
Yeah.
No, it's all good stuff.
I prefaced it with not to be negative right? It's not I didn't think it was negative
I just don't think it's I don't think it's common. I think that it's common amongst the niche group of magicians who have a level head
Right. This is the outcome. This is it. It's it's this
You have a level head, right? That's what I'm saying
If you knew me like you might maybe I have my moments, you know, I'm like I I mean I'm
I'm I'm really
Yeah, no, I'm not saying all the time right your assessment is a level-headed assessment
I should be I wasn't really arguing. I'm just like, you know, yeah
Of course. Yeah, I just didn't want to come off wrong. I wanted to make myself
Yeah, and you you people think you put things very well too and express yourself very well very
Listen, I've had to deal with personalities just yelling at me being like, you know
saying the worst things just to like find those
Wounds to find those triggers and then just hurt me as bad as they can and so I have seen the face of evil
Okay, but it is it can be in us like I mean it's like it's actually I think all of us have the good and evil
it's the light and the dark and
You know, so but I think that's why pride is maybe one of the most serious sins is because
all of a sudden it's making yourself God and
giving yourself the ability to judge others when it's really not our
Our business to judge others when we're all imperfect beings in my opinion and and I'm glad if there are these higher
magician magicians who
Ascribe to that and I hope that's a common thought of them, but it's like at the same time like, you know
Just like Crowley like he would like be sitting there
Summoning demons
To try to like look for gold basically for material things and he was wasting this divine energy
Supposed to be alchemizing our soul on to getting these temporary
And where did he died? I guess a heroin addict in the boarding house. Yeah
you know, and regretful and like, oops, I fucked up, you know, and just like Anton LeVe, again,
oops, you know, oh my god, like, it's like, I don't want to have the deathbed regret. I want to
figure it out now while I'm here, I have the ability, right? Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, and a further correction, right? Because I may have come off.
clear. Um when I say hi magic, I don't necessarily mean advanced magicians or
adepts. I mean the classification of high magic. I wouldn't say Crowley was
concerned with high magic at all. He was a low magician.
like entirely a low magician the only well okay one percent of it was the holy guardian angel which
i would critique that was actually his main he he would say that that was the main goal of magic
and that he like said he said okay well there's the goetia and he meddled in the goetia a lot but
ultimately he said well that's a waste of time because what you really want to be doing is finding
your holy guardian angel which is really your higher self ultimately i don't want to say that
But to be used as a tool though. It's once you come into contact with the holy guardian angel. You use it for low magic
Like I said, it was it was he did he did. Yeah
Well, yeah, and he kind of got that from golden dawn assuming that I was right it was I look at what we have now
I was and that's so interesting. Yeah as AI at the front of it. It is so interesting
Yeah, but like I said you and your assessment in Crowley's I would say are different. Oh
Definitely different, but I mean if you study them extensively there is so much beauty and art and beautiful
channels wisdom and some of this garbage garbage and it's like purely sick
and it's like even the book of the law I'm like I mean but the sad thing with the
book of the law is that it's
Kind of coming true in a certain way, and it's like, you know
mmm
That was it that was actually channeled by you know
In Egypt and it was like I guess the voice I'm thinking was rose like his girlfriend and stuff that was
channeling
through sex magic rituals and while he was writing stuff down as a scribe almost like
Are you familiar with the Elrond Hubbard Jack Parsons? Absolutely, man. Everything that you're
talking about right now, I own, I have all the equinoxes. I have all the, I have all of his works.
I've studied AA. I have the AA curriculum. I'm familiar with OTL. And a lot of it is plagiarized,
like not plagiarized necessarily, but a lot of it is like the secret knowledge that he
But I think nowadays everything's out there.
All the information is out there,
but the thing is about the discernment, the motive,
like the, and people, I mean, there's so much information.
It's like, what is, what do you look at?
What is true?
That is like where the guide comes in to show you,
like that the end, this voice is higher voice.
And there's, it's the devil and the angel on the shoulders
with a higher voice.
You know pulling you up wanting you to do better. There's a lower voice then go
Let's you can roll around in the mud and fight with pigs and stuff and what happens you fight with pigs
You know the pigs enjoy it and you get dirty and you just fought with a pig
And also that's the same thing throwing pearls before swine, too
Like I was I was used to be more like oh share this information with everybody everybody should have it's not
For everybody to understand everybody's on their own path along this spiritual journey
And it's not my place to judge anybody else's path, right?
I have my own
But also I asked like people
Have the respect not to judge my path at the same time. Yeah, I said, oh
You're gay, but you're celebrating Christmas?
Like, why are gay people allowed to celebrate Christmas?
There's people that say, oh, well, the Bible says that gays and witches and all these have
to not be suffered to live, and some people are thirsty right now to crucify people.
Like, they want to bring crucifixion back.
Look at what happened in Germany 100 years ago, which is not really that very long ago.
And look what's happening again 100 years later.
The same things are happening almost right before the bad stuff happened in Germany. It was almost the same social climate in
Germany, which is includes a bit like a such a liberalism and such a
overfreedom in some things that there is this tremendous
backlash and then the evil
takes over and
With by the time that happens nobody can do anything about it. It's it's takes on a zeke geist or a
Spirit or someone said the word there's a star of our gentle the silver star, right?
Yeah, the ones like cacao demons with the cacao demon is kind of like the
Like a whisper in your ear of the but it's kind of considered the evil spirit. I believe you know the cacao de monas
like a
Kind of an evil spirit and but I'm saying we have both the good and the evil in us
It's like it's up to us to discern and to
Decide what to listen to because they're gonna be the voiceless that tells us we're garbage and we're nothing in life
Is meaningless and there's gonna be the boy and to hate people and to be selfish
There's gonna be boys telling us to love and to do better and to be better
That's what they got to say. Yeah. No, it's good stuff man. Good riff. Yeah
Yeah, we want to come up
Or I don't know how much time you I think I might have to wrap up like by probably by minute. I'm trying to I mean it
But if anyone wants to come up and talk, I'm willing to run it a little while longer.
And I might.
Yeah, you want to do some trivia trivia tonight? Yeah. Well trivia. What does that mean? It's like trivia is like the tribe three
It's like, you know, and there's like these three. It's interesting
You know, and there's also a goddess named Hecate the triple goddess and she was also called trivia
That was one of her names interesting
And also, I'm getting a lot of right now for Lilith and stuff
Calling Lilith a
Child killing demon and all oh here. Here we go. Yeah, let's open it up. Hi guys. How are you? Hi?
I'm by quack-quack-quack. Yo, thanks.
Literally the same time
Quack, yes, I got a great time with you on my panel early
I just got to make sure everything's get past everything's good no strikes no bullshit, and then I'm coming right back
I'm gonna put it back up
Awesome. Oh, yeah, get your little fucking mr. Clean looking ass up here, too, bruh
Right over there text him in this in a child like he's stressing his shit. He about to grow his that lose more
Yeah, I bet you a button shit reverse
He about to get the alpha for you about to get that one strand of hair just pop up thing
I've been begging thing to come up for a thing for the past two weeks. And he's like, no
You know, I'm gonna play with him is this for this is for we're gonna play thing
If I have a panel, will you come up? Or if we be a co-host on my life?
Will you come up? We do something with somebody you're being weird.
We're sad. Yeah.
Yeah, he's gone quiet a little bit. Well last night. I was interested. Oh wait
He said hold on he got to make a coffee. Oh, okay. That's great
Like last well last night, you know, I have been doing like some and it's like people will say oh
I mean I get so criticized for making use of AI and any like in new ways and things like that
Like I've scraped every single I'm trying just I'm still in the process of getting every single transcript of every single one of my shows and
to analyze
Every every guest and things like that is the last time we'd be read about Alexander McQueen
And then we did thing that is and besides I mean the AI got a little bit confused that thought thing that is in Mason
We're the same person which is
Yeah, that was a guy fully hair with a guy. No hair. Oh my god. No a guy who has many shirts and a guy who has none
Yeah, and then, you know, and it was saying, oh, well,
the thing that is, it's sort of, she's from Canada,
and he's 34 years old, and he plays the drum,
and I was like, no, this is a little confused,
but it did say one thing about the thing that is,
that I think we all got, we all got some chills.
Like, one of them says, you know,
I guess it was at the very end, and it says,
I was in here.
Oh, it's pretty good.
So this is what we asked, you know, what is,
Tell us about Thing That Is based on the transcript and his appearance on the show.
And so it says Thing That Is fits the witness boundary keeper archetype from the middle.
So it's a quiet observer who sees through the chaos, but he also has an element of the full
initiate, entering conversations with genuine curiosity rather than agenda.
Psyche's tribute song to him, you know, the everything that is song,
says essentially canonizes him as the philosopher of the community.
the one who argues with integrity and seeks the truth.
The warlock pathology, the panel builds on around him,
is the community's way of acknowledging
that someone that calm and that reasonable in a space
this chaotic must have some kind of hidden power.
So I just got chills again reading that,
but I think that was pretty fucking cool.
And I think he kind of enjoyed a lot of the assessment.
So we have Alex McQueen coming up.
I
Quack-quack Alex quack-quack. You're the fifth quack my man. You've been initiated into the crew
You know what's like he told beat him earlier recently he said I'm gonna get a fucking quack a duck tattoo
Well, instead of the cat
Yeah, he told
You know, it's about stopping quack. I'm keeping quack quack as much
We should all get ducks on our ass cheeks right a little
I think Chanel and Paige are aspiring
Initiates and you know, I'm brand new as though I think but um, I think that you're definitely
Definitely come to easy's panel
Easy, what's your panel or channel name? Is it allegedly or?
Let's just put in the um, the, the, the leak later on the link in the chat for you guys to go live again.
You know what their strategy is?
Well, they, they say this won't stop until this panel is gone.
Well, I mean I've been under the I mean I've been under what are we gonna do with them to and it's like, you know what?
I believe that you I believe that good will to know it's true though. I saw her type that bullshit yesterday
I was I was actually told by another woman like that, you know
Good times and I are Jews
which is not I'm just not saying who said it but I mean it was like that was I mean and you know that
cloud back in the chat what is that avatar is that a finger with headphones or is that a dick
I'm not sure
Hey, I'm not I'm not trying to interrupt
Hey guys be quiet for what's that? It was a pleasure to meet you. Yes, likewise. Yes. Thank you
And I hope to see you around. Yeah. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Yep. Have a good night. I like any time, okay?
Have a good born talk. So thank you
Okay, I need to I'm gonna okay. I've got your I'm gonna share your channel right now. Hold on
I'm gonna push this in the chat and hey
Yo, that was a good lot. We had earlier dick put that shit back. That was funny
Okay, Alex, I'm waiting for the okay
It is it is an interesting process like the more you go through it
Like I mean I was like very uptight and worried like so much about oh my god
This person said this person said that YouTube is pretty liberal if you're on tiktok
If you're on YouTube I've had crazy ass panels with the n-word flying and all the just back and forth friends
And I mean just terrible things and just wackiness and then it's like and it's fine
I mean it's like I once you're monetized. I think it's maybe different, but I don't like
So I don't really have the
advertiser concerns and so it's
not to I've just been a I don't
know how I've been able to
survive with all the attacks
just group after group after
group ganging up and
on that note I can really
when I first came to Japan
one year ago I think it's also
anyone has any you got the
I would say that anyone has any motherfucking groups against each other at this age. It's right
I'm not perfect and none of us are. I mean, that's the whole thing. None of us are perfect and
I always say if you won't let you drop as a service
Not jesus christ go get whatever god you believe in and tell him you are perfect
Right. Yeah, exactly. And it's like, and then you'll just get laughed at because we all have our our our own like, you know
Journey and our in our own process and our own less lessons to learn that's the part
That's the part of being a person is that we can like you actually learn these lessons in a 3d
Shame us
People do mistakes in life. Even you me Alex
We all did mistakes on YouTube, but they're not trying to forget it. They're trying to only shame you
they're not trying to let you learn and I apologize and then it's like well you're not sincere or
your apology means nothing or it's like and it's like so it gets stuck to work when they do that
right to you because you are sincere you know you are yes thank you put yourself in the middle
Yeah, I'll put myself in there and also like I'm still willing to forgive people
I was I told somebody today
We know we all know who this woman is like, you know
That has a champ like a popular channel. I said, you know what it's like, you know this YouTube stuff
I think I think we're taking we take it way too seriously
I would like even if it was like the same arguments and stuff
I would love to be able to be hide in the scenes just be able to clink a glass together and say hey
You know this it's all in fun and we I mean it's like but there's like
this bitch of y'all that takes it offline and it burns it and it gets so nasty.
And it's like, and then there's like, well, I played the victim.
Well, I mean, it's like, I am like, I have pretty much that's what I said yesterday.
Right.
I mean, I don't know how I started talking to Christine in the chat and her
fucking, she made a comment and I like answered to it and she gave me a heart
and it spiraled from there.
I was like go live and she went live for me. She even named it Alex
You got ten minutes to get up here some bullshit and then bronze came up and I was talking to them and it was basically about Ronys
don't think they made no sense to me so basically she just wants to be left alone
i'm like he left you alone and they kept blaming you for everything i told you i'm like you
took down everything oh how they hit sport from hosting what is it his sport from being him
is it his that's what i guess bro you gotta go watch it i was like the guy just came on youtube
They just were saying a bronze bird is ridiculous. Everything he said was stupid. You made an enemy of yourself
He did like say hey
Or no, I want to draw a panel instead and it was like 80% people said no
I want to draw a panel that and I like I just like I was like, oh, I was like my heart was like
It's it's hard. I'm sure the people if I put a poll like that up for me. I get so many dislikes
I don't know. It's like I
It's not but I
I got you look listen to me listen to me page go to just good. Oh, she said by
So long as I told him he took your shit
and I'm like a bro, he took everything else.
No one told us nothing, okay, so I don't want to relax.
And Christine was like, why would he do that?
And I said it, go ahead, see your teacher.
Go to sounds, go to the little arrow next to the mic,
go up, put the speaker, then go back to default.
It should take away the echo.
Settings, then audio.
And then it's going to be on D4 and be under it. There's two different options. No echo. No echo
sometimes
Hit the buttons a couple times like the the options like there's like sound cancellation noise reduction hit them a couple times sometimes
There's it up. No, no, this is the secret you hit settings you go to audio right away
It's on default underneath that is a speakerphone and some other shit
You hit any of those and then go hit default again bring it back to default and it fixes it
Yeah
for some reason. Every time. Yeah, there you go. Oh, she's blonde and smart. Yeah, that
actually fits. That sounds a lot better. It does sound better. Thank you.
Okay, um Alex was protecting me like like a pit bull. Yeah, and I that's why you know
I love Alex and it's like, you know, and it's like I'm almost making me realize
They were like, why did he take it down? I'm like because you can't strike some that's not there motherfuckers
He's been getting strike every day and she was like, I knew it like ha ha like they gotta go to plan B now
Yeah
What you doing there?
What do you mean I still hear about who's doing all the crabs look at her. She does pages this beautiful jewelry
She was showing it earlier. She uses bullets and stuff like that. It's like so bad ass
But then with a good
Like I want to show my gun now
I'm like no no no she's so her earrings and you're trying to pull out a gun and I mean it's like good times
No, I'm not supposed to go live
I went to the ammunition shells, so that would make sense.
Yeah, the shells.
You can show where you're going.
He is literally a bullshithful point of the camera.
The other night, Greener Glow was pointing at his head.
And it's like the evil.
It's like, I'll put it on full screen.
Do you guys remember the eight ball that you used to shake?
Yeah.
I'm making cards.
That was the best.
Oh, she's making an eight ball deck.
That's so cool.
That's beautiful, creative.
Like, just like, don't be foolish.
I don't know.
Paige is awesome.
She's multi-talented, smart.
Multi-talented.
She does all the arts and crafts.
Let's continue.
Come on.
Somebody's got feedback man.
Are you ready?
I have all the stuff.
Got better Alex?
Oh shit
Like take me off me take me off mom. Hold on a second. Oh, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I hate it
I hate it so much. Thank you. I don't even show your jewelry inside because it's hard to see you
I know I do I don't want to do what I'm up there like that. So I just get I'm sorry
I was looking at your microphone and stuff like trying to
Don't be sorry I wig out
You're fine. I think it's you rolling exactly because I
Let's check it. Let's check it out. Everybody just by talking. Hi. I
I don't know you
You do it. I'll mute me. Oh, hello and testing one two three am I echoing? Hello, Joni. Yeah, it is page
Do you want to like we're having just is it me bro?
It's me you guys
Whatever we can go I can stop it through it. Let's just yeah, it's not terrible. It's not terrible
That's my jams that's my feel good song
I feel good. I feel good.
With a door. Yeah. I was looking
at his back and I'm like, yo, I'm
going to put it that I'm in
Paris. Come here. It's all
around. I think it's you
actually. I'm a double check
right now. I think it is.
Me real quick, and fiddle with your settings quack, I think.
Oh.
Is that it?
Fingertip settings?
Yo, you're a dick. I didn't see the allegedly panel. Oh my god
I was told being called Lili and there's this this the storyline that you know
That I'm stalking women or something like that and I was told by somebody I used to be great friends with stay away from DJ
Electra for a second
What's that?
Quack, can you...
Oh, it was him.
It was him, right? Told you.
Oh, I think maybe both...
I don't know. It's still kind of got a little it's all of us. Can we just hold hands and fucking?
Energy here so high right now. There's a little bit of electric electric, you know, but that's like we can we can deal with you?
I could be that honest and
More as a CB radio. It's a 10. You're magic. How does it feel in a room full of true psychics?
Like a room full like 50 more and y'all got the energy going on like shit-making projects
Ronie's is with his cat in Rome like
Psychic a was that shit's called when they have like
Yeah, so I okay, so this is a funny story
So there is a psychic named Kenny Kingston and Kenny Kingston is a like he used to I mean
He was a well-known
Chandler of the of the you actually dead celebrities like you channel Lucille ball and like Judy Garland
He had a book called I like a little spirit speaks
or he's no sweet spirit or he would say sweet spirit and later in life he got like one of
those 900 lines or whatever but he used to go on K-Rock with like Adam Carolla and Dr.
Drew and stuff and I was like 12, 13 years old listening to this show and he's like
they're like he's like we're having a psychic convention in the Canoga Park Bowl and I was
thinking it'd be like this Coliseum behind me like this arena called like like a football
Place and so I was like I was like in the whole convention of like 50 psychics and I was so excited until my brother
let's go there and
We're looking for this like big arena in Kenoga Park, and it was a bowling alley
And we went in and then my brother, we had to draw from my hat, the name of the psychic
that we would get and I drew a certain psychic and my brother drew him, who I was like, I
wanted the reading from.
So my brother just gave me, we did a switcheroo and then-
What a good draw, man.
Like my brother went to like this lady that read his jewelry. She like or actually kind of Kingston actually like I remember I
Ripped off a button. What he said give me jewelry. I had no jewelry
So I just ripped off a button off my shirt and he's like who's this button and he's like you're gonna be
Behind the camera someday and you're gonna be and it's like
Now remembering
And this was never like on my like I was I always wanted to be like an actor or something
I was younger, but it's like now that I'm like actually behind a camera and actually and he's like you're gonna be
Successful and you're gonna help a lot of people
I mean it's like and I think just I just gonna chills because it's like now
I'm remembering that reading and I know I was like always skeptical a little bit of it
And then it's like happening
They read the future actually he was a good
He felt something
Anything you'll be behind the camera
I think the book is called spirit speaks or something you have to look up Kenny King sinning as a book where he like goes to like the beach right here
I guess it's called
Like either redonda beach or the rat beach next to it, which is right where I lived and he went into
It's called right because I live by
Stands for right after torrent
Oh, wow.
We got on a beach, a torrents beach, and then Ratt Beach.
And Ratt Beach was like, it actually
has these beautiful, beautiful, you know, path down to it.
It was like, my school was like right on there.
And a beautiful ocean, we had oceanography and stuff.
At high school, we'd be able to go down to the beach and stuff.
It was a, I was very blessed.
And, but, yeah, but check out Skinny Kingston's.
Is that your older brother or younger brother
that gave you the ticket?
That was my old my he was ten. He's like ten years older than me and he drove me out there and I was like his little
I was like he was in his 20s, and I think he was like
And I think we got much of the right people that night because the lady
What's that? I was like I was like 12 or 13
223, you know
I thought it was like 50 years ago
12 as well. Like I said, I was really into like the occult and psychics and
Tarot and all this stuff and I was very very young and it's like people say oh now he's lying
He's lying. Blah blah. His tears all bullshit blah blah, and it's like so night. That's why I don't
If not someone asked me I don't really even pull the cards out because I've just been like
Denigrate is so hard over it and stuff and I respect my gift and that's not too
Just like you know give it to people who that don't care. That's the purpose. All right. Yeah, so if as long as like, you know
It's like ass of me
I will, and I, like I said, I do like 95%, 95% of people agree.
And I'm happy to, and 95% of the time,
person loves it, like the people love it.
And, you know, and I think I'm also improving.
I mean, I think the tarot is a lifelong study.
There's always more you can learn,
just like with astrology.
These are really like so complex,
and the symbology and everything is so complex,
live forever, or live like 100 years, and still we know the line.
I'm sorry.
Is that a squirrel asshole on the target?
Oh, that's YouTube.
Oh, YouTube, YouTube 2.0.
Yeah.
I'm sorry to cut you off.
No, I think it is Northwoods, by the way.
I think you're right.
It is Northwoods.
And Crunkle.
I've been, I've been, I've been talking to my friends.
Oh my god
Practice well, I like target practice on the target
Shit, let me see the arrow boy any man
That's too much for you tonight. Oh
Joni the cat found a June bug. How can a June bug come out in April? He was on his back
Oh, no, those stink bugs are gross
You know, they look so gross and she could teach you
Oh, she free the stink bug see somebody else is known for killing baby spiders in the community and
You better stop there stop it stop it Roni stop it, but Joni free the stink bug and you know, that's maybe
A lesson is like even if you're a fucking little crazy this morning mean to you man
You were trying you were up there alone. I was like, this is so awesome
I told you they'd be friends again
And then she went sideways and then I remember telling you the other day like I think it might be over with that bitch, right?
She's I don't know. I don't think there's I mean it's like if somebody won't accept an apology if somebody will keep
Man the way she talks like
I've tried for like over a year
And it's like it's just at this point. It's getting to her toxic
I think it's just time to part ways and you know, like
I don't think I'm gonna ever be
Accepted or forgiven. And so if I'm always thinking for forgiveness, it seems that way
You know
Not just to beat your ass down, you know, it's not really for like forgiveness and let's try to heal it
That's like yelling. Yeah
Yeah
Rooney, yeah, Johnny Johnny Johnny's like a Johnny and Rooney, you know
Is that funny, I never noticed that Johnny and Rooney and also hey, we have oh, we have
Pager onies Johnny
Tommy James, this is the Johnny James talking about my page
Yeah, oh my god, and don't tell me he's not yo Tommy
I'm not gonna say shit, bro
Okay, cuz I saw this morning's panel with beta and man you must have been a little tired my brother
Let's just leave it at that. But good to see you good to see you. I'm sorry about for coming at you all the time
So hard. I don't know why I don't barely know this guy
He has a good mic I think I can't hear me
He's muted
You think that is come on P and tell me no you're a little muffled. I mean is this like
Somebody's got to fix that feedback. We can't keep it going like this if we all have to drop and come back
But I think it's psyche man
I'm gonna mute. I'll mute here. Everybody that's not talking just mute one at a time
Hello, hello Tommy's good psyche black is good page
She has ghosts in her in her machine and electrical interferes
Yeah, if you just mute page and that and then when you talk you you know come on because it's like then it should be okay
Hello. Hello. Hello. Oh my gosh. Yeah, it's gone
Yeah, he's looking like Cartman right now. Come on, bro
Tell me I was just a little disappointed like cuz like I felt like you we had a good
Chemistry last night in a way, and I felt like I had fun and you're fun
And then I said hey, I think I was like I was cool with Tommy Tommy was cool with me
And then it turned into oh psych things
He's my friend now, and it's like and then you just had this like detestable kind of thing
for sure. I mean, I don't think we're best friends. I didn't say we're best friends.
I said, I said, I was cool with him. I said, I had respect for him as a, as a person I
never, I never said, but you just kind of went so mean to me.
I didn't mean to hurt your feelings, psyche. I feel like I'm being cordial with you like
right now. We're just being cordial. And you'll talk shit about me tomorrow somewhere, right?
Well, I was right to your face. So I don't think it was you weren't right to my face because I was just listening
Donald's on the phone. I know later in the show. I came talk to you but earlier when you came on
You just her her word for she's because like oh well Tommy thinks that oh
Psychic things that Tommy's cool with him and stuff and that your friends now
And then she's like put it in the way that I didn't put it, right? And then if you
Came back is like well, I
basically hate Psyche and he's
he's bull shit and I corrected
it was like look we're not friends
and I think Psyche is a terrible
person which I did say that and I
do stand on that and that's why I
couldn't have you on my show then
okay
I'd rather then Alex come in like get the fuck off the box. That's when I come in hot brother. Yeah, I do it
Turn up Alex is about to turn up in my head. That's the quiet
Go for it go for it Alex
We don't have to yell or
Freak out we can all left you in the lines. Then my fat feather friends
Alex let's get this back rabbit now rabbit season. It's fucking crackhead season. Did you see this guy nodding out all morning?
Let's put some crack on the fucking bag
You're feeling good now though. You're looking in better. You got a little it
Yeah, but that's cool, man. I had a friend like that that used to crush up oxy kinds and sniff them
Tommy now that I think about was there like a real reason that like shave your mustache like Hitler on Passover?
Okay, nope
Nope, bro. We were just starting. Okay. I was just
I don't want that on my show we said yeah, he said I hate
But it's cool because you're erasing the panels now
And he was doing like a very inappropriate
Things and it's like I'm ashamed that I even platformed him and and I'm the terrible person, right?
I
Oh, no, get the fuck out of here with that shit.
That's why it's you.
No.
That's why.
That's why it's you.
it's a possibility always a possibility well you know what Daniel survived the lines in you didn't
because you know i'm the so much we're aligned then cooked all year easy but i got in my head
how the f*** is it? now you're giving me the lines in the chat if you want to and the chat can
The rat it rocked on brother after today what I saw. I don't even know that honestly
I just come at him cuz he's fucking talk shit about psyche comes up here
I think it's my friend and then next day he's talking shit about him
So that's why I don't like him, but this morning. I saw the true Tommy James
Notting out on drugs making weird faces like it was the weirdest
Those are
Real drug addicts right there
Yeah, I'm a drug addict. Not even off on camera taking what I got. I was amending it. I was like, what am I watching?
You were there, but you was like fighting with Vito, but I got punched him on the
And he was just but the thing is he was I said I didn't say
I we were we were cool with each other. I said
Well, what I'll say is that you're a you're a two-faced and I will agree with that
And I don't deal with dealing with either of his bases right now that little fucking orange hair. I so
Beijing come back, baby
What's up with that whistle Alex? Oh no, no, I think Johnny was saying goodbye to him, but I hope she doesn't leave
Yeah, I hope he I hope she was by to him. Don't worry about Jody. Yeah, that was a good bite of him because I
Hate for that. Let's pull a card for card like we used to the shop to come. Yeah, we're gonna drop the drama combo
But I think you know, I want to I wanted to that fuck just woke up after his nodding all day long
He probably slept just woke up smoked up along. He's feeling good. He came up to be a dick
He just took a hit nigga. He took a crack at message. Well, he said
What's his drug choice?
Well, he was
Kind or heroin brother nothing makes you not like that besides those two things
opiates
It's like I bought me a purchase ahead. I
Mean, it's like he I'd like I was
I believe in giving people the right but it's like when they're
Going as far as like shaving Hitler mustaches and doing not I'm not gonna platform that and that's
final
Was that guy had a red face one time he had red face and I'm like, yo, he's he's a racist
You got long hair that is just talking shit like a loser
Okay, and crying come on loser
Come on stop the game up
Alex do not see salutes and never saw Alex like it really about
Racial and stuff like that and Alex has never been such an act like
It's like it's like the difference between a harmful person and then it's a negative energy and even it even Alex
Alex and sometimes get a little bit amped up and we all I can get amped up and bear
But it's like at the same time. There was a guilty story. I don't like that. I don't like that
Come up here and say that we can't we can't read all this all day, bro. We have a conversation
I'm here to talk shit with my boys, but I'll not read some dumb
If you want to really talk, it's not that serious thing, just get it off your chest
Like he's a little pussy, he's a keyboard warrior now
Can we get, he's scared to come up
Well, hold on Paige, Paige says something
Give me with the dolphin though
I can't even do that shit
It's Paige, it's Paige in the building, it's Paige, Paige are you here?
She's here
Paige, Paigey
That's why you do it. I'll get you now. Hey, honestly, I was like purely
People it is like on a stick where the labyrinth card
We need oh the labyrinth that
Yeah, we need some good reading page you get up here, man. We need your good energy after that
That devil that just left you gonna come up here. She's gonna bring the sage with her
I walk past the whole sage counter the other day downtown
And you thought about it on the street right after psyche ended it psyche right after you ended it you missed it
I walked right past the sage like uh right in the streets. They had a bunch of sage material and stuff like that
Yeah, I was gonna show y'all like y'all this nigga just ended it
Take about page you won't go. Yeah, I thought about page two. I wish I could show you page
I thought about the whole thing. I'm like, yo the sage once I saw the stage. I'm like, oh look at them
They popped in my head
Love sage for market. It's best you get to go. It's kind of like touch not touch everything
Yeah, part of me. She's not she's not a dog. They're asking why I'm whistling to your door. Oh, sorry. Sorry. That's
You said it I didn't even know what you said that
Yeah, we are too bad. We don't do that.
Alright, sorry, baby.
A dog. Not a kid.
That's way disrespectful if you know what I'm saying.
The dolphin thing is still cool, just no whistling like you're a dog.
I can totally handle you guys, it's funny.
But like, don't fucking whistle at me ever again.
Okay.
Shit.
God, he's hot when she gets upset.
No, it's not hot.
Well, it's kind of good.
Bermain Labouche boys. Anyway, Psyche, what are we doing here?
Get that stage going, girl! My arm is waving. I got my hands up in the air, like I just don't care.
I was like, what's that she's like that they're like a little bit like they had like the suit of vegetables
I mean, it's like and it's like sometimes it's like I have to like kind of like
Correspond to you because it's like, you know, every deck is different and things like that
But um, I also like um, but I also do like this book like some people will be like, oh my gosh
If you use the book like there's something wrong with you. Sometimes the book has great
Yeah
It has the authors, what they, how they would say it.
They interpret it with the spelling.
Yeah.
I mean, I'm an interpretation of it.
Hey, do you about to make your own damn book for your damn thing?
My dad?
Yeah.
I know.
Yeah, that may both still it's very construction worker of you. Yeah, exactly. I'm a construction worker at the heart
Alex that's my whistle Alex. I'm a corporate
That car for cars. Oh, I love that. Oh
Okay, so okay, this one is one that I have not showed you yet. This is like the Russian. It's like a it's a
It's a fortune-telling card. So it actually comes in like
Form of pictures that you have to put together and then there's symbols and direction
Oh, like pointing it's like it's a whole thing, but it's really cool
We'll do it one day
But I do have a new deck that I'll use with the cards. What are you using?
I have the labyrinth deck today.
This is like the, um, this is the opposite of that.
Try whatever you try to get.
Try to get opposite of labyrinth.
You don't like the labyrinth deck?
No, no, no.
We like it.
I'm telling Paige get the opposite.
Okay, you know like one one reading to the other. Yeah
And I will have like if you I mean maybe if you're like a fan of Labyrinth you'll enjoy it more
But I think the artist is pretty beautiful. I think it was
designed by this art by Thomas Kejo. I believe it says discover the Labyrinth
With the initial terror that gets fired by Jim Henson's whole classic
And original illustrations, this also includes a Ford from Barclay and Froud,
artist and production designer from the film. This is, I guess, the approved deck of the film.
And it has some beautiful art, it has some great...
drawings based on the original art of the film and it is slightly traditional in a
certain way but then again it has vegetables that I need to maybe consult
and sometimes to see exactly because also with the thing that's not this
thing that the major arcana are very illustrated but the minor arcana are
There's not much symbology in the pits, and so I might need to be sold for the pits a
little bit.
Because they're also...
The correspondence is different.
This is a new deck for me.
I haven't worked with it too much, but Grammy requested this, and so I'll give it a shot.
We page you page I used to do this here. We used to do card for card
Jada bow is January 8th. I'm January 7th, you know, and so I
Also been told that it looked like
Labrador's their favorite lecture. Hey, what's up girl and lecture fry. I knew I liked you labrador is one of my favorites
You know, it's just talking about that movie
It's a lot of our favorite
busy
It's amazing. We got to do movie night one night and watch that
Because I'll expose me I should I should do what she does and get the quack quack like you get a lecture
You'll have funny would that be guys, you know DJ Electra has the cartoon character
Imagine easy did that as quack as the dog. He wants to do that like
You know like the electric thing as the dog will that will be funny. Yeah
What is that that's a program though what you go to Best Buy and buy that shit and now you can become a lot like a cartoon dancing around
Oh, I'm so in a field of love back again the negative energy is going away
In with the good out with the bad
Really disturbing to me and taught me a kind of off guard, but I should have done better
Hey, yeah, and say and the lecture saying hi to everybody a lecture is like really an awesome person and it's like, you know
I am, you know, when I had my problems with my channel the first time it was over some, you know, it was over
Somebody trying to you know strike over like a beautiful beautiful
Video and introductions she made for me. They struck me 11 times and with her help
And page and some other awesome people, you know, I'll say like a lot of people were in my back
on my
Side or whatever, but I was able to
Resolve that it's you and but and you know, she really did help a lot and she's a very sweet
very cool person very talented woman
to and
Friendly and kind and you know and I've got just great great friends in the chat that I'm so happy to see and I'm like
I think we have a good the good energy a better energy happening tonight, right?
So I love you guys
I love y'all I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love I love
She was super jealous of her page. I don't know cuz you're prettier than her or something
You can just see it. She was so upset when you came up
It was just her anxiety and then you popped up to hang out old paging just being normal and you can see her face
She was just other first page
Okay, read the time read the time people this is a I don't know for the people just for the people guys. Let's get it
Collective, a collectivist, we call it.
Yeah, I'll let you turn off my background so it doesn't dry out.
I'm so sorry, okay.
What I got first is, oh, it's digital, but I got it, got it, got it, okay.
But I have for, oh, Lenore, Lenore, do you want to be part of the reading too?
She came over here.
You have this beautiful queen of feathers.
I queen this with the queen of swords.
And the queen of swords, this air element, is very,
it's very smart but the queen of swords has been through some stuff and so this has made her a
strong person this has made her a much stronger person but also it's like she might have been through
a lot of sadness and things like that but I like this one this particular pixie has like this
little smile on her face and it's like kind of like using these leaves
to kind of like for protection and beautiful greenery on the best look at look at oh she has my kind of like my feet
I mean this is going to remind me of my feet uh
I kind of look like if I was to grow my hair really long I might look at your picture a little bit
But yeah, this is ready. You want to tell me speed on those leaves?
Because that's also like your legs actually it does it does
So and I'll say I'll say the queen of swords
She knows what to cut off and what to keep okay
But I will re-use their interpretation because I'm interested to see the author of the book, the next interpretation of this, and it says...
The Queen of Feathers is an intelligent, sensible,
well-respected figure who does things her own way,
uses logic and reason to come to her own conclusions
and isn't easily influenced by others.
The Queen of Feathers has the confidence to say to herself,
even in the face of conflict, criticism, or hoggle.
And so if you know hoggle, you know hoggle.
It sounds like there's a police radio up your ass or something.
Am I the only one that he's not mine. Thank you, Paige
That's wrong. And you know that'll take you away because the people would have phone
Straight to the castle, right?
I've seen that one. Hmm. Hey, Lola. I love that. I love that
Irish man with the fuck was that castle
I was in the worm that said that but it was um
Yeah, there is I think you know that have been one of the the doorway guy or something like that
Hey, this is miss Lola. Can we play with pages new cards?
Or like I don't know if she's like
Okay, is the phone on something which is making the sound
Are the ways I'm fixing it fixing it
Relax boy. It was the it was the worm. Hello. It was the worm.
People to speak and come back to people. I just remember the worm. Oh shit. You remember the worm?
That was the worm. Okay. I was thinking it was the worm but then I was getting confused with Scottish dog guy.
I think I got it right.
Did it fix? Yeah, I know it was the hog. I didn't say it was hog. Oh my god. I think...
It's not fixed. It's okay
It's gonna make us close the watch it's all hidden blessings
Page your only I'm trying to fix it. Did that help at all?
Say that again did that help you fixed it. Oh my god
Yeah
Okay
Holy shit, she fixed it. Are you stoked or you just this is the biggest day. Whatever you did remember that
Oh, it's you quack
He drops easy to come back probably. Hey, okay. It was him. See oh your queen
You pulled the queen of swords, right? The queen of feathers if you will
Just from like, you know, obviously, you know the picture and the beautiful picture in that card
That's a beautiful card. I love how that it's a queen of feathers, but
Feathers represent, you know, in so many different cultures and or like whatever you want like spirituality as well
If you can combine that with what the Queen of Sorrows also like you explained in Terrapin
It's like all about the intellectual and emotional balance
So you have somebody who's very much been through an emotional journey and an intellectual journey
And she's earned that seat that right to sit there with those feathers like she knows what she wants
That's why she can cut
what the fuck ever else does it serve her off so easily is because she knows it's the knowing right
that's connected to the swords so um i'll just okay first of all these cards are called the arc
angel or book cards by durian virtue um i don't use them very often so also another deck that's not
here very much that you haven't seen so i'll clarify or pull a card on that for the collective as well
okay so just right off the get go though i'm feeling like okay
Who there's somebody that's in here that's gonna go through a mate like not a major surgery
It might be a minor surgery
But there's somebody or someone that they are connected to that they're quite worried about I want you to know that
That's gonna be okay. That's a huge
I don't know why that's coming out, but I had to say it to you so there you go
Okay, then we have teaching and learning
Coming up with the Queen of Swords, she's the person who knows all. She's been through the
experiences like Psyche and I just explained. Therefore, she has the knowledge to teach. She
has the teaching and the learning down pat, right? So keeping an open mind and learning new ideas
you're knowing your mind, you're listening to yourself, you're listening very intellectually
intelligent, you're very emotionally balanced, and I feel like you're now using that to a different
advantage as to have to teach others and guide them to a different place so they don't have to
go through the same experiences quite as harshly as you did, whether that be children or whatever
you want to call it. Is anybody that wants to learn that you're guiding? That's kind of what I
Yeah. Well, my next card is a card. You see, this is a page of polls, which I guess is
a page of wands. And this card, you know, he's holding magic. Oh, this wand, this pole.
There is like this live, live feature. Usually there's some, you know, wands are the fire
And this might be whispering some interesting information to him or something, but he's also grabbing that hole down there or like a chariot or something.
You know what it was? It was all three of you assholes. All three of you dicks it was. That's why we can't figure out what it is. Now it's Psyche's turn to go to audio.
I basically think of this page of wands. It's like, yeah, this is like kind of like one of these things.
one of the goblin army of jareth right and it's like this is like
He's still finding his power
He is still I mean it's like in looking for which one or which one to take power from the higher
He is one of the lower one on the higher and so, you know
But I would say this is the potential there's a potential there to grow into something powerful
And it's like holding this like what like or these two ones, right?
The goblins weren't just the smartest beings in the movie, they're kind of silly and things
like that.
But in the page is also this younger energy too.
And so it just reminds us that there's always more to learn, there's always more to do.
We don't know everything there is to know.
And then it's like we also have maybe a war inside of all of us of this higher and lower
We decided to pursue and listen to it.
And there's also, it's interesting, the carrot and the stick also in this,
there's something called the carrot and the stick, where it's like,
if you were trying to, like, move a donkey, you throw the donkey with a stick and
there's like a fishing line with the carrot on it.
And the donkey keeps walking for the carrot and the stick.
Yeah, you can shoot it, but never touches it.
Yeah, exactly.
There's a carrot and a stick.
And so that's kind of like, maybe like, not like walking a lot, but really like,
or,
You can pull your lower self along you which made me the donkey and you can like pull it pull it forward
With this with his hair it
But the donkey we can never really catch it. No, and so there's just something to think about is like
We can like the page is usually like I'm like a fucking crack it always looking for that next high and you can't ever find it
Like Tommy James exactly you got it
Listen you guys first rule of respect of being a reader in reading is to not do what you just did and you know it
You don't well what first rule being my panels. You don't do not this is loose with a Hitler mustache on Passover. Okay
Are you gonna be petty or are you gonna be? Oh my god? That's right. It's Easter
Oh
Seriously or does remind me of him
Even questioning it means
Don't tell me that was cool. Oh
The guy just did a Nazi fucking salute. That's you like that. What are you talking about the Nazi salute specifically Alexander?
I was talking about the fact that they even there
What he just did was petty and what whatever James, you know, Tommy James did to him obviously was you know
Petty is equality. Don't don't don't do what no hold on. But what did he do? That was petty
I didn't catch the petty part from sight. Oh, I miss that
They're all together man
It's simple.
Well, he comes on my piano.
You just came up with a festival.
Stop talking.
I'm talking.
You also go to other people's panels, too.
I'm just saying.
God, she's hot.
And I'll respect people to wear it as much as they
will respect me, you know?
It's not so much about the actions.
It's about the fact that you're both entertaining it.
It's the thing I'm trying to say.
Well, you know page well
Well, I mean, it's like I think if something just happened and then I pulled that card
Maybe there is something to think about as this correlation of this immature
Energy that he said knows everything that is just operating from his lower self
You should have said that then specifically people's names. Well, but I do but oh my gosh
But yeah
And who the fuck is Bakelips? Because I looked at his vinyl and he said there are no rules, there are no rules, you know.
Respect a lot of reference to McQueen and Bakelips shit.
Pardon me?
Oh, Bakelips. Who's that? Anybody know? Bakelips.
Respectfully. When we're in connection with Divine Spirit and doing a reading or providing so, it is important to not...
You you don't cross lines like that. Also, you don't bring specifics into names like when it comes to people
That's not that's because you never had a problem with him whenever you didn't you kept saying oh bring him back up bring him back
I'm sorry because he was trying to talk to you guys
I don't even know the guy I was just saying respectfully as a fucking human being it's hard to talk and say what you have to say
When you're trying to talk and no one will let you and then you start to be pay because you're triggered
I get where it was coming from though is all
But yeah, it actually did remind me of him and I said it. Yeah, that's fair
That's fair, but then now you're gonna have retaliation for that of some sort
I imagine like I'm just saying it comes with consequences
Okay, that's fair nice now you're talking like a man my friend
There acknowledge gay or not
All right
Okay, so what did we have there? We had the night of wands, correct?
That was a page of wands. Page of wands, okay
So yeah, like a prematurely thought offer or something but with lots of drive and passion
So it crashes and fails because it's quick and hot, but it's not the plan wasn't
Planned out well if that makes any sense. Sometimes that goes with that card in general. So
Alright, I'm taking that one. I'm taking that one. Okay, so we have a healthy lifestyle
So, you know, I guess like maybe making sense of this card with that
It's like, okay, so eat a healthy diet. So living a healthier lifestyle a healthy mindset a healthier
aspect or application to whatever the fuck it is of this like littler offer so you can
grow something into something bigger and more profitable and or beneficial to you in some
sort of way whether it nourishes your mind body or soul or it does on the exterior as well
but like combining the two of these cards it's like okay I know that I can do this but it needs
a little bit of work so whatever it is keep working at it but also you know keep in mind that
it's easy to lose sight of your goals and get sidetracked when there is um something isn't
kind of like if it doesn't have everything you're looking for in desire in a desirable sense where
you're like oh i can connect with that i have the passion i have the drive you do have it but maybe
the offer that you're being given don't feel so much pressure to make a decision if it's not something
for you even though it's what might seem for you it might not be and that's okay
work on it some more and just maybe ponder within yourself and say hey what am I willing to invest
to this smaller offer even though there isn't a bigger one yet it still could be in the horizon
if you know what I mean yeah that's what I get from it but you can perceive it or apply it to whatever
resonates to you.
Okay
Fucking quiet. Don't be weird you guys
You guys will make amazing lawyers honestly when I hear you like do these card readings the way you talk and
Express yourself so like articulate like you'll be great in a courtroom and you guys will whoop ass
Family says that to me all the time
Well, I told you see
I got it. I pulled another page and this is the
This is a junk lady the page of junk and I guess this would be the page of pentacles and the page of pentacles is often a part of
The other person holding a pentacle and they've been given something but sometimes they've been given something
Yeah, yeah, sometimes but sometimes, you know, you remember the Junkley is one of my favorite scenes in all of labyrinth
You know and he will tell Sarah. Oh, here's mr. Bear remember this remember this and then
And it's like, these things, these material things that we are sometimes focused on, and
sometimes younger people, it is easy to entice them with these material things.
But we have to remember that ultimately anything material is ultimately just our bodies.
Just like our bodies.
Our bodies in a car will grow older, fairer down, become, you know, and it's like the
real importance in this spirit, okay?
Since this is a this is a character from the movie. I'd like to see what the book has to say about it
So I will look at fight. I would write to the page
It says like the fledgling junk collector goblin the page of junk represents someone
He's just starting out on a journey that has the potential be very lucrative
May find yourself feeling inspired to start a new business venture
Learning your skill or make an important change in how you manage your finances. Don't discount your ideas
as being too ambitious and too big.
Okay, there we go.
It's like they're still growing to do
and it can grow into something that's huge.
But just remember to focus on the important things
and not the...
Yeah, that's a good way to put it psych. Just don't remember to they don't don't forget that also you're important as well
Like you're part of the important things because if you're not nourished and you don't nourish yourself
How in the fuck can you be your full self for others that?
Empty cup cannot fill other cups, you know
But y'all know that anyway, don't you?
All right
this is oh goodness okay well okay I've got three here I done and they're quick
so I won't I won't elaborate a bunch on them but apparently it's necessary oh
wait yeah three apparently it's necessary we do have case so that being said you
know like I mean questioning
Like I said before and in correlation with this card that you just pulled it's like well. What am I offering?
What is my worst like what is the worst not even about that?
Don't just don't forget about yourself because what are you being offered like?
What is the value of what you're being offered and what?
Do you think that that is adequate to what you're you're worth to yourself and hopefully it is like if it's if it's a large
Extravagant offer. I hope that you know that that's made because you are you should feel large and extravagant yourself
Like in the sense of on the inside out, right? We have hello heaven
So if there's anybody which I know that there is because there's people standing here in bedroom with me hello from heaven, okay?
I know what it's like to miss a loved one we all do, especially if it's like, let's say, said parent,
grandparent, father, you know what I mean, like somebody who's an immediate, I guess,
an immediate love of a greater kind to you in your heart. And I feel like, you know, your loved
ones are always with you, so...
Know that when we're down, you know, I miss my mom when I'm sad psych misses his dad when he's you know
I mean all the stuff we all miss our people
Just know that they're not as far away as you think okay, and I know that that's very t-shirt cliche shit to say
But fuck it accept it it is what it is because that's the reality of it
It's simple as that and then we have creative writing so
I love this because whatever maybe your building is small now and you don't see the greater
outcome, it might be more than, the outcome could be more than you ever imagined.
And just like you putting yourself into something is also your self expression with creativity
is also going to go along with the correlation of the teaching and the learning.
You know, you're creating something for others to learn off of because of the experiences
Everything you went through and that you do to this current date like right the second right this will impact you somehow in a weird way
You never know you just never know so be open-minded and prioritize the things that you are doing
So prioritize your passion prioritize that the energy you're gonna put into certain
categories of what you're trying to build and what is going to assist you in your most I guess highest self
Like left-hand man be yourself be your own fucking help right like just look look to your own
Follow your own fucking advice follow your own knowledge and like other people's opinions dude
If they're gonna put you down or they're gonna make the offer suck small or dim your light
Essentially make anything you're building small
Tell them to fuck off and cut them out of your life like the Queen of Swords would because like there's no more room for that
It's time for you to grow. There's no need to feel any other way other than excited for it. Okay, so that's my love for you for that card
My next card is right in there
You are really funny how I
I just said something about the camp the full cup in the empty cup because I got this
two of cups and it's like, you know the two of cups is
You know, and this can go a little bit into that, but it looks like when you do, when you do a full cup, you are able to pour it to others.
Yeah, you brought it up earlier. It's beautiful. You brought it. It's core. It's clarifying what you said. I love it.
I love that too. And I think that this is like, when you do have a full cup, it can be
You can get the others too right and it's like and it can be like a beautiful partnership
And it's like and then you can both pour into each other and you can you know alchemize it
It's like you know like two of the two of us is usually like these two people doing
the beginning or
process of a beautiful relationship that has the potential to grow into something more amusing
Maybe in our lives we met somebody, we met a special friend, and we're able to learn from each other, help each other, love each other, and work together to make sure that we both have some water in our cup.
And I think that's a good way to play football.
You feed the source and the source feeds you so if you're upset with how things are going or the energy
Frequency or or vibe in your life, and it's time to start putting out different thoughts different intentions
Different different vibes yourself because we feed the source and the source feeds us so if it's all negative shit
the universe only knows one answer and it's yes so if you're manifesting negative things about
yourself and what you expect for your life or what you envision I suppose would be another word
for it then you know it's gonna say yes it's gonna give you that if you also can do it with the
other opposite way which is manifesting positive things for yourself which is almost tricking
yourself and lying to yourself in a way saying I already have this I already believe I have it
I'm not that great at it, but you might be. So give it a go.
Wow. Um, I'm listening to this is a card. Um, right. Um, you know, okay. So this is the, uh,
this is an interesting card. This is a demon. Okay. And this is a fire spirit. And the demon is
traditionally, I guess would be the devil card number 15 in the terror deck. And he's got these
in their lower self, but he's kind of ruling over them.
And this is about controlling our passions.
I mean, maybe we're being controlled by our passions.
Maybe we're being controlled by our lower self.
Maybe we're based sometimes on our enslaved to ourselves.
And this is even the way he's sitting.
It's like a very bath, a bathymetic.
There's fire, and you can end up
in our own personal hells when you do this.
like me being a capricorn, like right in the middle of capricorn, you know, I'm familiar with my lower self and I've, wow, I've dealt with, I've dealt a lot with it and so that could easily remain, they stay in my lower self, but the point of this is to realize that maybe we are stuck in our, our lower mind, our materialism.
This is like basically almost really a part of being enslaved to the lower state.
And we can also make a decision to master it and part of that, I think, is the devil
wants to improve.
and then he can then then he can finally grow up because they're just
the devil as a devil is that's what I'm getting
I'm just I know that you probably think it's unusual
I'm looking through this deck because I know that you try to explain I just want them to see the
Comparisons that you're telling them like so that they can see it in their mind as well like of like kind of what this is the
Modern witch tarot, but it still has like the same rider weight ask like cuz his is more you know like in the
It's more personal like to that person you made it, right?
It's like the the graphics and everything this is the devil in like the normal form as he is explained with the chains and everything and
Then the two of cups is like this is like he said they're just kind of filling each other's cups, right?
So just an example so that you can visually see
I think that that's, I mean, honestly, I love that we're doing this because every time we do it, even though we're a million miles apart, a million fucking light years apart, really, from all of you.
No, you're only one plane right away. Look at my picture. That's the Air Canada plane that crashed the other day. Air Canada. One hour away.
But we're all that picture by the way from inside the hangar when once they took it off the runway
That's from my phone. You can't find that anywhere
No, Google no news nothing. That's from my phone click
Well, you know what then we'll just take a moment to maybe like stay a quick, you know
prayer to for the people and the families that
Only the pilots died the pilots died and they didn't find the bodies though. She's disintegrated into thin air
They didn't find the bodies
That's I mean those that are involved in their families like that's fucking crazy
It's sad and it's also like falls almost out of the conspiracy theory is in a sense of the disappearance
The firefighters in the truck didn't die. That's insane
Because they were not in the front of the truck.
They were like in the back of it, in the middle of something.
That's what saved their life.
So very weird.
Very weird that life is weird, right?
What are the chances, like, to put those things together
at that moment to make that happen?
A plane and a stupid truck just happened to, like, a second
later or after would have been different?
I guess it's just when it's going to happen,
it's going to happen, right?
Life has a plane, I guess.
Right, it's like my friend Danny who was like, you know, I sense there was something like in his or that was like
just recently like recently it was so
brightening up and he was and then he was going from these
States of high love and they telling me and then also being drowned in some negativity and
You know
Then it's one night. He's like I'm gonna go to the gas station and then
Three shots in his chest later, and he's gone and it's like it's like what if he went to another gas station or just didn't
Wait because I saw his live was on that night, and I didn't go in there
So what if I had gone in there and he would have like you know
I talked for five minutes and he would have been five minutes later the guy would have left five
We can ask ourselves this question. We can drive ourselves crazy with this question. Exactly. We will drive ourselves nuts like
Yeah, life of a plan for all of us. It's already designed my depth somehow like wherever it's gonna happen or it can be avoided
It's so weird. That's where I feel like the soul
Maybe
He's right here really that's why I asked you right now
You brought him up and immediately like yeah, I don't know. I don't know. I just got goosebumps
I don't like that when they do like they always kind of do that
But he just he just he spooked me a little did you not see me look
Oh, I could spooks me a little bit because it just popped out of nowhere
You've been bringing it. Okay. I don't know how to explain to you. I don't like doing this on here psych. Okay. Okay. I
Okay, I'm gonna
I don't you guys I need to explain something to you
It's not going to be me speaking to you like it is fucking obviously my dumb little fucking voice telling you
But like it's gonna be someone else like I mean it's him. So I would like how does it feel intense?
No, I know it's weird. I don't like doing it. I like all like this. No, it's not weird
Okay, personal readings. I don't mind doing it, but they now worry. Okay, whatever. So I do appreciate. Okay. Hold on
There's a kind of ticket breath here
Okay, so first of all when they come to me, I feel what happened to them
So I feel that in my chest right now, and that's why I had to breathe big
there's I
Want it. Okay. I want to say so much to you. I want to say thank you for keeping me alive even though
I'm no longer here. I want to say to everybody
To make sure that you're
more aware of
Your surrounding everything going on around you. Don't be so stuck in
Your lifestyle to not pay attention to the the dangers that surround you is kind of what I
Want to tell you I also want
To say how much it hurts to not be able to be with the people that you love
But also that should show you that you need to respect and appreciate the people that you love
Thank you to everybody and the people that I love.
Okay, I got to disconnect from him because I don't like I'm just going through what he went through in
Thank you so much for that message Danny
And also I do have like what I was like what you were used like he's like
But the same video I think that makes a tribute to him he says he says that big in the video
Make sure you tell the people that you love that you love them and the last thing he did say to me when I was on his panel is I said I love you Danny and he's like I love you too and we really didn't really say that to each other he was like a more like a more masculine like kind of like you know he was always sometimes he teased me and ribbed me for being gay and stuff but you know at the same time like he would be like oh I'm gay for pay like he's gay for you know so we would always joke about it and stuff I feel him too I feel him too I do I do
your messages too and I feel like he's watching out for me and it's always good to have
People on your spiritual team looking out for you
But he's right man, we have to love our family and who we love like that's all that matters Danny
He's absolutely right so tomorrow or right now everybody call your loved ones give him a hug and a kiss
Because we don't know when the fuck we're gonna go.
And it's true like a few weeks before it was filming, they went to the gas station,
someone was watching and they heard him argue with some younger guys and kind of broke them.
Like a few girls.
What's with the number three?
The number three. Yeah, I mean that's uh, I was just bringing up like the trivia is number like trivia three
It's like the three is very like one is like it was said that like one
That's three times. Yeah
Three times in the chest. Yeah, um and you know he was four I think he was 41
Four minus one is three
There's other like probably
I'm a 31 don't be lying to people. Do you have a sense of humor? I don't know who this guy
Yeah, he had a great sense of humor. He was very funny. He looked like kid rock and like one time
I don't talk like this. So for him he's like nah, just don't tell him not to be fucking doc
Like I mean not doc see really out me like that like I'm tell him I'm 31. Don't be lying
I don't know if he's funny though
Yeah, and did he pull the weapon burst? I think that's still unknown. There's still some unknowns in this situation
I don't know if he had I mean there's I know that he would even shot like there's people that
Fired back at the guy that shot him and stuff and then maybe there's other things involved
I tell you what I just heard when you said that
Okay, why'd you hear my homies when you said he don't I think he's funny
But like he's he's not being funny like he's he's funny. He's like got a sense of humor like me
It's kind of like dry, but funny or like dirt. I don't know. He's very good. I don't know there's something about
He asked me if he pulled a weapon first. I'm sorry
He's like open to talk to you like he's very open. He's so open
Like it's weird for this to be like this on like here like you know, it's not weird
But like I just don't do it on here like this. Okay. So what did you want to know?
Did he pull a weapon first at this person or did he threaten this person in some way and provoke the person?
Before that. No, there was like already okay, okay?
There is already there was already like an entanglement or there was already like some bad blood is what I heard
And like because I can just see the like they show me a stream with red
It was already bad waters like red was like there was only bad blood and then they're showing me
There's you know when you see on a movie like somebody accidentally they'll go to like take they take their phone out of their pocket
And then the person that's already on edge kind of like because of what they're doing like kind of reacts and shoots you or something
Like there is something to do with that where it was a quick reaction because but there was already
There was already some sort of like community like knowing of some thing to do with this
I that's what I'm being shown because I
Like I'm seeing like
Maybe him doing something that maybe appeared to the person I brandishing a weapon or something or sightings
That person felt slightly frightened and went back to look for him or something. I'm just like
Oh my gosh, I just know that there's pieces missing and like please do not take what I say on here
This is for entertainment purposes only I suppose I have to say that when I say shit like this right because it's serious shit
But like and I'm not I'm not at anything. I don't matter. I just to see I see certain things that are
Probably missing details that I feel like I know that they'll come around, but there's something about this
That's not it will be like a cold. It's gonna go cold if there isn't
There's like two people that need to be
Present to say something for some reason that if they if they don't do that then there's gonna be no
Like I guess prosecution, right? Well, I mean there is like there was somebody that was like another streamer
That was a scroll of his I believe that was celebrating the next day
More to this there's just more to it than than just that but I think it's a community thing like I said like I don't know where he lives
I'm just saying I think it's like I see a
Like a community like kind of circle, right where it says there's something
More personal to it, but it happened to be also connected to his online presence if that makes sense in a weird way
Like they're connected somehow. I'm not gonna get into any details
I'm not giving any but that's all I can say. Okay. Thank you. Thank you. This is like, you know, I appreciate
You know, I feel I feel a spirit come as like I just like
Clare Clare audience is like, you know, I am Clare audience too, but it's like basically I feel
He's there like I feel him
What about that wasn't that was part of his passing, you know party is him passing over well done
Well done page. Can you channel if someone's still alive or dead?
I can tap into the like I can know I know what the difference between
Like my dad can can you tell me if he's still alive with that because I don't know if he's still alive with that
Okay, this is fucked up because it comes to me and we were raised but I see like a man an old man
Like connected to an oxygen tank that's in like a chair like he's not
He like like a dingy living room. I don't know if that means anything to you
But I don't think he's not he's still here, but kind of barely like how old would he be he smokes a lot
He smokes a lot
He's like diminishing because I'm just being told by the but he's diminished because like quicker than he should have
Like he's he's he's he's rotting almost because of actions or choices that he's made in this life
avoidance maybe it's another word that it keeps coming to my mind avoidance and
living avoidance like avoiding his life avoidance in what sense avoiding like I
don't know I get his like responsibilities or like just avoiding
like ascending I guess is another way to put it like avoiding ascending at all
Like the all that makes sense
Smoking not really cuz he doesn't smoke or didn't I actually haven't seen
Like I just I just put that so he's still alive basically you feel he's still he's still here
He's still around I do I had a feeling he was still alive. Actually, honestly, I know he is
I don't know this, but you know, I felt like he's still there
Alex McQueen Alex McQueen, can I get some McDonald's?
What up Q?
What's up? No, he's got you guys McDonald's loser
Alex, I do like a weird thing to say to you, but I know that you might know because I wouldn't say it
Just say it baby, please
Do you feel like he's always been kind of closer than you like you saw it?
Like he's always you always feel kind of like he's might be around
Like watching over me without me knowing kind of thing
I don't know just like you always just feel his like I just feel him like I see him like a circle like circling around
Like it's just always a presence of like, you know, he's not far
He wasn't far last time I saw him, but it's been years. So I was just I don't even know if he's alive with that
I don't see so okay, but I think I would feel it if he was gone right when you connect it to the family
Right, you would feel something. I know you know, he's not dead
Hmm
He is an easy fuck no, he's not even that far until I'm at that's what I'm saying
Do I feel that like he's not even ever been far?
Anyway
Thank you. Yeah
Oh my head's standing up she gives me goosebumps I do have something to tell you though
Like whatever you got to do like you got like they're showing me the number two
So like I'm gonna go maybe shoot like two years like just that might be his like
Okay, I got you. Holy shit. You might have two weeks too much to find them doing because it's two years
So I have two years to find them and my relationship with him before he dies basically
Yeah, that's why yeah, if he doesn't kill himself
If you like his pain, you know that I think he goes through a lot of pain mentally physically
It's a lot of like something in it. Oh, yeah. Yeah, 100% that's a fact. You're right on that
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
Yeah, oh, so what's going on today? What are you guys doing tarot cards?
He was telling a story like he was talking. I don't know if you want to get into much into it, but like I guess you're
Yeah, if you don't know about that the government program I guess it's full like
You know, young people out of school and, you know, give them a bunch of tests about remote viewing and telepathy and this kind of thing and, I mean, it's pretty interesting stuff.
I know you go a little...
Holy shit, I know it's remote viewing.
So you can close your eyes and see if there's a delusion in you.
At least for me and then they we sat there they talked about my life for 15 minutes
And then they would like oh, what what do you predict behind this card?
What's like, what do you think of this art and then you have like the headphones on like is it coming from up down and
Do that's questions like that and
They only took three of us out and then I guess back in the day. They say it was
And make all these tests on you
Oh my god man.
There is a lot of games.
There's all those fucking movies.
Movies with fucking kids for lab rats.
Well, I mean, I've heard these like...
No, they do. They do a brief pace from young
for like their projects and special super soldiers
and all types of shit.
And all that remote viewing.
I have a friend, well, the guy that like, stab me like, in the ear and stuff like that.
And look at every vote you pick up on me and say, but this kind of relates to this a little bit because...
He was like, he was arrested for actually unaliving my neighbor, he was arrested the next day, and then he unalived himself in jail.
He was on a suit, he was on watch, and we shouldn't have been able to say that he was dead.
Is this kind of funny?
He got stabbed in the ear by a mass of serial killer.
He killed his neighbor and then himself.
Tried to kill you?
No, after like a year after, a year for stabbing me,
he stabbed my neighbor in the neck and then he yelled.
Jesus, that could have been you, brother.
But I always thought that he was alive still
and that he was taken by the government to know the truth.
Because he was a killer and the government wants to let him do that and stuff like that.
He's still alive on that page.
I got like a whole list of family members I need to touch up.
If you can channel my grandma, man, she's there, but I would love to hear what she has
to say to me.
I love her so much.
She loves me so much.
The best grandma on the planet.
Is she super tiny?
She was a little chilly
I'm not like giving you my info, but like obviously I do you know professionally I do I'm a spiritual therapist and a medium
So like okay, I got it. If comment
It's not it's just like I do with everyone else comment on my videos
I'll share my email and then we'll get in touch that way and then we can have the scenes and you can do it for me personally
That'll be a good cuz
Here, you know, it's too, it's too good.
Yeah, and honestly, I don't want that either.
Exactly.
It's an expect for you and your loved ones.
Thank you.
Appreciate that.
The person that you just asked me, I don't know why, but I just see it.
I smell rot and I see a body bag.
Why is this?
You smell wrong you see bullet then you know he perhaps was was uh you talking to me?
Yeah, he'd be coming for your absence, you know
I mean he was in a jail cell. I guess you know, you know, I kind of like solid to a confinement jail cell
It's icky it's icky and that's I know that's childish. It's you like it just fuck off like it's not it's like sludge
It reminds me of like just a body bag of gooey fucking toxicity
If I was to show you a picture with that assist you or is that you don't mean you can but I don't need it
Uh, I know you don't need it, but if you would like to share it with me. I mean you can
Yeah, um, yeah, it was like there was I was kind of in this
kind of bad situation and uh, and I always kind of had a crush on this guy, um
but and he was all you know, he was
He had a good side and uh
It was very interesting.
He's in a good state of mind, and I'm like, I forgive him.
I'm the most forgiving.
I forgive him for doing that.
I like, you know, was just, I forgive him for doing that.
I like forgive him.
But, you know, then with my neighbor and stuff,
and it's like, and he was just like, you know,
it was just very, very strange.
Cause he's like, oh, I'll bring it up in a second.
He's going in person.
Yeah, and here he is. Yeah, like his energy is gross. Let's okay. Well, I don't think
I think right here
This is him like right before it happens
That's the guy to stab you in the ear
He looks like a crazy fuck you can see it in his eyes. No motherfucker is not there
His name is Ernie Ernie
So did you have a relationship with him besides the stabbing like we see your friends like
I mean, he was my friend, and it's like, and then there are several...
A neighbor? Was he a neighbor, or you guys were on the street?
He was a neighbor, a person, was a gig member, and he was a neighbor, a person that was, like, dating,
like, one of my close female friends at the time, and... but he was, like...
I mean
Oh, so that's why he stabbed you because he was jealous of your friendship with his girl
I got in between their fight one night, and I didn't you know
Also
And he was about to like push it down on me and I just stare them in the eye and like not afraid
and like he just put it down and then he chased me out the house with a knife
and then I gave him a cigarette and then he just changed the personality and then like uh
I see how strong my Rony's is he saved that girl's life and took a fucking pencil to the hero
right good job I got between them and stuff and like I can you say come off there please yeah I'm
You know what he's he's definitely he's he's he's he's a murderer. He's not good. He's fucking up. I just see so much shit, dude
I just seen so much terrible shit. Did you ever see the you ever see the movie the suicide squad?
Yeah, we all have probably that movie is basically about these people that their criminals that faked their death
But that they could work for the government because there were killers and they're so effective killing the government
He's gross man. He's so fucking gross. He's still he's still here. He won't he's lingering give you oh
He's a creep. He's a fucking creep too. He's really creepy
So he's haunting psyche still there's a negative energy from this guy around
He's got a particular hate for women and no shit
He could be the one of fucking psyche spirit up with all these ladies up here
He honestly like well with psych is also like I feel like he doesn't like no, I don't want to say that word
I don't want to say that even he's like gays and he doesn't like women. He doesn't like anything feminine at all
I mean he was like he would like
again, another person who dances underwear
And did not care but
he was like
There was times when he was so nice one time we like drove out today
like dancing on the one I'm not caring for him like just like controlling you
brother because you have a good relationship with his mother at all
did he well I know that like he had like he just had it he had his mom but you
know it's like and his mom was very like
Forn up about it and stuff that he say with his grandmother and he was that's why he hadn't changed
He went to Texas stay with his grandmother for a while came back with his dog
And he's like video and it's like in his grandmother was a real like
Same energy because I'm talking about the guy who stabbed you. Yes. Yes. Okay. Okay. Yes
You know he I saw it. I saw there was a good side to him too. That's why I forgave him and take you cuz
Even if he wasn't like really that spirit might be stuck to your ass brother. You got to get rid of him
Hey, I do feel like you love the holy water on Frankie. How do we exercise that?
I know there's an evil spirit that is jumping around into people and saying making them
safety or taking them into the back, like some kind of energy, I definitely feel that.
And it's like, I don't know if it's him or if it's like, cause I was thinking it was
like demonic or something or something kind of evil spirit because it's like, it will
say this fucked up shit that it's like, it shouldn't know and stuff like that.
Bro, a year ago, two years ago, your videos, you were a completely different person.
just before everybody when you were by yourself hi i'm psyche awakens like those videos okay
then you started with us and then when you just subscribed about hating gays and women that's
basically what's been happening up here so i think page is onto something yeah well there is a dark
energy dude it's been taking i mean i thought it was me so thank god we found the source
Every single one of my probably myself look there definitely has been a poltergeist created from everybody on YouTube
It is a committee is a cumulative of energy. That is not of healthy
I'm sorry, I'm sorry to interrupt you
This is like a window on the screen right now this person
You see the screen right here? Look at this.
Look at that demon down there.
That is Sig.
I won't let him up, and so he's come on one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, seven different.
I think that's the maximum number of accounts you can come up on.
I keep kicking him out of the studio. He keeps coming back. He won't leave.
And then there's oh, that is very close there telling me this we're gonna kill you like this
Cut your throat
You know what yeah, you didn't look
And you
Why he does it because he's always gotten a rise out of you
Not being a rise out of me, but it's just like if you imagine how annoying would be page if someone builds your studio
After time I am just banning banning banning. He's coming on the same name. I don't know how
I'm gonna take
Hey, what's up, dude
So and bro drinking beers. I'm listening to you man smoking wax. Well, I don't have much left, but
Yeah, I think I'm like
Is that wax is that we call it
No, it's wax. It's a pen. It's a fucking so the pen was like a brand new it was a
foreground and then I
Don't know what this is. It's like
Wow
That is that like a syringe kind of thing you put the wax in is that a wax syringe?
You never and you know, you never disappoint baby. What the fuck is that?
It's oil. It's a it's a whale. Yeah
You can eat it, but it's not like you're gonna say like I
Have one that just like a shitty ass wax or fucking what oil whatever is one of these
Like fruity fucking goofy ass retard shit
Can't the fuck off like
Just sit here and suck.
Shut up, bro.
Holy fuck.
So what the fuck are you doing, Sight?
Well, you know, it's like, I'm just
trying to have a better night.
And you know, um.
Me too.
We've got it.
It's been it's been it's a really emotional time. I feel like you know, sometimes the calm comes up to the storm and there's
Certainly been a lot of storm and stuff
Like lately and I'm just waiting for that calm and I'm like, I think I'm on my way
I did a lot of cleaning
It's coming bro. We can't rain every day. Yeah. Yeah
Here's like I'll pull a card from my new deck like the April
S3 or cool or whatever see if they come out for you
Yeah, I'll see it
It looks like the April obviously have to do the back but like you know just the work in progress
But I really want to do this for you. I did earlier, but I didn't
Want to interrupt what you're doing
Actually
You can see into your little mind right now psych
Okay, go ahead
Okay
Interesting you're like I know what you're doing right now, and it's not to be you're being a little bit
Okay, let's do this whatever it is two weeks and okay, it's a two weeks and better and brighter days are to come
Don't be fooled by shady shit, and yes, that's what you get.
Thank you.
Benny, are you...
We have Paige here, who's a great reader.
Are you interested in maybe having a reading?
Sure, sure.
Do you mind Paige?
Not at all.
Okay.
You're very interesting. You're I'm just gonna tell you that right now your energy is like it's very playful
But it's also serious and so I get that like with the Sagittarius Capricorn and me
It's like I kind of understand that but you have been through like a ton of shit. So
You kind of transmute your pain into like dark humor and or like you take your experiences and you're like you know what I'm gonna
I'm gonna make music out of this or I'm gonna create something and you always make it something else
And then you teach people how to do that with with what you create from your pain. Is that I mean not probably too far off also
out of you never got to be like kind of I can relate to you it's weird like I can it's like a
mirror so your soul like you've never really got to be a kid in this life I don't think I think
you had to take care of people really young I feel like you've had a lot of responsibility as
maybe I mean maybe not the same kind of responsibility as like hey like no it was you
you really had a lot of responsibility you had to take care of everybody you've kind of always been
Like, I don't want to say Papa Bear, but like a mini Papa Bear, like you've always taken care of everybody, and even if you're like the most fucked up person at a party, you're still the most responsible one.
You still always have your head clear, like you can take, what is it, self-awareness and like kind of keeping your shit together for everybody else as a whole.
So it's a lot of weight to carry, and it does kind of play on you.
and even your physical now that's like as you get older you're like you know what it's starting to
kind of put some play on my my physical my wear and tear is is showing um but i don't think you
ever had an outlet to express your your like what you i call like gifts abilities fucking weirdness
whatever you want to call it but you have this like you have the abilities you have the gifts
and if anybody doesn't recognize that in you then they're also not a true one
Because you recognize that in others, too, and you really fucking hate fake people.
Like, when it comes down to, like, I guess, character, a judgment of character, yours is, like, spot-on most of the time.
Any time you've ever been fooled, it's because of out of love, like, the blind of the heart, or the rose-colored glasses.
But also...
It never really made you bitter about it.
You were always still open to experiences of such,
but different, like greater form
or like advanced version of such.
Like you just learn a lot from your lessons.
I think you're a really cool energy.
I think you're just, you're kind of interesting, I guess.
It's like intriguing would be the word.
Psych, would you like to pull a card
and then do tat for tat?
You probably nailed it.
You don't mind. Yeah. You were talking or you were talking about
Benny, right? I was reading. Yeah, you nailed it. You fucking nailed it on
Yeah, and
And Arthur
Arthur, okay
Not cool for my mom just like calm down Arthur. You don't want to be here. Just don't be here. Okay
Okay, Benny. This is temperance. Okay. This is a temperance card. This is like you need to
Like it's like be balanced. Okay. He does it well
And it's like this almost looks kind of like you in a certain way like that it does have like this appearance of you
And maybe like anything like you
Because there's these extreme parts of you, but then it's like there's a side of you that can be so
you know so
Even and it's like in cool and stuff like that kind of the one foot in spirit world one foot on the earth like and
able to maintain and like and to stay calm in a storm, but I think it's also a reminder to stay balanced
with all your
Inactivity not to like go to extreme one way or the other and that's it's better
That's better for you and that will help you stay more even-minded because I do see like you're a beautiful person
It's a queen of cups. I don't I think this queen of cups
Could be like a like a woman a water sign
Maybe an older woman like
In your and I don't know if you've been dating somebody that's older or just like
And this could be a water sign person, but it's also like you see this particular card
She's like walking and she has like this. She's walking in like nature
Then touch with her emotions. She walks walking my water actually by this by this stream and everything
so this is somebody that's able to like
Help you balance you in this and to stay balanced, you know, and it's interesting and also I see in this in this background
There's a big castle there. That's almost like saying like you have a possible big beautiful future
if you can find the right person that can help you stay balanced and
She can like
really help pull you up and maybe motivate you in certain ways and I don't know, I don't know who this is, or this person yet, but I do feel that for you, and also I got the three of swords, but this isn't a reverse, and this is so, this is really to me, this is like,
a really healing from some severe trauma, heartbreak,
really something that broke your heart.
Maybe I know you don't like to show it too much,
but I think that this is healing.
And it's like, and you have been working on yourself
and you are maturing and it's like,
whatever this has been is something that is like,
It's terrible, but at the same time taught you lessons. It's it's uh, you know, I
Feel your heart is healing. I feel it. I feel it with your heart
Oh my gosh, okay
This is a couple decks mixed together that I'm using but I pulled the three of swords again
But this is a this is in the upright
So that's kind of like hot of me of this to it like Q in a grocery store. It's like I
Do feel that there's that there's a healing there, but it's like beware of like
Letting it happen again. Oh Amanda
Amanda someone's time out Amanda for five minutes somebody in the chat
I'll hold the final car for you Danny. This is a hermit and this is like really like be honest. This is like
spending time spending some time and
like by yourself like
like thinking about things like like you have this light that can guide you the way you want to go, okay, and
Okay, if that makes sense, and there's and you're on it and you're on up your own
I'll go myself
I'll be on a better path and there's like, you know this light of the moon and there's also like the light you're holding
with any of the guiding and stuff and so
I think time alone is very important and so I would say time and nature and just that's healing for you
I think that's the key to restoring it. It's like you have to do this too like for yourself
Yeah, for sure man
Hey, are you like, okay, this is I know I'm sorry, but I have to like I've
Don't feel like I feel like you might be the one like looking for that
Like you might be in that the reverse of this energy that he was just explaining so it's like
Also, I feel you're kind of are you okay? Are you a Virgo?
Are you on the cusp? Are you like a fire or sign or like?
Okay, so that's a water sign. Okay, so you're I
Very you're okay. That makes sense. That makes sense. I'm just trying to understand your energy because like you're very I
Think you
You know, you know that you're like that. I think that's like your cork though. Like that's what makes you you that's like that
It's like an offset balance, but balance. It's like a puzzle piece that shouldn't fit the fit
That's like that's what you are within yourself in a weird way. There's like this
I don't know you're unique. It's like you're your own kind of fucking
Beacon of you don't create you don't vibe by like the most
Freak with the frequency of the norm. It's like there's weird. There's that vibe of frequency or whatever if tone if you will and then there's
Weird or and then there's you but it's not weird. It's unique and it's kind of what makes you
Helps you understand or navigate other people and how to like insert yourself
into certain things like a social chameleon if you will. It's like an understanding of self and
others which creates this balance of you won't accept anything less than in a relationship either.
I feel like for some reason I have to bring that up. I do feel like you were maybe the softer one
in the last relationship that you had and that they were the more aggressive overbearing kind of
For the one there was some deceit there for some reason I kept seeing the number seven and the numbers number five
Which for me is always conflict and deceit without any cards. I just feel like
You conflicted with how it ended is kind of what I'm asking you
Okay, okay, that's okay, you don't have to it's more or less like I think there was just like a misunderstanding of
of what you expected in the future with each other.
I just want you to know that for some reason.
I'm sorry, I'm just saying.
You're good, you're pretty good, like, I guess, not spot on, but closer.
It doesn't have to be romantic though, dude.
It can be like, honestly, when I'm seeing this connection, it just meant something to you.
It could be a friend, it could be fucking, you know, a business connection.
There was just something that you had higher expectations than they fell through.
Like, to me, that's what the basics I can sum it up to.
Ooh.
Yeah.
Cool.
Anyways, thank you. Sorry. I've never met you. I'm Paige. Nice to meet you
Yeah, my name is Benny. Okay, I've heard about you
Not in a bad way, you just have to be mentioned as all because you know, like Benny was like where I
Kind of like was introduced like this kind of concept of streaming and Benny was like the first person that would like you know
He would like it let me do tarot in his chat and he would um he would like for a moment
I don't know I'm tell me get rid of 50 first 50 subscribers and
You know, he's a really interesting and yeah a very interesting energy for sure. Yeah
You're way too nonchalant for how in tune you know that, right?
I guess
That's what makes him cool. He's too cool for school, right?
I know I'm just saying he's he uh, he's too nonchalant
Yeah, this guy is cooler than the other side of the pillow my friends
Hey, what's that?
Isn't this just kitty just kitty. Yeah, I was thinking was kitty like I think you told me that
But I would say any like like that cat has like some really really good healing energy for you
Like and it's like, you know treat that cat the cat is special. Okay, so
You know that
Yeah, I think the cats have a vibration that is a healing vibration
And it's like I know my like my cats have like helped heal me like a lot and they just help and
Continually they also protectors. They're also astrally. They're like these
They can be like lions
I've heard him for like a year almost two years. Yeah, oh, yeah
Yeah, the beautiful cat like I had a you know, I had a black and white cat
Does everybody on fucking YouTube have a black and white cat?
Because it seems that way
Except me. I'm gonna have to get one because I feel left out. What is this shit?
I have five cats and they're all everybody has a fucking tuxedo. Yeah, if I you have five cats
No, I was just kidding
I have five cats just five cats. I have four cats
Alex you have a cat or you just looking for pussy Alex. Yeah, exactly number two
No, but seriously bro, I mean James has a black and white be it as a black and white
Oh
Christine has a black and white. I saw them do a panel everyone camped up this group of black and white cats now
Oh, Benny you have
You got a black and white
I had a tuxedo cat just like him before him for fucking eight years.
Yeah, I figure it's for like almost eight years.
Oh, turn, thank you, folks.
I was about to call you pussy.
Well, after you, my friend.
Stop playing with him.
Come on.
Don't come on
Easy my pull-up quack is around fuck. Who pulls out what?
I was a freaking panel
Alexander McQueen's a freaking panel guest, but he didn't start trying to start his own panels
But he just named it after me and then he just wanted to ban people
Yeah, one night. I hit Shreem Yard. I started my own shit
I just wanted to ban people. I was waiting for them to come out just to kick them out.
I heard about that. That was the good story. I heard about that.
That was funny as hell.
That was definitely funny.
I even tried to beat them in. I called the psyche awakens open panel.
I was trying to beat them. I was waiting for them.
And he just wanted to, as soon as they came in, he would just ban us and he just loves to ban us.
I know Prairie, who's this little boy in the top right hand corner?
Who's this?
Master, who is that?
That is Benny and Benny is a streamer who is very viral and you know, he's pretty fascinating.
That's no law.
Yeah, oh shout out the home. He just looks Bailey League. Well, I'm just saying
But you know it's funny so Benny I talked to this guy good times
He said you were on his show two years ago, and he asked how
Yeah, I was on his channel what fucking five years ago. Oh, it's five years ago. Okay, we're not five years
We're gonna say like that. Okay, you're 20
Okay, so you're 21, but why'd you tell me you're 17?
You said you were 17, and he swears that you said you were 17, but I know, but why did
you say that to him?
I just like, because then he was like, oh my God, and now people think that.
Oh, I literally showed one birth certificate most of the time on the stream.
I know.
I
Listen Benny you need a manager. I got you brother. I will have you in Times Square and Calvin Klein underwear
You know Sammy on a billboard. You were showing a fucking um 10 million dollars
I'll give you my cut. I'll take your million man. Nine for you, one for you.
Oh my god, I lost the turn. Oh my god
Oh my gosh, I'm in the quackers game and like
Pays how old are you?
Why I?
Don't know. I'm just wondering
Okay, I was just wondering
Okay, sorry, he looks super young though. Honestly if I saw you guys together like you guys can make a good couple
I swear to God
Right, I swear to God. I would buy that a party like page. Does that look 35?
I could definitely see you know penny with his arm around at a ball
Someone answered my fucking question. How old are you? How many? How old are you?
I'm 24.
You're hurt.
You're just a little...
24. Oh, you're made. I thought you were like 18, 24.
So when's the wedding?
Oh my god, I accidentally banned Amanda. I accidentally banned Amanda.
No, I did I banned the bitch
They keep saying my nails are like so good. Is that I know it's a little bit long
You know really well Ronys hey one fucking bottom down here
Clip nails your fucking supermodel
How the fuck do why do you care who gives a shit what people think of you man?
Like if you can tell like sometimes a good tarot reader by you know, so many you got to do it soon, buddy
Because you know your blink you're gonna be dirty. So the window
But right now supermodel hundred percent
He can't really that's not nice to say. I'm just like, oh, how do you Alex? How do you?
Kids where how do you Alexander
Alexander's the guy. Yeah. Yeah, how are you buddy?
What?
He's muted, but Alex, have you ever, have you ever been in Benny's chat before?
Yeah, I'm in my forties, bro. I'm in my forties, my boy.
Have you been in Benny's chat? Because I think you said you went to Benny's chat before.
Did go to Benny's chat. Okay, the first time I saw him I got intrigued like he said something about him intrigued me the guy
I thought he was in a haunted house, honestly
What is this kid?
You and you were like Benny Benny and like I think I know who you're talking about and now he's here with us
So this is great before yeah before that all this I'll just like I'll just sob and then I'll
Discuss what else but I'm like a page. I look half my age. You understand? I shave it. I look fucking 25
Doesn't have to shave she just looks like
Benny I would jump all over that and
But continue your brother. They'll throw you on a billboard instantly like yeah, you're not coming time
Sweetie or sweetie you dumb bitch. That's not you easy. Good morning everyone
the
So funny
Creepy I appreciate you taking a channel down for psyche and hiding all that stuff. That was really nice of you
You should probably change her to change her name. Just just don't just don't be like hey, hey
No negativity here
You know they stick together
I used to wear, I worked at a clothing store where I had to wear a tie and then I worked at a job where I had to wear a tie.
Listen, listen.
I refuse to wear one anymore.
Yeah.
The coyotes
Yeah, Benny will protect you who shoot their heads off
There's a reason my neighborhood Benny and one of my cats I did a black in my cat and like the coyotes
You don't have the right to shoot them here, and if you call the animal control, they won't come in unless they're like a danger of people or they're-
Awww, it'll be a little bit tight. Come on, get a 22 or something.
Well, I don't- I never see them around here, but it's like wanting to get my cat-
Oh, 22 won't mark it for it. I hope it's a little too big for that caliber.
Yeah, but if you fucking shoot a fucking coyote ahead, they're done.
Yeah
I was walking around I look like literally she was in police station about as we walking around with a shotgun looking for coyotes
I would definitely not
Explode in the streets of fucking explode you literally yeah, she's right. It would have fucking explode
Well, you know
Literally I have an interesting like, you know really with the coyotes because coyotes are actually they remind me of the sign of Gemini
Really they remind me of the rodents of the canine world, right?
Well, but they're also known as the divine trickster and like because
Indian totems and they are considered the divine trickster their coyotes always
Teaching lessons by fooling people, right?
They don't suppose any more. They used to like pretend they're a baby. You don't want to eat babies, don't they?
Oh my gosh, they eat their baby. I never heard of that part of the poem.
They will eat, they will eat their babies.
I'm 22, let's put the shit.
No, you're babies too, they'll eat babies.
Cats, cats will eat their babies.
Oh, so Betty, he's got a short, he's so, I don't know what that thing is, that looks like straight out of fucking Afghanistan, a military, what the fuck is that thing?
and
of the
He'll pay your sweepy. You're still there, baby. Yeah page. It fascinates me how long you could sit like that the way you are
Why without it bother in your town, right before I was thinking I could not
It's called my it's good. Just yeah
Well, I mean that is
It's actually you can get quite comfortable like seeing like this it's actually like it's actually very grounding
First my lower back
I do golf barefoot too, so I mean like I'm just weird. I'm sorry
Yeah, I'm fucking love golf is life. I used to work here at mini golf
I actually work in a fucking well a golf course not mini golf. Yeah, but yeah, I
Like I don't know. I like this fun. It was just born sometimes like is either there's a shed ton of people like or there's no people
I feel like that flow goes with like most service industries, though, right?
Like there's like a rush hour for certain things in every industry and that kind of
I love it. Love it. Cheers to that. Cheers to golf
What no more dirty footpegs. They're all gone. They're a race to more
Yeah, yeah
Alexander McQueen because I am a fan of the 30 toes baby. We're especially yours
the
Putting a cock up poor mom in the guy on accent
Yeah, the 19 inch top pick was right next to the foot pick and I hit the cock instead of the
I mean I didn't look at beforehand and there's a porn clip at the end of it and people had actually seen it and nobody
Warmed me about it
I think my channel was taken down and
Miraculously got it back by a miracle
But I perform on that was my kind of my public form on myself by putting a short on also one time
I did show like the SeaWorld like Russia thing where they had this thing
It was it came the dolphin to catch a fish by jumping up on the platform onto like a lady laying down there and like and then
It was on porn site.
You were there for that was an accident.
Right.
That was because it was on porn sites.
The ad came up for it.
It was like a porno.
Oopsie.
Yo, psyche, put a tie on.
But OK, do you have Instagram?
Yeah.
Oh, I go Instagram.
What is your Instagram?
Instagram's the devil, man.
Like, oh, he's fucking out.
Hold on.
The internet's the devil.
on this use of a good
, is bad on the score
the game
,
I keep looking spiffy tonight man
I can only imagine when this guy goes out on time
It's a good match man, honestly
Yes, Brad underscore Benny
Brad underscore Benny page
He's hot he's hot. I mean what the fuck it makes sense
Page just watch out your mom. He likes to punch mom he punched. He did punch his mother
So just watch out with that. I'm not his mother. I know but he's a little violent
His mom was on the show last the other night
Look at the lady of the castle painting that painting is on that castle that painting move around like to pay by the way
Because you know I love her so but I love her that much that I just want to be happy and hey, I guess you know
We make a little tense, but they make sense. You get it
I've so many people on Instagram am I dating all of them. No, I'm not yes
I will find my pageroni some day. Don't worry.
I'm Pageroni. I'm Psyche Roni. She's Pageroni.
And then we join
Arthuronies, have you called him?
Arthuronies, yes.
He has been an operator at Arthuronies.
You have Benny Ronie too.
Benny Ronies, correct.
That sounds like a bread company.
It sounds like a, yeah, it sounds like a rice company maybe.
Mine sounds like a fucking-
You are invited to the Royal Wedding
of Paige and Benny Ronies.
Huh?
Has a ring to it.
Yeah, I love it.
How about a sight being gay or rony?
Why do you shit and run with it all the time, Alex?
We all know that I'm gay.
Gay or rony.
That's what you're about.
I like it's okay. We love him psyche is hurting to right now because he loves Benny and I love page
But we gotta let them go
Oh, yeah hit him with the bushes
So one day Psyche was driving on the highway and I saw him speed by and I was like, whoop, whoop, I pulled the ball, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, who
I
I don't know if I saw the I do have the parts you but I mean, oh my gosh. I have a lot of messages here
Let me see. Okay. Yeah, he fucked up man. He didn't have the pride proper paperwork. Well, you know, that's got ugly
Views the advice where you're about to watch the faint of heart
I
Can I find it I could find I could find
She is looking up Benny as we found I found it guys. I found it guys. I found it. I found it. Hold on a second
Okay, you can pause these look at how do you fucking know? She's looking me up off cam the fuck trust me brother. I could feel it
Fucking energy
Fucking energy good dog. Okay the decode. Yeah
I was just going to the bathroom you dickhead
How'd you hear him?
Because my master bathrooms in my master bedroom
Whoa, my bad. Oh
God Arthur unfortunately these two need a room fuck. Oh my god
I'm hurting right now, man, but it's okay. I love her. Why are you hurting? You gotta let it go. You know if you love her
wait what if you love something let it go and if it comes back to you it was it
was meant to come back it was never yours in the first place right exactly so
we'll see I'm gonna throw in Benny's lap she comes back to me she was always
mine she doesn't then hey Benny have fun with her Canadianist okay
I hope I look I'm gonna give it one more run. Oh, is this it? No, no, no, if I hope I don't find it
I do have one other thing I can show you actually because I've been animated. I've been turned into a cartoon character and stuff and
That's pretty funny. Oh, really? Yeah
Okay, this is Tony. Okay. Okay. This is straight. There's so many emails here. I've been going through. Let me see
Oh, where the fuck is this? But it's pretty funny. Is this it?
to bring others a bricked up song, my God, so that you can find it, come on, let's go, it's right there
I'm looking for it, I'm looking for it, I'm looking for it
How many videos do you have?
I literally, like
Oh, those Indian shit every day, you gotta scroll through that to get to it
I literally, like, a thousand, uh, guys, okay, it's like
Goot them, fuck you up, what happened to Goot them anyway?
Okay, he's here tonight. What happened?
Did you see it?
I found it, I found it, I found it, I found it.
He found it, he found it.
Here, body cam.
Okay, I'm going to put it.
Viewers discretion be advised.
And then I'm going to share the screen, okay?
This is a, this is a cartoon that was made of Alex and I.
This is actually a true story.
And this is a-
I'm not lying, brother.
That's, okay, I'm lying, I'm lying.
Okay. This is a dash cam footage. Okay. Tire screen.
Close to it. Got it. Here we go. Here we go.
There. Okay. And...
the
Okay, you said that four times already pal. I'm sorry not to believe it
No, no, nothing
That fucking series.
Here it is, here it is.
Finally, I got it, I got it up.
Okay, hold on.
Alex, what are you gonna do to me if I, you pull me over?
I've been cheating on the, on the freeway.
What are you gonna do to me?
I'm gonna say sir, oh, license registration.
I'm gonna pretend it's bad.
I'm gonna say step out of the car
and I'm gonna throw you in the bushes.
In the bushes, I'm gonna pump the shit out of you.
In the bushes.
Okay
That was a romantic thing
It was romantic that was the best
I
Freak is if it's cops pulling you over and stuffing you into a bush, maybe
And this one I had a lot quicker I promise is a lot quicker this is this happened this is my this is like when I started streaming
They they made these cartoons to be on this channel to Lord of the crew
and uh i got this really quick okay there what they're called lord of the grove and they do
cyrax cartoons and they do other cartoons yeah so you know this one okay well here we go this is
this one uh it's pretty great here you go uh there i am okay ooh
You know, this time, this time, I already know the buttholes scam, I'm not falling for it again, okay?
I see it first, okay?
I'll pay you after you show me your butthole.
You can't just say you're going to show me your butthole and then I send you a $10 cash
up and then you don't show me your butthole.
And then no butthole.
Exactly.
No, I get it.
It's a new rule.
You have to show it to me first.
Oh, maybe I'll give you a tip.
This is crazy.
No, please, nobody send me a picture.
That would be weird, because then it would be like, oh, then Aldi would do it or something.
Oh, I'm not.
I think you should replace that picture.
I know.
I'd like a man to do it.
I see never never mind. It's too expensive. It's not a very many but holes. Yeah, the fish taco one
Oh, that's the Mexican pizza lady. Where's the piece? No come here. There's some Franco and then we got to do the same man
to finish it all
And I was like, hello, was it paid for?
Okay.
And they're like, it was a paid for.
They're like, no, senior.
And I was like, oh, I was like, lo siento.
It's like some prank, some prank.
And she's like, oh, okay, okay.
And she left.
I haven't happened three times in a row, though.
Literally, Benny they were sending pizzas to his house. That's why they made
Does that
This can't stop eating them so good I eat them so fast
I'm like, I'm turning into a fish taco, basically.
Fish taco?
I'm like, I just need a tortilla wrap.
Looks like I put my blanket around me.
It feels like I'm a burrito.
And I feel like I'm turning into a fish taco.
I'm sorry.
You're right.
I hate too many of them.
And it was like, first it was like fun.
It was like, oh, this is good.
And then it turned into an addiction.
I've turned into a fish taco all you do is wrap myself in a blanket and turn myself into a burrito
You ever seen one of the blankets all wrapped up?
What's the same man one later, but yeah, that was that was good
Amazing you guys gotta be more didn't they make another one of you wait as you as the fucking a way the wanker guy
Yeah, that might be the best one ever bro
You guys never do you ever feel like you want to punch your own self in the fucking face when you watch your own videos?
Cuz like I kind of do yeah, of course
That's why I never watch any I've never watched a stream of mine if I'm like referenced. Are you really said that's interesting
You I might go check it out, but when I have to I just want to fucking I want to punch myself in my own face
Hey, you watch your streams. Do you go back and watch them? Never? I've never watched
That's not I guess it's we don't have the stream, but I do I go back and watch like old shit and
Yeah, up there you wouldn't go watch yourself. You'd be irritated by it
Yeah, you're like second guessing everything
Yeah, 100 percent. Fuck my face, fuck my voice, fuck my stupid-
Oh my god. Yeah, exactly.
They just don't do it and just keep moving forward.
Yeah, they just don't do it. Yeah, exactly.
They could be like, me and fucking degenerate.
The only one that's done that with are like the ones with Spandela where I go to like reference something to her like say there's this one video and we're golfing and I'm like the beginning of the video sums her and I up to a fucking tea in like real life where we're together like and she's like all this is like oh yeah well we're just out here we're just working on our golf game blah blah and like dude we've been golfing for years we should be fucking better you know what I mean just the whole concept of it is like you suck you have no talent.
This is a new triplicate video, it's a new triplicate video, and I'm really walkin' on this one.
I wish he paid me, he's good, you still talk to him, obviously.
But, Paige, did you have me on Instagram?
I didn't, yeah, but here, but...
I'm listening, Rony.
Look, wait, look at that.
Do you have a Snapchat?
Yeah.
Oh, here we go.
Yeah, have me on Snapchat, it's just what we do.
Amanda, many words go listen to Vita's stream tonight, where she had a woman saying F-A-G-G-O-T and N-I-G-G-E-R about a thousand times, laughing, all the way through, with everybody out there, and also saying gay people should die.
Go listen to that, Amanda, and go defend her. Come back in. Come back in.
I mean, I thought you and Amanda were like...
like a lot.
I like Amanda, and Amanda went to Christine's and I heard Christine talking all this shit
and Amanda was kind of like, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, and it's like, they're not really
you know and she would say later she's like oh I like psyche and you know but I'm not expecting
this leading up to the really want to shit or we just watch it
oh shit right now we have to choose he kind of in the enemy territory
no no I don't want to hear about Mando between you and Tony
well that was like so then she I thought it would be because I had that
let's be uh that's cool let it out if you got it to once in a while I was
I was interested in this brand new one but yeah I'll show you I'll show you the other one okay
Or we can just go back to us and let's do some more
Aronnie psych aronies banner onies
Nostalgic video from like even like it's like six months. Oh those are the best. Yeah, we can
Honestly because it's so different than now. You're actually watching me like oh my god. This was us like now
It's like all months every day each other
So
Fucking jammies I've got wasted do reeks for you guys like I'm not
His channel got deleted and so oh my god, that was funny
You can't try something. That's not there my friend. Aha
Gotcha. Check me. Good shit
They're trying to strike them bro every fucking day fucking site
Yeah, I don't know it's all crazy
Well, I got bro. I fucking went from fucking 70 K fucking overall to fucking not even 500
70 K sobs you had ones no 70 like I would like average 70 case been overall
Oh views and shit, so okay
If you think if you could do it every day, that's like
Oh my god, start doing it again, bro, it's crazy
To get to brand a month from YouTube you have to consistently at least get 35 K views a day
From anything you have going whether it's
35 K views
Daily for a month though. That's 30 days of getting 35 K views
Then you'll get a check for two grand to three grand in a month. Yeah
I had like five grand on fucking YouTube and they slowly drained my account to where I only have
$300 on my YouTube account and I never took any money out of it
In reality, I should have like fucking 30k fucking YouTube from YouTube ads, but I don't fucking have anything
Wow, see and that's why multiple panels help other channels
If you're running three channels at a time and you get 10k here from a short, you know
I fit 11k from this one, whatever as long as it has up to 35k daily views
That's three grand a month check. That's not even that hard to do. I see 35k. No, I was me. I was I had
10 times that amount of views at one point. So how did they know if you got a million views a day?
Okay, so they said my my my um
My my push of myth misinformation on ukraine. This was it been like three years ago
Um that they're gonna take the money out of my account and so they already take like I think it was like 30%
And they said we're taking an additional
40 to 60% or I think it was 40% of your
Earnings that so I went from having 10k in an account on YouTube to fucking like I said
They just literally drained it to where now I barely have $300
But the reason that they were doing it was because they were sending the money to Ukraine.
Okay, so then transit issues kind of in the sense of like the transfer of
Yeah, well basically basically they fucking just took my money out and said that I was spreading misinformation and just took my money and sent it to Ukraine
So yeah
And if anybody does read like the fine print with like the YouTube kind of I guess which you kind of like like designed your life over when it comes to the
Yeah, pretty much yeah
Yeah, it's in there, but no one I mean to an extent it's in there
So that's something actually you could fight though if you think about it because there is like even wording
You're very smart, you know all that stuff if that's a lot of money to just fucking be taken from you
Like it is yeah
That's ridiculous, and it's not like we don't create stuff to put out there
And it doesn't mean like if it's not creative to all of you
It's still us putting ourselves out there and should you know like that's fucking if you're paid for it
Then you're entitled to that, right?
But yeah, um, it just really sucks. I try not to think about it because it just speaks to me like there's nothing that's there's nothing me getting mad about it
Is it gonna do a fucking thing about it? You mean?
Okay
I'm trying to ask is it like the YouTube funds do you have to transfer that into or exchange it into some sort of like
My bang, yeah, I got a transfer to a bank. Yeah. Okay, watch it. Look. It's my cat
Okay, well never mind. Hey, well, you can look in my cat right here though
Say play some old shit play like
I don't know. Let's laugh let's laugh at ourselves like when you started your channel the content was fucking money
It was gold. We did the most random shit ever
I'm a 35 year old mother and I was on my roof playing the recorder like there's just so much stuff
That's so really bad. Yeah, there's fun stuff where we used to actually all kind of like
Tastefully troll each other if it makes sense like it was a different
You know
Oh, it's like trivia and shit, too, which was super fun.
It wasn't just always drama related, like in.
Sawie.
Actually, it was like, there was like the panels were like,
this is wild back then.
They were like, it was like I said,
tastefully done in a sense, where
everybody's kind of lost a little bit of their class
when it comes to the troll day.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
So I love you.
But I don't know shit. I've only been here for six years not in this particular community, but like my channel's actually seven my channel's been up for seven
This only community I've ever learned any like it's like the back alley of like YouTube Street
It's like sometimes when it comes to like the behavior, I guess
No, I'm fucking cooked on YouTube. I went from so many Taylor said to now. I barely you fucking ten viewers
Yeah, you say cooked
I'm cooked. Yeah, I think we say cooked here
I say cooked a lot people take in their own context because it means so many different here and then it does like where I live
Yeah, you're cooking. Yeah, you're cooking with fuel. You're cooking with gas now. Yeah
But like if we say that either like you're fucking cooked bro like not it's not like the same
Yes, not. No, no, but it's okay. Now y'all know now y'all know. Yeah, it's just the old time saying like yeah, you're cooking with Josh
Yeah
Mark Mark
We're cooking bro
Cooking yeah, you be cooking taste
Well, sometimes it really takes a bit for me to like push to that point
But when I do apparently it's I guess it's not a comfortable. It's come. It's not comfortable at all
Okay, I'm like
These two guys not like me for each other. I don't get it. You know, she lives in the woods. He's a woods woman like you
This one
Basically you with a vagina
Yeah, oh basically me with a vagina
You are you think you are you page with a dick, you know
You sound like you're jerky boys
Yeah, Benny's in Pennsylvania
That's pretty far away it's pretty far away damn
Yeah
It's two hours by plane. What do you mean for two hours by plane?
One movie watch a movie you're there
Fucking movies crazy
Interesting. I don't know what time zones it made me know it, but...
What?
Oh, I'm just going, I'm such a fucking nerd.
Okay, so in my mind, I'm just like talking out loud.
I'm like, Calculate.
I'm like, so by time zone, so Alex, you might not be correct because like,
if you thought about that, right?
Because I'm actually...
Alright, okay, hold on.
If you want to get technical.
You're in Alberta, Canada, you say?
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, damn, yeah, yeah.
Oh, he said, oh, like, you know something about Alberta, so if we just go to your airport get up take it to Alberta Canada
How long is it?
Honestly, I really don't know. I'm just joking around. But does anyone know?
Three and a half hours if you calculate the time do like that's it. That's that's a movie
That's a long movie watch Titanic that she was three hours and something you're there Titanic
with Leonardo DiCaprio
boom
No, I'm rather fucking
I am a boarding fish that I bought
Okay, you can do it
You can jump a little kinda to watch Titanic and land in this guy's arms
No, I'm not landed in anyone's arms man.
Why not?
No
I honestly, I'm still like not quite over right. Are you serious? It's been fucking two years already or no
Yeah, I hear a year a year and a half a year a year
I've been there, but it's been one
Still not over him or the best way to get over him is to get under this guy, okay
This guy's fucking nuts. Listen, I am ready to kind of maybe date now, but maybe not a date cuz I don't know
He dating is crazy. Yeah, but I mean, uh, yeah, I really talked to you
This is you know what but in the aspect Alexander you're ready to spend a long fucking time bitch get over it, right? I know
Oh my god, this is just...
If you are evil...
Yeah, they are and you know what everybody has their own agenda and intentions and it's hard to see when you really care about somebody
Hey, are you seriously talk to me?
Oh, so what how much are you there though? Are you like 80% recovered or you're still like, uh-huh in him forever?
I want to put it in exact percentage. I'd say like 87.5 percent
Do you got 13 12.5 to go? You know, he's like, oh, you're good wait, uh, exactly
I don't know adequate suitors in my general area that I'd be interested like it's so fuck it
I'll just be single cuz I take care of myself and my kid. I'm fine. I don't need a man
He's hot bro too hockey way not in a cocky way
I'd love I'd love like a partner like somebody like a companion, but I don't need need one
Yeah, I get that. Yeah
Ronys
I would kill you I would say we could kill but you just live really far
I know I live across the world pretty much Ronys. There we go. I'll be right
What everyone's just leaving us. Let's make it more awkward. I grow up. I don't give a fuck
I don't care either. I'm having a good time. So fuck it
So what is the content because I haven't checked it out of your channel?
Should I just go I'll just find out for myself kind of no me getting dry. It's just me getting drunk bad
Well, apparently it was successful if you've had that many like views, you know
At one point yeah, my channel is stupid compared to that except for I do get drunk on it sometimes
So it's not really that far off I guess
What's your channel?
It's oh my god, it's the longest thing ever don't laugh. It's prairie winds and wildflower spiritual arts. No, no put me back stage back stage
What are you doing? He's a good third wheel though because he talks more than either of us
Yeah, he's funny as fuck
Fucking so yeah, how many subscribers you got like almost a thousand. I think I'm at like nine. Yeah. Yeah, why would you have?
have 24k well that's a oh damn you're gonna that's a lot I was at 30k but then
I lost like a lot of subscribers you just got to be yourself and drink so
that's pretty cool so it says a lot a lot about your energy in general for
people to be like that attracted to it yeah it's definitely true yeah did you
Okay, but but uh, yeah, I'm kind of drunk
Pardon me am I drinking again, I am of course, it's like nighttime. That's what we do in the night, right?
Yeah
What the fuck is that?
It's great. It's beer. It's reindeer
I've never seen it before in my life. I don't think well. It's like I think it's American. Why have you not seen it?
I don't know. I'll be drinking Coors Banquet and Millers.
I love Coors Banquet. I don't like Millers.
Yeah, hell yeah.
I'm not a big fan of the Millers though.
Millers, they're...
They're good.
It's a gassy beer. Let's be real.
Yeah, yes it is. Yeah, for sure.
Doesn't work.
Yeah, the Coors Banquet almost has like the viscosity of it is like a velvet to you like creamy finish
Whereas like then you have the more like I don't know micro bubble brew if you will with the high life the Miller high life
Especially yeah
Yeah, I don't mind it but for the price like I fucking have way better options for a lower price
No, it's only $20 at 30 rack. Well, okay, so they're here. It's like, okay
So 30 30 beer you guys have that coming up. That's a thing. We have case. Yeah, we get 30 racks yet
Yeah, we get 24 so we call it flat
It was a twist you but a flat of highlight Miller highlight
So if I would be able like that's like over a hundred bucks
I'm not kidding. Look at Google it. I'm not even kidding. We get
USD you're like, what do you mean?
The Canadian like CAD
So yeah, that would be like what I don't know $30 American. Yes, it's a few it's a quite a few dollars difference for sure
So yeah, and also like the duty-free shit like you guys that there's certain taxes that you don't have that we do
Yeah, we get a lot we get a lot of taxes for look at some reason
Bullshit does it depend on like what product it is or is it depending on every product you have taxes
There's not a single product in America. It doesn't have a tax
Well, same here, but like I just smell like is it very on the tax price says to where it comes from obviously
Yeah, yeah
Okay
Yeah, we have like we have quite a few more rules like we don't have so if you want to talk about like liquor rules
Regulations, for example, like that we can all understand is beat boxes and buzz balls and fucking what's the other one?
Or locals or locals that's illegal here. It's just like the high the content of consent
Yeah, we don't have them here at all not at all. Yeah, be boxing. They're so good
Never had them. It's on my they're dangerous. They're dangerous if you boxes are so good
They taste like they don't taste like I'll call it all bro, and you could you could kill three of them. Yeah
tour up
That's what I mean and the for locos too is that not like ridiculous. No for locos tastes like ass. Yeah. No, you're not
They taste like the fucking rock stars with vodka. Do you remember those?
Kind of worse way worse. No, it's just
Yeah, it's similar it's similar. It's just so sugary
It's 13% alcohol. Yeah 14, but it's just so disgusting
And I have no idea why those are like our buzz balls good. They look like they taste I never had a bus ball
But I'm the bosses are my shit though
They're like juice like it's literally just like a fucking adult juice. Yeah, it literally just tastes like you yeah
It tastes like no alcohol at all, but it's fucking I think 12%
Okay, so I'm missing out on shit from America. Oh, yeah
Poutine and an actual proper Caesar and like America's a shit bro. Where's this shit? You already know where this shit late
We're just too kind over here, and you know America's probably yeah, we don't give a damn
No fucks given ever any American
Has called me miss like if I okay, so I went out one night to one of like my like there's a beach town
That's near us. It's only fucking thing. That's normal like that. Oh like that in Alberta
So whatever I live 25 30 minutes from it and last summer I met like four Americans and all of them called me miss
I felt like a lady, you know, it was nice, but it was I was like, yeah, do you want to fight you like cuz we're not used to that
dressing me like that
We try to be proper, but like we try to be proper like when we're not at all. Yeah, miss. Oh hi miss, but
Like yeah, we talk about purpose proper
Yeah, we try to but we talk like sailors. I'm a fucking trucker. Oh, I just as you can yeah
I'm not very
In that regard. No, you're good. No, you're more ladylike than a lot of women. So
Well, that says a lot about women. We need to step it up ladies
At least out here in America, man
Me and women are apparently like well, I mean we're built different obviously but American women
I find very like I've been intimidated by but then I heard evil
I heard it's the opposite way as well to like we're Canadian women like we play hockey
We fucking play rock. We're a little bit more on like
He's living on the edge if you will. Yeah, those are a bitch ass dudes. They're like
Yeah, well, yeah, so there's I guess there's a diamond reader like just why do you like so like the drink beer
I like the American that like most people see like are like me and that's like really going away pretty quick
So dudes that just hop on a bike that are nasty with it like fucking just pure skill fucking
Rodding and doing all that. That's that's that's just dinner
Extinct do you write to stroke or for stroke to stroke of course only way to go
Only two strikes exactly, you know, so yeah, I do it's kind of like not that for like up and I guess
Comparison to where I live to where you live
just the accents maybe yeah yeah they be they all y'all be rigging shit crazy but it'd be legit
but you say rigging and you certain things that you guys like I think to like honestly if someone's
to ask me what's the most like equal like lingo comparison it's kind of like where you're from
actually and like yeah in the way you say it it just like it is very similar to Alberta Canada
Yeah, yeah, it's a PA. Yeah, PA like
Yeah, this is PA stuff
Rigging you fucking rigging shit, but yeah, it also goes like yeah, you know, there's a lot of lingo. That's the thing
You can't get into this the same like out here. Yeah
We should make a
I don't know. Canada's, oh right. I feel like, okay, everyone in Canada, everyone has the same conflict, like, oh, it's always, it's the same everywhere.
No, you guys have, like, the link, like, in the sense of accent-wise, you all think that we sound like new bees or new, or new Brunswickers or East Coasters, but that's the East Coast side.
Even the province next to me, which is British Columbia and Saskatchewan, they are so different from Alberta, even just the way they talk.
Yeah, there's a don't you guys there's French Canadians?
Fucking yeah, there's there's so many different like it's like because it's uh, I don't think it's bigger than America
It might be but I know that you guys have a lot of like
different accents
like most people just really like you and holler like oh holler and
Like that's like most Americans I guess equivalent to what they think a
Canadian accent is
Pretty much or a boat like a boot leave the hole. Oh, yeah
It's a boot. Yeah, I do let it slip sometimes though
So they're not really that wrong and they've heard it for themselves. So I'm
My grams here, he's fucking from Virginia. She was like the worst
I'm a worse than close
Yep, hundred percent. Yeah, the world. Yes, the are with the fucking where it should never exist
Yeah, we're first. I don't know actually drop in chat. We're from every you're from or reside is a
How do you say certain things that you notice are different from other places even just close to you? That's a good one
That's a good topic
Yeah, how old the turret and the cat damn they're talking magic
What do you mean, are they talking about I know it never mind
I remember watching your channel when you okay, there's talking about shit on me on you
Yeah
Oh, well, okay, what's my minute what's happening in here what's happening to will and also will
Yeah, we'll wickers
What's going on? I don't know it's the most recent cuz it won't show me anything else like just the most recent I
See so you be watching do you be watching like AI videos like AI love Island?
Why would I watch that?
No, I don't I don't even watch TV
I never watched this shit, but I always get like fucking recommended like my channel's talking about how it's fucking getting banned off the takedown
No, I don't I actually don't like I'm not really a
Peer I don't know. I mean I do lives on my like my channel. I have done panels
I joined like psych safe panel and other I'm like a moderator and lots of channels and communities
But I actually don't come up here very like
Often for like and my intentions are kind of always the same. You know what I mean? I'm very neutral, but I'm
Bored maybe I'm boring am I boring? That's no you're not boring
For a girl maybe a little bit
What are you drawing or coloring?
I'm honestly, I have way too much to like, even get into that.
I make so many things.
I'm an artist of like, the media variety, if you will.
Right now, I'm working on this.
I don't know.
It's just doodling.
It's honestly because I have ADHD really bad, so I fucking have to do something.
Yeah, I pace really bad. Yeah, I do too a pace. I make duery a pain
I fucking draw a color fucking anything to like get rid of that excess energy. You know what I mean?
Yeah, I don't know. I like pasting. I don't know what it is like crazy and just makes me feel good
Well, I'm on the phone if I don't have to like I'm not video chatting even if I'm I'm always pacing my whole house
Just there's like should be like a pigeon in the snow footprints. It's back and forth
But yeah, people think I'm insane though. I don't really care though. I think that you're insane
I think that you also have like undiagnosed or maybe diagnosed form of ADHD
Which is just like a it's like a tendency to always have to be either moving. It's like hyper focus or hyper
Tenancy, right? So you're either always moving. You're always like thinking you're always you're always doing something. It's you can't sit still
Yeah, I was diagnosed when I was three young. They had me up, but they gave me pills when I was like 11 years old
Yeah, okay see that for me is like kind of
It's a good to get you on something like that, but at the same time
It's also like kind of hinders you from becoming your true like version of yourself at that age
Like where you're trying to become you're already fucked up when you're that age
Let's be real you guys you can't just diagnose someone with that and yes
It is a thing it can be present
But let a fucking teenager or a kid be a kid till they get to like say like like early adulthood and then start
Diving into that because you're kind of interrupting
who the fuck they're supposed to be in a way yeah that'll do that I know for sure
I like I don't know I broke my wrist dirt biking one time I don't know if that's cool it's probably
not that cool
Yeah, no, crashes are cool.
But no, I broke my wrist once.
That's the only time I ever broke my wrist.
That was rich.
I thought I broke my whole arm.
My whole arm, I couldn't feel it.
I didn't understand that.
It was my wrist, but my whole arm, I was just like,
it just wouldn't work anymore.
I don't know, it was unusual.
Yeah, it feels like you fucking have liquid leaking.
Yeah, then I my mom was didn't she was mad at me about first of all my bike being fucked up and then second of all
Like she was just like you're fine. You're fine
I come from a sweeping under the rug or like put some dirt on it kind of family, which is fine
But fucking my shoe was actually broken and so it swelled up to the size of like a baseball mint
And then they find me the doctor, but they were like, oh also we need to re-break it because it won't set properly
So that's like double pain like fuck you mom. That was rude. So God bless her soul, but fuck you
Well, yeah, when I broke my wrist, they said that it was so clean that I was just super lucky
So it was already healing back together
once uh
But I fucking felt about the clock and then
Yeah, I just feel like the marrow. I guess we can
Marrow, okay, so like
When you break a bone, they sit at least on your back. Well, of course, of course now. I know what you're talking about
It's just like, um, did you have to wear a caster? Did they just like yeah, I cast I cast her
little over
What's that bad?
Yeah, it wasn't horrible
I
Broke a bunch of shit not doing any dirt biking last year. I was fucking golfing
I fucked up a bunch of shit that kept golfing and kept working full-time and did not
Even acknowledge the fact of the extent of my injuries and then it got worse and it got worse and it got worse than it
Like I honestly didn't know if I was gonna ever walk without a fucking little kitchen or a kitchen my giddy up because of it
But you know what we worked it out, but I actually took a break off YouTube when that happened
I kind of just fell off the
Face the earth, but I was so good. I mean it's my own fault. So like how do I complain about it? You know, why do you begin?
YouTube I always take a break from YouTube and then rediscover some part of myself
And you guys revamp the channel with if you will it's important to do that
They don't like it all they're saying they're telling me to take 60 of them pills Benjamin
Second mean what's going on? What are they doing? How the fuck did you?
blinds get
Alexander come up here and say that let's see no beezer
Peer
I'm gonna go roll a joint and
Let's like take his channel back over and I love all of you and also fuck you but with love
We make fun of everybody you guys girl. Just let's do something different for once, okay?
I don't care if it's positive. Just do something out of your norm for me. Please and thank you
I'm going to go. Bye-bye.
I'll stretch out feel the sunshine glow
Starts pumping nice and slow
Let your body away
Healthy choices every day you may choose on step strong take it through the street
Every little move is a victory
fruits and veggies on your plate fuel your power feeling great
Strong mind, strong mind
I'm gonna play outside
Yeah